<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:04.538" end="00:00:09.109">&gt;&gt; JANUARY 12th, 2012, FROM COMEDY CENTRAL&apos;S WORLD NEWS HEADQUARTERS IN NEW YORK </p>
<p begin="00:00:09.109" end="00:00:12.179">THIS IS THE DAILY SHOW WITH JON STEWART.</p>
<p begin="00:00:12.179" end="00:00:15.082">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)  <span tts:color="#ffff00">Captioning sponsored by</span> </p>
<p begin="00:00:15.082" end="00:00:18.352"> <span tts:color="#ffff00">COMEDY CENTRAL</span> </p>
<p begin="00:00:24.958" end="00:00:25.926">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELCOME TO THE DAILY SHOW.</p>
<p begin="00:00:25.926" end="00:00:26.527">MY NAME IS JON STEWART.</p>
<p begin="00:00:26.527" end="00:00:31.999">OUR GUEST TONIGHT, ONE OF MY FAVORITES, DOLLY PARTON IS GOING TO BE JOINING US.</p>
<p begin="00:00:31.999" end="00:00:33.000">SHE IS A FIRECRACKER.</p>
<p begin="00:00:33.000" end="00:00:34.368">I JUST LOVE HER TO DEATH.</p>
<p begin="00:00:34.368" end="00:00:36.770">WE&apos;RE SO GLAD SHE IS HERE TO JOIN US TONIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:36.770" end="00:00:40.841">BUT BEFORE WE GET TO THAT WE WANT TO BEGIN WITH THE REPUBLICAN PRIMARY RACE AND </p>
<p begin="00:00:40.841" end="00:00:48.448">THE TALE OF ONE NEWTON LEROY GINGRICH, WHO JUST LAST MONTH HAD READ THE ELECTORAL </p>
<p begin="00:00:48.448" end="00:00:53.520">TEA LEAVES AND WAS READY TO CALL THE PRIMARY FOR ONE NEWTON LEROY GINGRICH.</p>
<p begin="00:00:53.520" end="00:00:57.291">&gt;&gt; IT&apos;S VERY HARD NOT TO LOOK AT THE RECENT POLLS AND THINK THAT THE ODDS ARE VERY </p>
<p begin="00:00:57.291" end="00:00:59.693">HIGH I&apos;M GOING TO BE THE NOMINEE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:59.693" end="00:01:00.127">&gt;&gt; Jon: YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:01:00.127" end="00:01:03.697">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:01:03.697" end="00:01:05.132">&gt;&gt; Jon: IT&apos;S GETTING EASIER.</p>
<p begin="00:01:05.132" end="00:01:09.203">(LAUGHTER) YOU HAVE TO THINK ABOUT THE POLLS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:09.203" end="00:01:12.272">THEY ARE UNFORTUNATELY FOLLOWED BY THE VOTING.</p>
<p begin="00:01:12.272" end="00:01:15.342">THE TWO DON&apos;T REALLY MATCH UP EXACTLY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:15.342" end="00:01:17.377">&gt;&gt; NEWT GINGRICH CAME IN FOURTH IN IOWA.</p>
<p begin="00:01:17.377" end="00:01:21.148">&gt;&gt; NEWT GINGRICH FINISHED FOURTH LAST NIGHT IN NEW HAMPSHIRE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:21.148" end="00:01:25.886">&gt;&gt; Jon: SAY HELLO TO THE NEW PRESIDENT OF FOURTHLANDIA,</p>
<p begin="00:01:25.886" end="00:01:27.588">NEWT GINGRICH.</p>
<p begin="00:01:27.588" end="00:01:31.992">LISTEN, NEWTON LEROY GINGRICH ISN&apos;T GOING LET STION LIKE NOBODY VOTING FOR </p>
<p begin="00:01:31.992" end="00:01:34.394">HIM STOP HIM FROM BECOMING THE NOMINEE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:34.394" end="00:01:35.395">HE&apos;S PLAYING A LONG GAME.</p>
<p begin="00:01:35.395" end="00:01:40.601">THE NEXT STOP IS SOUTH CAROLINA, A STATE WHOSE POPULATION IS FAR MORE DIVERSE THAN IOWA AND NEW HAMPSHIRE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:40.601" end="00:01:43.637">NEWT DECIDED TO MAKE A BOLD PLAY TO EXPAND HIS BASE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:43.637" end="00:01:46.106">&gt;&gt; OBAMA IS THE BEST FOOD STAMP PRESIDENT IN AMERICAN HISTORY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:46.106" end="00:01:49.843">I WOULD LIKE TO BE THE BEST PAYCHECK PRESIDENT IN AMERICAN HISTORY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:49.843" end="00:01:56.617">I&apos;M PREPARED IF THE NAACP INVITES ME, I WILL GO TO THEIR CONVENTION AND TALK ABOUT WHY THE </p>
<p begin="00:01:56.617" end="00:02:02.055">AFRICAN-AMERICAN COMMUNITY SHOULD DEMAND PAYCHECKS AND NOT BE SATISFIED WITH FOOD STAMPS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:02.055" end="00:02:09.730">&gt;&gt; Jon: AND THEN I WILL STAND THERE AS THE APPLAUSE WASHES OVER ME--  (LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:02:09.730" end="00:02:14.835">AND GLADLY ACCEPT MY NEW TITLE AS THE KING OF KWANZA.</p>
<p begin="00:02:14.835" end="00:02:21.308">(LAUGHTER) NOW OBVIOUSLY SOME MAY QUIBBLE WITH THE IDEA THAT NEWT GINGRICH MUST ENTER </p>
<p begin="00:02:21.308" end="00:02:22.342">INTO-- YEAH, YOU LIKE THAT,</p>
<p begin="00:02:22.342" end="00:02:25.812">QUIBBLE WITH THE IDEA THAT NEWT GINGRICH MUST ENTER INTO THE BOWELS OF THE INNER </p>
<p begin="00:02:25.812" end="00:02:28.482">CITY TO EXPLAIN TO BLACK PEOPLE THE POWER OF THE PAYCHECK.</p>
<p begin="00:02:28.482" end="00:02:31.718">SOME MAY MENTION THAT HALF OF FOOD STAMP RECIPIENTS ARE ACTUALLY WHITE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:31.718" end="00:02:37.357">THAT 75% OF FAMILIES RECEIVING FOOD STAMPS ALSO BRING HOME AT LEAST ONE PAYCHECK SO THEY ALSO WORK.</p>
<p begin="00:02:37.357" end="00:02:41.795">IT MAY BE UNNECESSARY TO PERHAPS LECTURE AFRICAN-AMERICANS ON THEIR WORK ETHIC.</p>
<p begin="00:02:41.795" end="00:02:44.097">NEWT&apos;S GOT A PRETTY GOOD RESPONSE TO THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:44.097" end="00:02:50.504">&gt;&gt; THE DEMOCRATIC NATIONAL COMMITTEE TOOK TOTALLY OUT OF CONTEXT, HALF OF THE SENTENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:50.504" end="00:02:51.104">OKAY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:51.104" end="00:02:54.541">I MEAN CLEARLY AS SOMEBODY WHO HAS SERVED WITH COLIN POWELL, SOMEBODY WHO HAS </p>
<p begin="00:02:54.541" end="00:02:58.512">SERVED WITH CONDI RICE, I HAVE A FAIRLY GOOD SENSE THAT, IN FACT,</p>
<p begin="00:02:58.512" end="00:03:05.152">AFRICAN-AMERICANS HAVE MADE MANY CONTRIBUTIONS TO AMERICA.</p>
<p begin="00:03:05.152" end="00:03:07.387">&gt;&gt; Jon: FIRST OF ALL, SERVED WITH?</p>
<p begin="00:03:07.387" end="00:03:12.826">YOU MEAN WERE EMPLOYED BY THE GOVERNMENT AT THE SAME TIME AS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:12.826" end="00:03:17.064">BELIEVE ME, I HAVE A FAIRLY GOOD SENSE OF AFRICAN-AMERICAN&apos;S CONTRIBUTIONS AFTER ALL I&apos;M </p>
<p begin="00:03:17.064" end="00:03:23.070">TALKING TO YOU VIA A TELEVISION THE SAME BOX THAT ONCE BROADCAST THE COSBY SHOW SO I THINK-- AND OF </p>
<p begin="00:03:23.070" end="00:03:26.840">COURSE THE COSBY MYSTERIES WHICH WAS-- HERE IS THE GREAT THING ABOUT NEWTON </p>
<p begin="00:03:26.840" end="00:03:28.942">LEROY GINGRICH, HE IS NOT BEING DEFENSIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:28.942" end="00:03:35.749">HE&apos;S TRULY BEWILDERED THAT HE IS TAKING [BLEEP] FOR SAYING SOMETHING SO INCREDIBLY ALTRUISTIC.</p>
<p begin="00:03:35.749" end="00:03:39.520">&gt;&gt; I SAID I WOULD BE WILLING TO GO TO THE NAACP ANNUAL CONVENTION WHICH MOST </p>
<p begin="00:03:39.520" end="00:03:40.587">REPUBLICANS ARE NOT WILLING TO DO.</p>
<p begin="00:03:40.587" end="00:03:44.691">AND I WILL WOULD BE WILLING TO TALK ABOUT THE IMPORTANCE OF FOOD STAMPS VERSUS PAYCHECKS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:44.691" end="00:03:47.427">NOW I WOULD HAVE THOUGHT THERE WOULD HAVE BEEN A POSITIVE RESPONSE THAT SAYS </p>
<p begin="00:03:47.427" end="00:03:50.864">GOSH, HERE SAY REPUBLICAN WHO CARES ENOUGH THAT HE IS WILLING TO GO AND TALK TO </p>
<p begin="00:03:50.864" end="00:03:54.001">ONE OF THE MOST LEFT WING ORGANIZATIONS IN AMERICA,</p>
<p begin="00:03:54.001" end="00:03:59.106">ABOUT HOW TO HELP THE PEOPLE THEY REPRESENT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:59.106" end="00:04:00.774">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:04:00.774" end="00:04:05.412">&gt;&gt; Jon: I&apos;M WILLING TO HEAD DOWN TO THE SLUMS OF BALTIMORE, TAKING MY LIFE </p>
<p begin="00:04:05.412" end="00:04:10.350">INTO MY OWN HANDS AND TEACH YOU PEOPLE WHAT A PAYCHECK LOOKS LIKE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:10.350" end="00:04:14.121">I BELIEVE THE PHRASE YOU&apos;RE LOOKING FOR IS THANK YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:04:14.121" end="00:04:20.827">(LAUGHTER) FOR MORE SENIOR POLITICAL ANALYST WYATT CENAC JOINS US RIGHT NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:04:20.827" end="00:04:27.367">WYATT WHAT DO YOU MAKE-- WHAT DOW MAKE OF THESE, WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF THESE LATEST REMARKS BY NEWT GINGRICH.</p>
<p begin="00:04:27.367" end="00:04:28.402">&gt;&gt; JON, LET&apos;S JUST SAY IT,</p>
<p begin="00:04:28.402" end="00:04:31.839">THAT IS SOME RACIST BULL </p>
<p begin="00:04:31.839" end="00:04:32.172">[BLEEP].</p>
<p begin="00:04:32.172" end="00:04:33.907">I MEAN IT IS 2012.</p>
<p begin="00:04:33.907" end="00:04:36.276">WHAT TOOK HIM SO LONG.</p>
<p begin="00:04:36.276" end="00:04:39.179">&gt;&gt; Jon: WAIT, ARE YOU UP SET HE HASN&apos;T MADE RACIST REMARKS SOONER.</p>
<p begin="00:04:39.179" end="00:04:43.450">&gt;&gt; I DON&apos;T KNOW IF HIS REMARKS WERE RACIST, THAT&apos;S JUST NEWT BEING </p>
<p begin="00:04:43.450" end="00:04:47.855">CONDESCENDINGING AND DICKISH OR AS HE CALLS IT, TALKING.</p>
<p begin="00:04:47.855" end="00:04:49.623">WHAT&apos;S RACIST IS HIS TIMING.</p>
<p begin="00:04:49.623" end="00:04:54.995">IT TOOK GINGRICH UNTIL NOW TO BE CONDESCENDING AND DICKISH TO BLACK PEOPLE?</p>
<p begin="00:04:54.995" end="00:04:58.532">FIVE YEARS AGO HE WAS ALREADY DOING THIS TO HISPANICS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:58.532" end="00:05:04.238">&gt;&gt; WE SHOULD REPLACE BILINGUAL EDUCATION WITH IMMERSION IN ENGLISH SO THEY </p>
<p begin="00:05:04.238" end="00:05:12.479">LEARN THE LANGUAGE OF PROSPERITY, NOT THE LANGUAGE OF LIVING IN A GHETTO.</p>
<p begin="00:05:12.479" end="00:05:17.851">&gt;&gt; I NEVER HEARD HIM SAY THAT ABOUT RAT MUSIC OR EBONICS, WHAT, OUR LANGUAGE </p>
<p begin="00:05:17.851" end="00:05:20.254">OF LIVING IN THE GHETTO ISN&apos;T GOOD ENOUGH FOR HIM?</p>
<p begin="00:05:20.254" end="00:05:22.055">&gt;&gt; Jon: CAN I JUST GO BACK FOR A SECOND.</p>
<p begin="00:05:22.055" end="00:05:25.092">DID YOU JUST SAY SPANISH WAS THE LANGUAGE OF THE GHETTO?</p>
<p begin="00:05:25.092" end="00:05:31.131">&gt;&gt; OH, NO, BUT HE APOLOGIZED IN BROKEN GHETTO LANGUAGE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:31.131" end="00:05:47.247">&gt;&gt; SPEAKING SPANISH).</p>
<p begin="00:05:47.247" end="00:05:48.115">&gt;&gt; YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:05:48.115" end="00:05:53.954">IN THE CRAPPIEST SPANISH EVER, THAT GUY ALREADY PATRONIZED AND APOLOGISED TO </p>
<p begin="00:05:53.954" end="00:05:58.392">HISPANICS BEFORE HE EVER GOT AROUND TO INSULTING BLACK PEOPLE!</p>
<p begin="00:05:58.392" end="00:06:04.932">&gt;&gt; Jon: BUT, BUT ISN&apos;T THAT IN AND OF ITSELF BY IGNORING BLACK PEOPLE INSULTING AND PATRONIZING.</p>
<p begin="00:06:04.932" end="00:06:06.900">&gt;&gt; NO, DON&apos;T TRY AND MAKE ME FEEL BETTER.</p>
<p begin="00:06:06.900" end="00:06:10.637">THIS GUY HAS BEEN A DICK TO GAYS, OTHER REPUBLICANS,</p>
<p begin="00:06:10.637" end="00:06:12.406">SCIENCE, WOMEN.</p>
<p begin="00:06:12.406" end="00:06:13.674">&gt;&gt; TALKING ABOUT BEING IN COMBAT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:13.674" end="00:06:15.409">WHAT IS COMBAT MEAN?</p>
<p begin="00:06:15.409" end="00:06:22.549">IF COMBAT MEANS LIVING IN A DITCH, FEMALES HAVE BIOLOGICAL PROBLEMS STAYING IN A DITCH FOR 30 DAYS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:22.549" end="00:06:25.619">BECAUSE THEY GET INFECTIONS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:25.619" end="00:06:29.690">&gt;&gt; RIGHT, RIGHT, WOMEN ARE TOO FRAIL TO SERVE IN THE MILITARY.</p>
<p begin="00:06:29.690" end="00:06:34.161">THIS COMING FROM A GUY WHO PROBABLY CAN&apos;T GET OUT OF A POOL BY HIMSELF.</p>
<p begin="00:06:34.161" end="00:06:40.501">(LAUGHTER) (CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) </p>
<p begin="00:06:40.501" end="00:06:46.673">&gt;&gt; I MEAN LOOK, HE WAS CONDESCENDING AND DICKISH TO A CERTAIN PEOPLE THREE </p>
<p begin="00:06:46.673" end="00:06:49.209">MONTHS BEFORE GOING AFTER BLACK PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:49.209" end="00:06:57.217">&gt;&gt; AND I THINK THAT WE HAVE HADN&apos;T INVENTED PALESTINIAN PEOPLE WHO-- WERE </p>
<p begin="00:06:57.217" end="00:06:58.652">HISTORICALLY PART OF THE ARAB COMMUNITY.</p>
<p begin="00:06:58.652" end="00:07:01.522">&gt;&gt; HE DOESN&apos;T THINK PALESTINIAN PEOPLE EXIST,</p>
<p begin="00:07:01.522" end="00:07:02.389">JON!</p>
<p begin="00:07:02.389" end="00:07:08.095">I MEAN I&apos;M SURPRISED THE GUY DIDN&apos;T [BLEEP] SMURFS BEFORE THINKING BLACK PEOPLE ARE </p>
<p begin="00:07:08.095" end="00:07:11.164">WORTHY OF HIS DISDAIN.</p>
<p begin="00:07:11.164" end="00:07:13.200">&gt;&gt; Jon: WYATT, MAYBE HE IS JUST SAVING THE BEST FOR LAST.</p>
<p begin="00:07:13.200" end="00:07:18.338">&gt;&gt; NO, NO, HUH-UH, WE HAVE WORKED TOO HARD AND COME TOO FAR TO NOT HAVE SOMEONE TELL </p>
<p begin="00:07:18.338" end="00:07:21.708">US WE DIDN&apos;T WORK HARD ENOUGH.</p>
<p begin="00:07:21.708" end="00:07:22.442">NO.</p>
<p begin="00:07:22.442" end="00:07:26.580">BLACK PEOPLE SHOULD NOT HAVE TO SIT AT THE BACK OF THE BUS WAITING FOR SOMEONE TO </p>
<p begin="00:07:26.580" end="00:07:30.617">CALL US LAZY FOR BEING AT THE BACK OF THE BUS.</p>
<p begin="00:07:30.617" end="00:07:32.052">&gt;&gt; Jon: THANK YOU, WYATT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:32.052" end="00:07:32.653">WYATT CENAC,</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
