<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:07.040" end="00:00:07.608">&gt;&gt; WELCOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:07.608" end="00:00:12.779">MY GUEST TONIGHT, A TWO-TIME PULITZER PRIZE WINNING AUTHOR, AFTER SEEING THIS I </p>
<p begin="00:00:12.779" end="00:00:17.618">THINK IT&apos;S GOING TO BE-- THE NEW BOOK IS THE FOURTH ABOUT PRESIDENT LYNDON B JOHNSON,</p>
<p begin="00:00:17.618" end="00:00:20.754">IS CALLED THE YEARS OF LYNDON JOHN SORNING THE PASSAGE OF POWER.</p>
<p begin="00:00:20.754" end="00:00:26.860">PLEASE WELCOME TO THE PROGRAM ROBERT CARO.</p>
<p begin="00:00:26.860" end="00:00:31.899">VERY NICE TO SEE YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:00:31.899" end="00:00:32.933">WELCOME.</p>
<p begin="00:00:32.933" end="00:00:34.468">&gt;&gt; Stephen: THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.</p>
<p begin="00:00:34.468" end="00:00:37.771">I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT WE HAVE A LOT OF AUTHORS ON THE PROGRAM.</p>
<p begin="00:00:37.771" end="00:00:39.473">AND ARE YOU PREMIUM SHELF.</p>
<p begin="00:00:39.473" end="00:00:42.576">YOU OFFER HISTORICAL,</p>
<p begin="00:00:42.576" end="00:00:46.980">NONFICTION NERDS SUCH AS MYSELF, ARE YOU THE GOLD STANDARD, SIR, AND I APPRECIATE YOU BEING HERE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:46.980" end="00:00:52.519">AND I ALWAYS TRY AND MAKE A GREAT EFFORT TO READ EVERY AUTHOR&apos;S BOOK THAT COMES ON </p>
<p begin="00:00:52.519" end="00:00:53.153">THE PROGRAM.</p>
<p begin="00:00:53.153" end="00:01:00.627">AND I JUST WANT TO YELL--  (LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:01:00.627" end="00:01:05.732">&gt;&gt; Jon: I&apos;M STILL GETTING THROUGH EPISODE TWO OF THERE IS THE PASSAGE TO POWER.</p>
<p begin="00:01:05.732" end="00:01:10.571">THIS IS YOUR FOURTH WORK HERE, THE FOURTH VOLUME, IS REALLY WHERE THE RUBBER HITS </p>
<p begin="00:01:10.571" end="00:01:12.539">THE ROAD FOR JOHNSON S IT NOT?</p>
<p begin="00:01:12.539" end="00:01:17.077">&gt;&gt; YES, BECAUSE HE&apos;S CONFRONTED WITH JACK KENNEDY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:17.077" end="00:01:23.217">HE&apos;S THE SENATE MAJORITY LEADER, HE THINKS HE HAS THE DEMOCRATIC NOMINATION LOCKED UP IN 1960.</p>
<p begin="00:01:23.217" end="00:01:26.954">DOESN&apos;T REALIZE THAT THIS YOUNG SENATOR IS RACING AROUND THE COUNTRY ACTUALLY </p>
<p begin="00:01:26.954" end="00:01:28.655">GETTING THE DELEGATES.</p>
<p begin="00:01:28.655" end="00:01:30.090">&gt;&gt; Jon: AND HE DID NOT,</p>
<p begin="00:01:30.090" end="00:01:33.427">LYNDON JOHNSON DID NOT REALLY HAVE MUCH RESPECT FOR JOHN KENNEDY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:33.427" end="00:01:35.128">&gt;&gt; NO, HE HAD NO RESPECT AT ALL.</p>
<p begin="00:01:35.128" end="00:01:39.266">YOU KNOW WHAT HE SAID ABOUT KENNEDY AS A SENATOR, HE SAID HE WAS PATHETIC.</p>
<p begin="00:01:39.266" end="00:01:41.602">HE DIDN&apos;T EVEN KNOW HOW TO ADDRESS THE CHAIR.</p>
<p begin="00:01:41.602" end="00:01:46.106">AND HE USED TO MAKE FUN OF HOW SKINNY HE WAS BECAUSE HE WAS SICK ALL THE TIME.</p>
<p begin="00:01:46.106" end="00:01:52.145">HE USED TO SAY YOU EVER SEE KEN DOE&apos;S ANKLES, THEY&apos;RE ABOUT THIS BIG AROUND.</p>
<p begin="00:01:52.145" end="00:01:55.549">&gt;&gt; Jon: SO HE WAS HE THOUGHT HE COULD KNOCK KENNEDY AROUND.</p>
<p begin="00:01:55.549" end="00:02:02.823">WHEN KENNEDY WINS THE NOMINATION, WHY DO YOU THINK JOHNSON TOOK THE VICE PRESIDENT SEE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:02.823" end="00:02:08.061">&gt;&gt; WELL, YOU KNOW, HE SAID I DON&apos;T THINK ANY SOUTHERNER CAN GET NOMINATED IN MY LIFE TIME.</p>
<p begin="00:02:08.061" end="00:02:13.066">AND HE WAS RIGHT BECAUSE THE BIG DEMOCRATIC NORTHERN LIBERAL STATES WERE </p>
<p begin="00:02:13.066" end="00:02:17.471">DESTRUCTED, THE SOUTHERNERS CONTROLLED THE CON VECHBLINGTS HE ONCE CALCULATED AND THE STAFF </p>
<p begin="00:02:17.471" end="00:02:20.174">CALCULATESED HOW MANY PRESIDENTS DIED IN OFFICE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:20.174" end="00:02:23.577">AND IT IS ABOUT ONE OUT OF SIX, AT THE SEEMMENT-- TIME.</p>
<p begin="00:02:23.577" end="00:02:24.945">AND HE USED TO SAY TO PEOPLE,</p>
<p begin="00:02:24.945" end="00:02:29.816">YOU KNOW, WHEN THEY ASKED HIM WHY DID HE PICK THE VICE PRESIDENT SEE, HE WOULD SAY </p>
<p begin="00:02:29.816" end="00:02:33.587">WELL, YOU KNOW, SIX OF THEM DIDN&apos;T HAVE TO GET ELECTED.</p>
<p begin="00:02:33.587" end="00:02:35.622">&gt;&gt; Jon: SO HE WAS A VERY SWEET MAN.</p>
<p begin="00:02:35.622" end="00:02:37.958">BUT WHAT IS AMAZE BEING THAT,</p>
<p begin="00:02:37.958" end="00:02:43.430">WHAT MOVES HIS CHARACTER IN THIS AND I THINK YOU SEE THAT, IS EVERYTHING WAS STRATEGY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:43.430" end="00:02:48.836">HE WAS AS YOU SAY, PERHAPS THE WORLD&apos;S GREATEST LEGISLATOR, THAT HE HAD THE </p>
<p begin="00:02:48.836" end="00:02:50.270">SKILL KENNEDY DID NOT HAVE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:50.270" end="00:02:51.305">&gt;&gt; YES, HE DID.</p>
<p begin="00:02:51.305" end="00:02:55.709">AND WE SEE IT IN THE CIVIL RIGHTS BILL, YOU KNOW, WHEN OBAMA MADE HIS ANNOUNCEMENT </p>
<p begin="00:02:55.709" end="00:03:01.682">ABOUT GAY RIGHTS, I FLASHED BACK TO JOHNSON FOUR DAYS AFTER PRESIDENT KENNEDY IS ASSASSINATED.</p>
<p begin="00:03:01.682" end="00:03:06.053">HE HAS TO GIVE HIS FIRST SPEECH TO CONGRESS AND HIS ADVISORS ARE SITTING AROUND </p>
<p begin="00:03:06.053" end="00:03:07.421">SAYING DON&apos;T MENTION CIVIL RIGHTS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:07.421" end="00:03:10.490">DON&apos;T USE UP YOUR POLITICAL CAPITAL ON CIVIL RIGHTS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:10.490" end="00:03:12.626">IT&apos;S A GREAT CAUSE BUT A LOST CAUSE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:12.626" end="00:03:13.894">YOU KNOW WHAT JOHNSON SAYS,</p>
<p begin="00:03:13.894" end="00:03:15.596">HE SAY WAS IS A PRESIDENT SEE FOR THEN.</p>
<p begin="00:03:15.596" end="00:03:19.700">AND HE TAKES THIS, HE SAYS IN HIS SPEECH, THE FIRST THING WE HAVE TO DO IS PASS </p>
<p begin="00:03:19.700" end="00:03:21.101">THE CIVIL RIGHTS BILL.</p>
<p begin="00:03:21.101" end="00:03:25.339">&gt;&gt; Jon: AND HE SHOWED REAL COURAGE IN THAT, AND THAT IS WHAT IS SO INTERESTING IS </p>
<p begin="00:03:25.339" end="00:03:28.609">YOU, THE BOOKS PAINT THIS VERY COMPLEX PICTURE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:28.609" end="00:03:35.082">AND IT ALMOST, DO YOU THINK HE WAS ONE OF THE MOST COMPLEX OF OUR PRESIDENTS </p>
<p begin="00:03:35.082" end="00:03:38.185">BECAUSE OF HIS ABILITY TO LEGISLATE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:38.185" end="00:03:44.258">&gt;&gt; YES, I THINK HE WAS, I MEAN HE WAS A GENIUS IN PASSING LEGISLATION.</p>
<p begin="00:03:44.258" end="00:03:47.327">HE ALWAYS WANTED TO HELP POOR PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:47.327" end="00:03:49.363">AND PARTICULARLY POOR PEOPLE OF COLOR.</p>
<p begin="00:03:49.363" end="00:03:54.434">AND HE SAYS WHEN HE GETS INTO THE PRESIDENCY, YOU KNOW, I ALWAYS SWORE IF I </p>
<p begin="00:03:54.434" end="00:03:56.570">HAD THE POWER TO HELP THEM,</p>
<p begin="00:03:56.570" end="00:03:57.237">I WOULD DO IT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:57.237" end="00:04:00.707">I WILL TILL A SECRET, I HAVE THE POWER NOW AND HE DID IT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:00.707" end="00:04:06.113">HE PUSHES THE CIVIL RIGHTS AND VOTING RIGHTS BILLS TO PASSAGE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:06.113" end="00:04:09.917">&gt;&gt; Jon: INCREDIBLE MOMENT WHERE YOU--  (APPLAUSE) THAT IS CORRECT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:09.917" end="00:04:14.855">SPEAKING TO HIS ABILITY AS SORT OF A TACTICIAN AND STRATEGIST IN WAITING, THE </p>
<p begin="00:04:14.855" end="00:04:17.124">VICE PRESIDENT SEE REMOVES ALL POWER FROM HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:04:17.124" end="00:04:20.894">THE KENNEDY GOES OUT OF THEIR WAY TO HUMILIATE HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:04:20.894" end="00:04:21.261">&gt;&gt; YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:04:21.261" end="00:04:26.400">&gt;&gt; Jon: IN DALLAS ON THAT TERRIBLE DAY, HE IS NOTIFIED AT THIS HOSPITAL, HE IS </p>
<p begin="00:04:26.400" end="00:04:28.936">CALLED MR. PRESIDENT FOR THE FIRST TIME.</p>
<p begin="00:04:28.936" end="00:04:32.940">AND YOU HAVE AN AMAZING SECTION ABOUT HOW HE KIND OF COMES TO LIFE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:32.940" end="00:04:33.540">&gt;&gt; YES.</p>
<p begin="00:04:33.540" end="00:04:35.075">&gt;&gt; HE IS TRANSFORMED.</p>
<p begin="00:04:35.075" end="00:04:39.346">AND ONE OF HIS ASSISTANTS SAYS TO ME, HE WAS BACK WHERE HE BELONG.</p>
<p begin="00:04:39.346" end="00:04:41.748">HE WAS BACK IN CHARGE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:41.748" end="00:04:45.853">AND LADY BIRD, SEEING HIM STANDING THERE, WAITING FOR 40 MINUTES WHERE NO ONE </p>
<p begin="00:04:45.853" end="00:04:47.221">TELLS HIM IF HE IS PRESIDENT OR NOT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:47.221" end="00:04:51.925">HE KEEPS SAYING SEND SOMEONE OUT, TELL ME KENNEDY&apos;S CONDITION.</p>
<p begin="00:04:51.925" end="00:04:54.361">ALL THEY WILL SAY IS THE DOCTORS ARE STILL WORK.</p>
<p begin="00:04:54.361" end="00:05:02.135">THEN LADY BIRD SAYS SEEING PENNY O DOM OHL, KENNEDY&apos;S ASSISTANT, SEEING THE </p>
<p begin="00:05:02.135" end="00:05:04.905">STRICTEN FACE OF PENNY O&apos;DONNELL WHO LOVED HIM, WE KNEW.</p>
<p begin="00:05:04.905" end="00:05:11.044">A MOMENT LATER ANOTHER ASSISTANT CAME IN AND SAID MR. PRESIDENT, AND INSTANTLY HE IS IN CHARGE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:11.044" end="00:05:14.047">&gt;&gt; Jon: AND HE DOES, THE FIRST DECISION MAKES IS A STRATEGIC ONE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:14.047" end="00:05:16.450">THEY WANT HIM TO FLY BACK TO WASHINGTON.</p>
<p begin="00:05:16.450" end="00:05:17.150">EVERYBODY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:17.150" end="00:05:20.053">&gt;&gt; THE SECRET SERVICE AGENT SAYS WE HAVE TO GET YOU TO THE PLANE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:20.053" end="00:05:23.056">WE HAVE TO TAKE OFF IMMEDIATELY AND GET YOU BACK TO THE WHITE HOUSE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:23.056" end="00:05:25.325">BECAUSE NO ONE KNOWS IF IT IS A CONSPIRACY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:25.325" end="00:05:28.529">JOHNSON SAYS NO, I&apos;M NOT LEAVING WITHOUT MRS. KENNEDY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:28.529" end="00:05:32.199">THEY SAY WELL SHE WON&apos;T LEAVE WITHOUT HER HUSBAND&apos;S BODY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:32.199" end="00:05:36.970">HE SAYS I WILL GO TO THE PLANE BUT I WON&apos;T LEAVE UNTIL SHE AND THE COFFIN ARE ABOARD.</p>
<p begin="00:05:36.970" end="00:05:40.774">&gt;&gt; Jon: AND HE MAKES A DECISION TO HAVE HER NEXT TO HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:05:40.774" end="00:05:41.708">&gt;&gt; YES.</p>
<p begin="00:05:41.708" end="00:05:44.778">&gt;&gt; AS HE IS SWORN IN AS A SHOW OF A PEACEFUL TRANSFER.</p>
<p begin="00:05:44.778" end="00:05:46.146">BUT EVERYTHING IS DONE WITH PURPOSE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:46.146" end="00:05:49.183">&gt;&gt; WITH JOHNSON EVERYTHING HAS A POLITICAL PURPOSE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:49.183" end="00:05:55.322">AND USUALLY A POLITICAL GENIUS AND SOMETHING PERSONAL IN IT YOU KNOW, HIS REFUSING TO LEAVE DALLAS </p>
<p begin="00:05:55.322" end="00:05:57.858">WITHOUT JACKIE KENNEDY THERE IS A POLITICAL PURPOSE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:57.858" end="00:06:01.094">BUT THERE ISAS, YOU COULD SAY A HUMANITARIAN PURPOSE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:01.094" end="00:06:04.498">I&apos;M NOT LEAVING HER BEHIND IN DALLAS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:04.498" end="00:06:07.034">&gt;&gt; Jon: HIS RELATIONSHIP WITH BOBBY AFTERWARDS IS FASCINATING.</p>
<p begin="00:06:07.034" end="00:06:12.573">&gt;&gt; THESE ARE TWO MEN, AS A HISTORIAN, YOU HATE TO USE THE WORD &quot;HATE&quot; BECAUSE IT </p>
<p begin="00:06:12.573" end="00:06:13.507">IS SO STRONG.</p>
<p begin="00:06:13.507" end="00:06:18.378">BUT HATE ISN&apos;T TOO STRONG TO DESCRIBE BOBBY KENNEDY AND LYNDON JOHNSON.</p>
<p begin="00:06:18.378" end="00:06:24.051">WHEN JOHNSON IS VICE PRESIDENT, ROBERT KENNEDY SELDOM INVITES HIM, HE HAD GREAT PARTIES AT HICKORY HILL.</p>
<p begin="00:06:24.051" end="00:06:27.421">WHEN JOHNSON IS INVITED HE&apos;S PUT AT WHAT ROBERT KENNEDY&apos;S </p>
<p begin="00:06:27.421" end="00:06:29.823">WIFE ETHYL CALLS THE LOSER&apos;S TABLE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:29.823" end="00:06:32.559">AND JOHNSON KNOW OS IT&apos;S THE LOSER&apos;S TABLE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:32.559" end="00:06:35.295">&gt;&gt; Jon: I&apos;VE BEEN AT THAT TABLE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:35.295" end="00:06:38.332">AND THEN AFTERWARDS HE HAS A PHONE CALL WITH ROBERT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:38.332" end="00:06:38.699">&gt;&gt; YES.</p>
<p begin="00:06:38.699" end="00:06:40.100">ONE OF THE MOST, YOU KNOW,</p>
<p begin="00:06:40.100" end="00:06:43.837">THE MAN WHO TOLD ME ABOUT THIS CALL, NICHOLAS-- DIED YESTERDAY.</p>
<p begin="00:06:43.837" end="00:06:46.240">HE WAS ROBERT KENNEDY&apos;S DEPUTY ATTORNEY GENERAL.</p>
<p begin="00:06:46.240" end="00:06:51.078">AND I SAID WHAT IS THE REASON FOR THE CALL, YOU KNOW, JOHNSON FROM AIR FORCE </p>
<p begin="00:06:51.078" end="00:06:57.784">ONE CALLS ROBERT KENNEDY, A FEW MINUTES AFTER HE IS LEARNED THAT THE BROTHER HE </p>
<p begin="00:06:57.784" end="00:06:58.886">LOVED SO MUCH IS DEAD.</p>
<p begin="00:06:58.886" end="00:07:04.024">TO ASK HIM THE FORMALITIES OF HOW HE TAKES OVER HIS BROTHER&apos;S POSITION.</p>
<p begin="00:07:04.024" end="00:07:06.727">AND CATSENBACH SAID YOU KNOW,</p>
<p begin="00:07:06.727" end="00:07:12.533">COHAVE TOLD ME, COHAVE CALLED ANY ONE OF A HUNDRED GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS, FORGET </p>
<p begin="00:07:12.533" end="00:07:16.270">THE WORDING OF THE OATH OF OFFICE, WE ALL KNEW IT AND I SPOKE TO JOHNSON&apos;S SECRETARY </p>
<p begin="00:07:16.270" end="00:07:17.671">WHO TOOK DOWN THE OATH OF OFFICE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:17.671" end="00:07:19.039">I SAID WELL WHAT WAS IT LIKE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:19.039" end="00:07:24.144">HE SAID WELL CATSENBACH VOICE WAS LIKE STEAL.</p>
<p begin="00:07:24.144" end="00:07:27.214">HE SAID ROBERT KENNEDY&apos;S WAS NOT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:27.214" end="00:07:28.916">I THOUGHT YOU SHOULDN&apos;T BE DOING THIS.</p>
<p begin="00:07:28.916" end="00:07:35.255">AS I WENT TO THE DOOR LEAVING AFTER HE HAD BEEN VERY CAREFULLY LAYING OUT THE THINGS ON BOTH SIDES,</p>
<p begin="00:07:35.255" end="00:07:38.158">WHY JOHNSON CAUSE HE SAID YOU KNOW TO TILL THE TRUTH,</p>
<p begin="00:07:38.158" end="00:07:43.463">THE FACT THAT LYNDON JOHNSON CALLED ROBERT KENNEDY AT THAT MOMENT OS, I WAS APPALLED.</p>
<p begin="00:07:43.463" end="00:07:44.364">&gt;&gt; YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:07:44.364" end="00:07:46.066">&gt;&gt; IT&apos;S AN UNBELIEVABLE STORY.</p>
<p begin="00:07:46.066" end="00:07:48.468">THE DETAIL THAT YOU ARE ABLE TO RING OUT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:48.468" end="00:07:50.571">HISTORY, THE WAY YOU MADE IT COME ALIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:50.571" end="00:07:52.573">YOUR PASSION FOR IT IS JUST MAGNIFICENT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:52.573" end="00:07:55.342">I REALLY APPRECIATE YOU BEING ON THE SHOW AND THE BOOK IS PHENOMENAL.</p>
<p begin="00:07:55.342" end="00:07:58.078">THE PASSAGE OF POWER ON THE BOOK SHELVES NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:07:58.078" end="00:07:59.079">ROBERT CARO, EVERYBODY.</p>
<p begin="00:07:59.079" end="00:08:00.013">THANK YOU SO MUCH.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
