<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:04.705" end="00:00:08.809">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELCOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:08.809" end="00:00:11.912">PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE MITT ROMNEY CONTINUES TO REFUSE TO RELEASE HIS TAX RETURNS </p>
<p begin="00:00:11.912" end="00:00:15.382">FROM ANY YEAR PRIOR TO THE YEARS HE WAS RUNNING FOR, I DON&apos;T KNOW, THE PRESIDENCY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:15.382" end="00:00:21.255">(LAUGHTER) BECAUSE AS HIS WIFE ANN ROMNEY EXPLAINED TODAY Y DON&apos;T YOU ALL SHUT UP.</p>
<p begin="00:00:21.255" end="00:00:24.858">&gt;&gt; WE&apos;VE GIVEN ALL YOU PEOPLE NEED TO KNOW AND UNDERSTAND ABOUT OUR </p>
<p begin="00:00:24.858" end="00:00:28.262">FINANCIAL SITUATION AND ABOUT HOW WE LIVE OUR LIFE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:28.262" end="00:00:29.897">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU KNOW ENOUGH!</p>
<p begin="00:00:29.897" end="00:00:30.964">YOU HAVE LEARNED THAT WE,</p>
<p begin="00:00:30.964" end="00:00:39.306">THE ROMNEYS, LIVE IN THE GRAY KNELTER-- NETHERWORLD BETWIXT WHAT IS LEGAL AND WHAT IS MORAL.</p>
<p begin="00:00:39.306" end="00:00:42.943">WHERE DESIRE MEETS POWER AND ONE FIGHT GET ITS DRUNK,</p>
<p begin="00:00:42.943" end="00:00:47.047">SLEEPS AND HAS A BABY NAMED PRIVILEGED T MONEYBUCKS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:47.047" end="00:00:52.819">BUT AS YOU MAY REMEMBER YESTERDAY I REVEALED THAT WE HERE AT THE DAILY SHOW HAVE </p>
<p begin="00:00:52.819" end="00:01:11.972">COME INTO POSSESSION OF THE SECRET TAX RETURNS IN A SEGMENT WE CALL-- HOW DID WE DO IT!</p>
<p begin="00:01:11.972" end="00:01:17.644">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) HOW DID WE DO IT?</p>
<p begin="00:01:17.644" end="00:01:22.082">HOW DID WE GET ACCESS TO ALL OF HIS TAX RETURNS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:22.082" end="00:01:23.083">WE MADE IT UP.</p>
<p begin="00:01:23.083" end="00:01:29.189">(LAUGHTER) SUCK ON THAT, WILL McEVOY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:29.189" end="00:01:31.191">LET&apos;S GET TO IT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:31.191" end="00:01:37.097">YESTERDAY IN OUR FORUMS WE LEARNED SOME OF THE WAY ITS ROMNEY SPENDS HIS MONEY ARE </p>
<p begin="00:01:37.097" end="00:01:38.098">SOMEWHAT EXCESSIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:38.098" end="00:01:40.100">BUT NOBODY CARES THAT HE&apos;S RICH.</p>
<p begin="00:01:40.100" end="00:01:46.907">THEY CARE ABOUT THE INSTITUTIONAL ADVANTAGE THAT HE HAS GOTTEN THROUGH TAX CODE LARGESSE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:46.907" end="00:01:50.644">SEE, HE&apos;S BEEN DOGGED BY ALLEGATION THESE HIDES HIS MONEY IN TAX-FREE OFFSHORE </p>
<p begin="00:01:50.644" end="00:02:00.153">ACCOUNTS IN PLACES LIKE THE CAYMANS, SWITZERLAND AND THAT ISLAND FROM &quot;LOST&quot; (LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:02:00.153" end="00:02:03.290">PROBLEM THERE IS IT TAKES SIX YEARS TO MAKE A WITHDRAWAL AND EVEN WHEN YOU </p>
<p begin="00:02:03.290" end="00:02:07.060">GET YOUR MONEY BACK YOU LOOK AT IT AND IT DOESN&apos;T MAKE ANY SENSE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:07.060" end="00:02:09.396">YOU STILL CAN&apos;T FIGURE IT OUT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:09.396" end="00:02:11.365">BUT UNDERSTAND THIS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:11.365" end="00:02:15.802">MR. ROMNEY HIDES HIS MONEY NOT BECAUSE HE DOESN&apos;T LOVE AMERICA, BUT BECAUSE HE </p>
<p begin="00:02:15.802" end="00:02:16.904">LOVES US SO MUCH.</p>
<p begin="00:02:16.904" end="00:02:18.238">HE KNOWS WHAT MONEY DOES TO PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:18.238" end="00:02:22.342">(LAUGHTER) HE DOESN&apos;T WANT TO SEE MONEY CORRUPT HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:02:22.342" end="00:02:26.113">OF COURSE MITT ROMNEY COULD ONLY KEEP SOME OF MONEY OFFSHORE WHICH IS WHY WE </p>
<p begin="00:02:26.113" end="00:02:30.617">FOUND IN THESE FORMS MITT ROMNEY HAS BEEN A PIONEER IN A NEW SYSTEM OF TAX </p>
<p begin="00:02:30.617" end="00:02:35.088">AVOIDANCE N 2006 HE PUT $12 MILLION INTO HOVER MONEY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:35.088" end="00:02:41.895">IT&apos;S ONE OF THOSE GAME SHOW STYLE CASH BLOWING MACHINES INSURANCING THAT HIS MONEY </p>
<p begin="00:02:41.895" end="00:02:44.298">NEVER TOUCHES AMERICAN SOIL LONG ENOUGH TO BE TAXABLE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:44.298" end="00:02:53.473">(LAUGHTER) A VAST IMPROVEMENT OVER HIS FIRST IDEA--  (APPLAUSE) A VAST IMPROVEMENT OVER THE </p>
<p begin="00:02:53.473" end="00:02:59.580">FIRST IDEA REINCOMED IN HIS 2005 RETURNS, HIRING MILLIONS OF MONEY JUGGLERS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:59.580" end="00:03:03.450">THIS IS ALL IN ADDITION TO ROMNEY&apos;S ON-SHORE OFF-SHORE ACCOUNTS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:03.450" end="00:03:08.155">ACCORDING TO HIS 2002 HE RETURN HE DIDN&apos;T JUST SEND MONEY TO SWITZERLAND, HE </p>
<p begin="00:03:08.155" end="00:03:10.557">PURCHASED A TOWN IN AMERICA FOR AN INTERNAL BANK,</p>
<p begin="00:03:10.557" end="00:03:15.395">POPULATED IT WITH SWISS PEOPLE AND STUFFED MONEY UP THEIR ASSESES, BECAUSE THE </p>
<p begin="00:03:15.395" end="00:03:21.168">INSIDES OF SWISS PEOPLE ALSO TECHNICALLY SWISS SOIL AND IMMUNE TO AMERICAN TAX LAW.</p>
<p begin="00:03:21.168" end="00:03:24.972">BY THE WAY F THAT&apos;S NOT UNCOMFORTABLE ENOUGH, INSIDE EACH ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE IS </p>
<p begin="00:03:24.972" end="00:03:30.110">ALSO A TOOTH PICK, TWEEZERS AND A CORK SCREW.</p>
<p begin="00:03:30.110" end="00:03:37.217">BECAUSE-- THEY&apos;RE SWISS AND ARE MULTIFUNCTIONAL.</p>
<p begin="00:03:37.217" end="00:03:39.253">YOU ARE PROBABLY ASKING,</p>
<p begin="00:03:39.253" end="00:03:42.956">WHAT HAPPENS IF HE NEEDS HIS MONEY RIGHT AWAY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:42.956" end="00:03:49.129">IT&apos;S IN SWISS PEOPLE&apos;S COLONS AND THEY ARE NOTORIOUSLY CONSTIPATED PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:49.129" end="00:03:57.104">(LAUGHTER) -- MUCILI YOU SAY, NO T WILL TAKE TOO LONG.</p>
<p begin="00:03:57.104" end="00:04:02.376">MITT ROMNEY PLAYS A GAME HE CALLS SWISS PINATA AND HE DOESN&apos;T EVEN WEAR A </p>
<p begin="00:04:02.376" end="00:04:06.480">BLINDFOLD WHERE IS THE FUN IF THAT, I&apos;M SAYING WHEN MITT ROMNEY NEEDS MONEY </p>
<p begin="00:04:06.480" end="00:04:10.951">QUICKLY HE BEATS A SWISS PERSON UNTIL THEY BREAK OPEN.</p>
<p begin="00:04:10.951" end="00:04:15.055">AT LEAST ACCORDING TO THE TAX PAPERS WE HAVE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:15.055" end="00:04:17.724">I&apos;M SURE IF THERE IS ANYTHING ELSE WE NEED UNDERSTAND ABOUT THE </p>
<p begin="00:04:17.724" end="00:04:19.660">FINANCIAL SITUATION, THEY&apos;LL LET US KNOW.</p>
<p begin="00:04:19.660" end="00:04:20.661">WELL&apos;S BE RIGHT BACK.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
