<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:00.000" end="00:00:00.300"> <span tts:color="#ffff00">Captioning sponsored by</span> </p>
<p begin="00:00:00.300" end="00:00:02.035"> <span tts:color="#ffff00">COMEDY CENTRAL</span> </p>
<p begin="00:00:03.170" end="00:00:10.177">&gt;&gt; MAY 2, 2012, FROM COMEDY CENTRAL&apos;S WORLD NEWS EADQUARTERS IN NEW YORK, THISH </p>
<p begin="00:00:10.177" end="00:00:17.618">IS THE &quot;THE &quot;DAILY SHOW&quot;&quot; WITH JON STEWART </p>
<p begin="00:00:17.951" end="00:00:20.320">( <span tts:fontStyle="italic">THEME SONG PLAYING</span> ) </p>
<p begin="00:00:20.654" end="00:00:26.293">( <span tts:fontStyle="italic">CHEERS AND APPLAUSE</span> ) .</p>
<p begin="00:00:26.293" end="00:00:27.861">&gt;&gt; Jon:  WELCOME TO THE DAILY SHOW.</p>
<p begin="00:00:27.861" end="00:00:34.635">MY GUEST, THE SENATOR THERE THE GREAT STATE OF OKLAHOMA, TOM COBURN, WILL BE JOINING US LATER.</p>
<p begin="00:00:34.635" end="00:00:37.237">HE&apos;S WRITTEN A BOOK-- IT&apos;S A COMEDY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:37.237" end="00:00:41.341">( LAUGHTER ) IT&apos;S ABOUT AMERICA AND HOW WE&apos;RE ALL GOING TO DIE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:41.341" end="00:00:45.279">( LAUGHTER ) BY THE WAY, WE&apos;LL RICK OFF THE TOP, THIS AFTERNOON WE GOT A BIG </p>
<p begin="00:00:45.279" end="00:00:49.383">ANNOUNCEMENT FROM THE ONE-TIME FRONT-RUNNER FOR THE REPUBLICAN PRESIDENTIAL NOMINATION.</p>
<p begin="00:00:49.383" end="00:00:49.950">&gt;&gt; TODAY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:49.950" end="00:00:51.351">&gt;&gt; I&apos;M SUSPENDING THE CAMPAIGN.</p>
<p begin="00:00:51.351" end="00:00:55.322">&gt;&gt; Jon:  WELL, THERE YOU HAVE IT, NOT ENDING, JUST SUSPENDING.</p>
<p begin="00:00:55.322" end="00:01:01.728">HE&apos;S SUSPENDING IT LIKE WE HULLA TO DO WITH OUR DISBELIEF WHEN HE THOUGHT HE WAS GOING TOOK PRESIDENT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:01.728" end="00:01:08.268">&gt;&gt; BUT SUSPENDING THE CEEM DOES NOT MEAN SUSPENDING CITIZENSHIP.</p>
<p begin="00:01:08.268" end="00:01:11.271">CALISTA AND I ARE COMMITTED TO BEING ACTIVE CITIZENS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:11.271" end="00:01:15.242">&gt;&gt; Jon:  WOULDN&apos;T IT BE AWESOME THOUGH IF IT DID MEAN SUSPENDING CITIZENSHIP?</p>
<p begin="00:01:15.242" end="00:01:21.081">LIKE IF YOU&apos;RE YOU LOSING A PRESIDENTIAL PRIMARY, YOU&apos;RE DEPORTED.</p>
<p begin="00:01:21.081" end="00:01:22.182">WOULDN&apos;T THAT AWESOME?</p>
<p begin="00:01:22.182" end="00:01:25.118">I DON&apos;T THINK ANYBODY THOUGHT THEY WOULD LEAVE THE COUNTRY BUT </p>
<p begin="00:01:25.118" end="00:01:29.256">IT&apos;S GOOD TO KNOW YOU MEMBER ACTIVE CITIZENS AND HAUNT PEOPLE ON JURY DUTY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:29.256" end="00:01:30.924">( LAUGHTER ).</p>
<p begin="00:01:30.924" end="00:01:33.660">LET&apos;S MOVE MOVE ON.</p>
<p begin="00:01:33.660" end="00:01:40.834">OUR MAIN STORY TOAPS FOCUSES ON THE MAN WHO DEFEATED NEWT GINGRICH.</p>
<p begin="00:01:40.834" end="00:01:45.772">AS YOU KNOW, MITT ROMNEY IS MORMON.</p>
<p begin="00:01:45.772" end="00:01:52.379">THAT&apos;S ACTUALLY, THAT&apos;S KIND OF UNNECESSARY-- HE&apos;S MORMON.</p>
<p begin="00:01:52.379" end="00:01:56.016">THERE&apos;S NOTHING-- THERE&apos;S NOTHING FRIGHTENING-- THERE&apos;S </p>
<p begin="00:01:56.016" end="00:02:02.923">NOTHING FRIGHTENING ABOUT HIM BEING A MORMON.</p>
<p begin="00:02:02.923" end="00:02:04.258">OKAY, YOU&apos;VE OVER-CORRECTED.</p>
<p begin="00:02:04.258" end="00:02:06.293">THAT WAS AN OVER-CORRECTION.</p>
<p begin="00:02:06.293" end="00:02:08.428">I SHOULD HAVE QUALIFIED THAT STATEMENT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:08.428" end="00:02:11.331">THERE&apos;S NOTHING FRIGHTENING ABOUT ROMNEY BEING A MORMON TO ME.</p>
<p begin="00:02:11.331" end="00:02:15.402">APPARENTLY, SOME IN THE REPUBLICAN PARTY&apos;S EVANGELICAL BASE THINK OTHERWISE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:15.402" end="00:02:19.106">&gt;&gt; MITT ROMNEY IS A GOOD MORAL PERSON BUT HE&apos;S NOT A CHRISTIAN.</p>
<p begin="00:02:19.106" end="00:02:21.341">MORMONNISM IS NOT CHRISTIANITY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:21.341" end="00:02:25.846">IT HAS ALWAYS BEEN CONSIDERED A CULT BY THE MAIN STREET OF CHRISTIANITY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:25.846" end="00:02:29.616">&gt;&gt; MOST CHRISTIANS WOULD NOT RECOGNIZE MORMONNISM AS PART OF THE CHRISTIAN FAITH.</p>
<p begin="00:02:29.616" end="00:02:32.519">&gt;&gt; WHAT THIS WOULD MEAN FOR THE SPIRITUAL HEALTH OF THE UNITED </p>
<p begin="00:02:32.519" end="00:02:37.824">STATES OF AMERICA IF A WORSHIPER OF A FALSE GOD OCCUPIED THE WHITE HOUSE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:37.824" end="00:02:38.525">&gt;&gt; Jon:  YES!</p>
<p begin="00:02:38.525" end="00:02:45.432">YOU WOULD NEVER WANT SOMEONE IN THE WHITE HOUSE WHO WORSHIPPED A DIFFERENT GOD THAN YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:02:45.432" end="00:02:52.906">IF I MAY, AS A JEW-- ( LAUGHTER ) YOU GET USED TO IT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:52.906" end="00:02:58.445">( LAUGHTER ) ( APPLAUSE ) BUT OF COURSE, THOSE COMMENT WERE MADE WHILE ROMNEY WAS STILL </p>
<p begin="00:02:58.445" end="00:03:00.581">DUKING IT OUT WITH REAL CHRISTIAN CANDIDATES.</p>
<p begin="00:03:00.581" end="00:03:05.052">NOW THAT A FALSE GOD HAS TRIUMPHED, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?</p>
<p begin="00:03:05.052" end="00:03:11.491">&gt;&gt; GIVEN THE CHOICE BETWEEN A CHRISTIAN LIKE BARACK OBAMA, WHO EMBRACES NON-BIBLICAL </p>
<p begin="00:03:11.491" end="00:03:17.898">PRINCIPLES, LIKE ABORTION, AND A MORMON LIKE MITT ROMNEY, WHO EMBRACES BIBLICAL PRINCIPLES,</p>
<p begin="00:03:17.898" end="00:03:20.400">THERE&apos;S EVERY REASON TO SUPPORT MITT ROMNEY IN THIS ELECTION.</p>
<p begin="00:03:20.400" end="00:03:22.402">&gt;&gt; Jon:  SIMPLE MATH.</p>
<p begin="00:03:22.402" end="00:03:24.471">( LAUGHTER ).</p>
<p begin="00:03:24.471" end="00:03:28.675">I HATE BARACK OBAMA MORE THAN I LOVE JESUS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:28.675" end="00:03:33.413">WHATEVER THE REASON, AT LEAST CONSERVATIVES WILL NOW FINALLY CEDE THEIR ANTI-MORMON ATTACKS </p>
<p begin="00:03:33.413" end="00:03:37.918">TO THE GROUP THAT&apos;S SUPPOSED TO BE MAKING ANTI-MORMON ATTACKS,</p>
<p begin="00:03:37.918" end="00:03:38.452">GODLESS DEMOCRATS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:38.452" end="00:03:42.289">&gt;&gt; MONTANA&apos;S DEMOCRATIC GOVERNOR, BRIAN SWRIETSER,</p>
<p begin="00:03:42.289" end="00:03:52.099">TOUCHED A NERVE, ASKED ABOUT GOVERNOR ROMNEY TRYING TO APPEAL TO LATINO VOTERS, SINCE HIS </p>
<p begin="00:03:52.099" end="00:03:54.268">FATHER WAS BORN IN MEXICOICO,</p>
<p begin="00:03:54.268" end="00:04:00.040">IT&apos;S IRONIC FROM A FAMILY COMING FROM A POLYGAMY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:00.040" end="00:04:04.411">&gt;&gt; Jon:  I&apos;M NOT SAYING ALL MORMONS ARE MEXICAN POLYGAMISTS,</p>
<p begin="00:04:04.411" end="00:04:07.047">I&apos;M JUST SAYING MITT ROMNEY&apos;S GRANDFATHER WAS ONE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:07.047" end="00:04:13.353">I&apos;M SAYING MITT ROMNEY IS ONE-QUARTER MEXICAN POLYGAMIST IS WHAT I&apos;M SAYING.</p>
<p begin="00:04:13.353" end="00:04:18.926">AFTER ALL PRESIDENT OBAMA WENT THROUGH WITH THE WHOLE MUSLIM KENYAN STUFF, IS THERE ANYTHING </p>
<p begin="00:04:18.926" end="00:04:20.060">YOU WANT TO WALK BACK?</p>
<p begin="00:04:20.060" end="00:04:21.228">&gt;&gt; IS THAT FAIR TO TALK ABOUT?</p>
<p begin="00:04:21.228" end="00:04:24.064">&gt;&gt; WELL, PEOPLE TOOK IT WAY OFF BASE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:24.064" end="00:04:27.968">I DIDN&apos;T SAY ANYTHING ABOUT ANY RELIGION, AND AS I&apos;VE SAID BEFORE, MITT ROMNEY OR HIS </p>
<p begin="00:04:27.968" end="00:04:31.071">FAMILY AS I KNOW OF, DOESN&apos;T ACCEPT POLYGAMY TODAY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:31.071" end="00:04:36.076">&gt;&gt; Jon:  WHY ARE POLITICIANS SO ADEPT AT THE DICKISH APOLOGY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:36.076" end="00:04:41.315">( LAUGHTER ) I MEAN, THAT I KNOW OF.</p>
<p begin="00:04:41.315" end="00:04:46.119">&quot;I DON&apos;T THINK ANYBODY IN HIS FAMILY IS IN POLYGAMY THAT I KNOW ABOUT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:46.119" end="00:04:47.554">WE CAN&apos;T BE SURE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:47.554" end="00:04:53.360">DOES ROMNEY HAVE ONE WIFE WHO DRIVES A COUPLE CADILLACS OR FOUR WIVES WHO DRIVE A HALF A </p>
<p begin="00:04:53.360" end="00:05:00.734">ADILLAC, EACH, I DON&apos;T KNOW?&quot;C A SOMEWHAT OBLIQUE ATTACK ON ROMNEY&apos;S RELIGION.</p>
<p begin="00:05:00.734" end="00:05:04.238">&gt;&gt; TODAY WE WANTED TO FOCUS ON WHAT MORMONNISM SAYS ABOUT LYING </p>
<p begin="00:05:04.238" end="00:05:09.810">AND THE REASON IS QUITE SIMPLE-- THERE ROMNEY SEEMS TO BE HAVING SOME TROUBLE TELLING THE TRUTH.</p>
<p begin="00:05:09.810" end="00:05:20.053">ALL LIARS AND WHO SO EVER LOVEST AND MAKEETH A LIE, AND THE WHORE MONGERRER AND SORCERER SHALL </p>
<p begin="00:05:20.053" end="00:05:27.761">HAVE THEIR PART IN THE LAKE WHICH BURNETH WITH FIRE AND BRIM STONE, WHICH IS THE SECOND DEATH.</p>
<p begin="00:05:27.761" end="00:05:30.931">&gt;&gt; Jon:  REALLY?</p>
<p begin="00:05:30.931" end="00:05:33.133">WHORE MONGERRER AND THE SORCER?</p>
<p begin="00:05:33.133" end="00:05:39.473">IS THAT FROM THE BOOK OF MORMON OR MSNBC&apos;S NEW DEBATE SHOW ( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ).</p>
<p begin="00:05:39.473" end="00:05:40.107">&gt;&gt; Jon:  OR-- </p>
<p begin="00:05:40.107" end="00:05:42.709">&gt;&gt; MR. ROMNEY HAS GOT TWO CHOICES.</p>
<p begin="00:05:42.709" end="00:05:49.783">HE CAN EITHER KEEP LYING AND POTENTIALLY WIN THE WHITE HOUSE BUT BRING ETERNAL DAMNINATION </p>
<p begin="00:05:49.783" end="00:05:52.085">UPON HIMSELF, OR HE CAN START TELLING THE TRUTH.</p>
<p begin="00:05:52.085" end="00:05:57.424">&gt;&gt; Jon:  YES, THOSE ARE HIS ONLY TWO CHOICES OR HE COULD TAKE THE THIRD CHOICE, THE ONE </p>
<p begin="00:05:57.424" end="00:06:04.498">EVERY PRESIDENT AND POLITICIAN HAS MADE FROM THE DAWN OF TIME-- CONTINUE TO PROFESS YOUR FAITH </p>
<p begin="00:06:04.498" end="00:06:05.399">WHILST ALSO LYING.</p>
<p begin="00:06:05.399" end="00:06:09.536">BEING A MORMON HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH ROMNEY&apos;S CONUNDRUM.</p>
<p begin="00:06:09.536" end="00:06:16.677">YOU DON&apos;T SPIT SCRIPTURE AT HIM ALTHOUGH IT TAKES A BOLD MAN TO CRITICIZE SOMEONE ABOUT A BOOK </p>
<p begin="00:06:16.677" end="00:06:19.947">THEY ARE SIMULTANEOUSLY ( BLEEP ).</p>
<p begin="00:06:19.947" end="00:06:24.218">HE IS NOT SAYING IT&apos;S A FALSE RELIGION.</p>
<p begin="00:06:24.218" end="00:06:29.656">&gt;&gt; A GUY IN UPSTATE NEW YORK, IN 1830, WHEN HE GOT CAUGHT HAVING </p>
<p begin="00:06:29.656" end="00:06:34.561">SEX WITH THE MAID AND EXPLAINED TO HIS WIFE THAT GOD TOLD HIM TO DO IT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:34.561" end="00:06:39.333">&gt;&gt; Jon:  MORMONS AREN&apos;T THE ONLY RELIGION WHO&apos;S ORIGIN STORY </p>
<p begin="00:06:39.333" end="00:06:41.768">CAN BE EXPLAINED AS A CONVENIENT ALIBI.</p>
<p begin="00:06:41.768" end="00:06:47.708">YOU CAN AS EASILY SAY THE CHRISTIANITY WAS CREATED BY A KNOCKED UP TEENAGED GIRL WHO </p>
<p begin="00:06:47.708" end="00:06:49.776">TOLD HER PARENTS AN ANGEL HAD COME DOWN.</p>
<p begin="00:06:49.776" end="00:06:55.883">OR MAYBE YOU COULD SAY BUSED BOOUDISM WAS CREATED BY A GUY WHO FELL ASLEEP UNDER A TREE AND </p>
<p begin="00:06:55.883" end="00:07:01.555">MISSED WORK AND EXPLAINED HE WAS LATE BECAUSE HE DISCOVERED ANOTHER STATE OF BEING.</p>
<p begin="00:07:01.555" end="00:07:03.290">YEAH, WHATEVER, FAT ASS.</p>
<p begin="00:07:03.290" end="00:07:05.125">GET BACK TO THE DEEP FRYER.</p>
<p begin="00:07:05.125" end="00:07:07.027">STOP EEGHT THE INVENTORY.</p>
<p begin="00:07:07.027" end="00:07:10.831">NOW, OF COURSE, IT IS FAIR TO QUESTION RELIGIOUS PRACTICES AT TIMES.</p>
<p begin="00:07:10.831" end="00:07:15.636">MORMONS HAD A STRICT NO BLACK CLERGY ALLOWED POLICY UP UNTIL 1978.</p>
<p begin="00:07:15.636" end="00:07:17.104">THAT COULD RAISE SOME CONCERNS.</p>
<p begin="00:07:17.104" end="00:07:18.605">NOT THIS ONE BUT-- </p>
<p begin="00:07:18.605" end="00:07:25.212">&gt;&gt; SO, DID MORMON MEN MITT ROMNEY&apos;S AGE ACTUALLY BELIEVE OR EVER BELIEVE WHAT THEIR HERO </p>
<p begin="00:07:25.212" end="00:07:31.285">BRIGHAM YOUNG TAUGHT THEM ABOUT THE AFRICAN RACE THAT THEY WOULD DIE ON THE SPOT IF THEY HAD SEX </p>
<p begin="00:07:31.285" end="00:07:33.320">WITH A BLACK WOMAN?</p>
<p begin="00:07:33.320" end="00:07:37.057">MITT ROMNEY KNOWS HE WILL NEVER HAVE TO ANSWER THAT QUESTION.</p>
<p begin="00:07:37.057" end="00:07:46.200">&gt;&gt; Jon:  FIRST OF ALL, THAT WOULD BE THE GREATEST PAM GREER REVENGE MOVIE EVER, EVER!</p>
<p begin="00:07:46.200" end="00:07:51.271">( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ) BUT AS A QUESTION, IT IS RIDICULOUS.</p>
<p begin="00:07:51.271" end="00:07:56.343">ALTHOUGH, IF YOU&apos;RE TRULY CONCERNED IF ALL MORMONS BELIEVE THAT, YOU HAD DEMOCRATIC SENATE </p>
<p begin="00:07:56.343" end="00:07:58.078">MAJORITY LEADER HARRY REID ON,</p>
<p begin="00:07:58.078" end="00:08:02.883">HE&apos;S A MORMON, WHICH WHO I CAN&apos;T WAIT TO HEAR HOW HE ANSWERS IT.</p>
<p begin="00:08:02.883" end="00:08:06.019">&gt;&gt; DO YOU FEAR THIS FAILURE OF THE PERFORMANCE OF THE REPUBLICAN PRESIDENTIAL </p>
<p begin="00:08:06.019" end="00:08:15.662">CANDIDATES WILL, IN FACT, FOCUS REAL REPUBLICAN ENERGY ON TRYING TO TAKE AWAY YOUR MAJORITY LEADERSHIP?</p>
<p begin="00:08:15.662" end="00:08:17.264">&gt;&gt; Jon:  AND AS A FOLLOW-UP,</p>
<p begin="00:08:17.264" end="00:08:19.933">IF YOU BANG A BLACK WOMAN, WILL YOU DIE ON THE SPOT?</p>
<p begin="00:08:19.933" end="00:08:28.375">( LAUGHTER ) YOU CAN&apos;T CHERRY PICK THE WORST ASPECTS OF THE A RELIGION AND </p>
<p begin="00:08:28.375" end="00:08:30.077">HOLD A PERSON RESPONSIBLE FOR IT.</p>
<p begin="00:08:30.077" end="00:08:30.844">IT&apos;S NOT RELEVANT.</p>
<p begin="00:08:30.844" end="00:08:34.047">IT&apos;S NOT LIKE MITT ROMNEY WILL PURSUE POLICIES THAT ARE UNFAIR </p>
<p begin="00:08:34.047" end="00:08:36.617">TO BLACK PEOPLE BECAUSE HE&apos;S A MORMON.</p>
<p begin="00:08:36.617" end="00:08:39.820">HE&apos;LL DO THAT BECAUSE HE&apos;S A REPUBLICAN.</p>
<p begin="00:08:39.820" end="00:08:40.420">( LAUGHTER ) </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
