<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:02.102" end="00:00:03.370">&gt;&gt; Jon:  WELCOME BACK!</p>
<p begin="00:00:03.370" end="00:00:06.773">WE TURN NOW TO PRESIDENT OBAMA,</p>
<p begin="00:00:06.773" end="00:00:18.085">PRESIDENT OBAMA WHO SPENT MONDAY ON A SOOOUL TRIP!</p>
<p begin="00:00:18.085" end="00:00:21.622">I&apos;M SORRY, I&apos;M BEING TOLD IT&apos;S A TRIP TO SEOUL, SOUTH KOREA.</p>
<p begin="00:00:21.622" end="00:00:22.356">MY BAD.</p>
<p begin="00:00:22.356" end="00:00:25.926">THERE, APPARENTLY, THE PRESIDENT MET WITH OTHER WORLD LEADERS TO TALK ABOUT ARMS CONTROL AND TO </p>
<p begin="00:00:25.926" end="00:00:30.197">PERFORM WITH THE WORLD LEADER TABERNACLE CHOIR.</p>
<p begin="00:00:30.197" end="00:00:35.102">BUT YOU KNOW THIS IS HOW TOUGH IT IS TO BE PRESIDENT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:35.102" end="00:00:41.508">EVEN SOMETHING AS SIMPLE AS A HIGH STEAKS NUCLEAR DISARMAMENT,</p>
<p begin="00:00:41.508" end="00:00:44.344">CAN BE FRAUGHT WITH DOMESTIC POLITICAL PERIL </p>
<p begin="00:00:55.556" end="00:00:57.224">&gt;&gt; Jon:  HOT MIC!</p>
<p begin="00:00:57.224" end="00:01:02.462">MR. PRESIDENT, WE CAN HEAR YOU CAPITULATING TO THE RUSSIANS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:02.462" end="00:01:05.199">ALTHOUGH, ON THE PLUS SIDE,</p>
<p begin="00:01:05.199" end="00:01:09.469">MEDVEDEV NO LONGER THAT&apos;S TRANSMIT THAT&apos;S INFORMATION TO VLADIMIR.</p>
<p begin="00:01:09.469" end="00:01:10.938">( LAUGHTER ) IT&apos;S ON THE TV.</p>
<p begin="00:01:10.938" end="00:01:13.674">CAN WE HEAR HIM SAY THAT AGAIN?</p>
<p begin="00:01:16.510" end="00:01:19.379">&gt;&gt; Jon:  I TRANSMIT THIS INFORMATION TO VLADIMIR.</p>
<p begin="00:01:19.379" end="00:01:22.583">THAT IS A SENTENCE THAT SHOULD ONLY BE SPOKEN INTO A SHOE PHONE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:22.583" end="00:01:24.751">( LAUGHTER ).</p>
<p begin="00:01:24.751" end="00:01:32.159">I MEAN, I KNOW IT&apos;S NOT NECESSARILY SINISTER, BUT IT REALLY DOES SOUND PRETTY </p>
<p begin="00:01:32.159" end="00:01:35.262">( BLEEP ) SINISTER, DOESN&apos;T IS IT?</p>
<p begin="00:01:35.262" end="00:01:40.868">&quot;I TRANSMIT THIS INFORMATION TO VLADIMIR.&quot; GIVE ME THAT AGAIN.</p>
<p begin="00:01:40.868" end="00:01:44.137">ALL HE&apos;S REALLY SAYING IS, ALL RIGHT, I&apos;LL TELL HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:01:44.137" end="00:01:50.110">BUT WHEN IT COMES OUT WITH A LITTLE RUSSIAN SAUCE ON IT &quot;I WILL TRANSMIT THIS INFORMATION </p>
<p begin="00:01:50.110" end="00:01:55.182">TO VLADIMIR.&quot; I WONDER IF RUSSIA HAS BEEN OUR ENEMY FOR SO MANY YEARS BECAUSE </p>
<p begin="00:01:55.182" end="00:01:57.317">EVERYTHING THEY SAY SOUNDS EVIL.</p>
<p begin="00:01:57.317" end="00:02:03.056">WE WOULD GO, &quot;HEY, MAN, IS DINNER READY?&quot; AND IN RUSSIAN IT WOULD BE, &quot;HAS </p>
<p begin="00:02:03.056" end="00:02:11.064">THE BORSCHHT BEEN PREPAREDDED FOR DINNER?</p>
<p begin="00:02:11.064" end="00:02:13.066">I CAN&apos;T BELIEVE IT&apos;S NOT BUTTER.</p>
<p begin="00:02:13.066" end="00:02:18.805">THE AUTHORITIES INSIST IT IS NOT BUTTER, BUT, MY LIFE EXPERIENCE TELLS ME OTHERWISE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:18.805" end="00:02:23.477">NOW, I&apos;M SURE REPUBLICANS ARE GOING TO SAY THAT THE PRESIDENT&apos;S GAFFE WAS SINISTER.</p>
<p begin="00:02:23.477" end="00:02:27.247">BUT I REALLY FEEL IT&apos;S MORE SAD AND VAGUELY PATHETIC.</p>
<p begin="00:02:27.247" end="00:02:32.085">HERE&apos;S THE PRESIDENT EXPLAINING WHAT HE MEANT IN THIS &quot;CAUGHT ON LIVE MIC&quot; MOMENT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:32.085" end="00:02:36.857">&gt;&gt; I WANT TO REDUCE OUR NUCLEAR STOCKPILES.</p>
<p begin="00:02:36.857" end="00:02:42.362">FRANKLY, THE CURRENT ENVIRONMENT IS NOT CONDUCIVE TO THOSE KINDS OF THOUGHTFUL CLTATIONS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:42.362" end="00:02:45.799">I THINK WE&apos;LL DO BETTER IN 2013.</p>
<p begin="00:02:45.799" end="00:02:49.236">&gt;&gt; Jon:  I&apos;D LIKE TO REDUCE THE NUCLEAR STOCKPILES BUT MY </p>
<p begin="00:02:49.236" end="00:02:59.580">HANDS ARE TIED UNTIL I&apos;M DONE WITH THE, YOU KNOW,... I GOT TO ACT LIKE AN IDIOT UNTIL I GET MY </p>
<p begin="00:02:59.580" end="00:03:01.815">SECOND TERM AND THEN I CAN DO THE GOOD THINGS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:01.815" end="00:03:06.053">BETWEEN THE LENGTH OF OUR NOMINATING PROCESS AND THE RUN-UP TO MIDTERM ELECTIONS AND </p>
<p begin="00:03:06.053" end="00:03:10.824">POSTELECTIONS AND LAME DUCK SESSIONS, WHICH PROBABLY ONLY A QUADRENNIAL THREE-WEEK WINDOW </p>
<p begin="00:03:10.824" end="00:03:13.727">WHERE THE CONDITIONS ARE PERFECT TO GET SOMETHING ( BLEEP ) DONE ANYWAY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:13.727" end="00:03:15.929">I HOPE IT DOESN&apos;T SNOW DURING THOSE WEEKS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:15.929" end="00:03:23.237">THE WHOLE TIPTOEING AROUND THE ELECTION SEASON MUST SOUND RIDICULOUS TO MEDVEDEV AND PUTIN.</p>
<p begin="00:03:23.237" end="00:03:27.674">I WONDER WHAT THAT WILL SOUND LIKE IN RUSSIAN </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
