<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:02.369" end="00:00:05.539">( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ) </p>
<p begin="00:00:05.539" end="00:00:08.208">&gt;&gt; Jon:  MY GUEST TONIGHT AN AUTHOR.</p>
<p begin="00:00:08.208" end="00:00:09.877">HIS NEW BOOK IS CALLED,</p>
<p begin="00:00:09.877" end="00:00:14.548">&quot;PUNCHING OUT:  ONE YEAR IN A CLOSING AUTO PLANT.&quot; PLEASE WELCOME TO THE PROGRAM,</p>
<p begin="00:00:14.548" end="00:00:26.026">PAUL CLEMENS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:26.026" end="00:00:29.630">&quot;PUNCHING OUT.&quot; I JUST WANT TO SAY, THANKS FOR WRITING THIS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:29.630" end="00:00:36.904">THIS IS ONE OF THOSE STORIES THAT I FEEL LIKE PEOPLE WOULD NEVER HEAR WERE NOT FOR THE </p>
<p begin="00:00:36.904" end="00:00:41.441">DILIGENCE AND PATIENCE AND OBSERVANCE OF A JOURNALIST SUCH AS YOURSELF WHO GOES IN THERE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:41.441" end="00:00:48.782">YOU SPENT A YEAR WATCHING SOME GENTLEMEN IN MICHIGAN PACK UP A STAMPING PLANT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:48.782" end="00:00:50.284">&gt;&gt; YES.</p>
<p begin="00:00:50.284" end="00:00:55.222">FOR ABOUT 11 MONTHS, I WENT AS OFTEN AS I COULD TO THE BUD PLANT, WHICH IS ON THE EAST SIDE </p>
<p begin="00:00:55.222" end="00:00:56.023">OF DETROIT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:56.023" end="00:00:57.324">IT WAS BUILT IN 1919.</p>
<p begin="00:00:57.324" end="00:00:58.559">A RICH HISTORY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:58.559" end="00:01:04.097">ITS CLAIM TO FAME WAS IN THE 19 FICHTs IT STAMPED AND ASSEMBLED THE BODY OF THE FORD </p>
<p begin="00:01:04.097" end="00:01:07.434">THUNDERBIRD, AS ICONIC A CAR AS DETROIT PRODUCED IN THE 20th CENTURY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:07.434" end="00:01:14.575">WHEN I SAW THAT THE PLANT WAS CLOSING IN 2006, I THOUGHT THAT MIGHT BE A NICE WAY TO GET INTO </p>
<p begin="00:01:14.575" end="00:01:18.812">THE TOPIC I WANTED TO WRITE ABOUT, BLUE COLLAR DECLINE AND UNEMPLOYMENT PROBLEMS AND SO ON.</p>
<p begin="00:01:18.812" end="00:01:20.047">&gt;&gt; Jon:  WHICH MAKES SENSE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:20.047" end="00:01:24.651">YOU HEARD ABOUT IT FROM A NEWS LETTER CALLED &quot;PLANT CLOSING NEWS.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:01:24.651" end="00:01:27.554">&gt;&gt; THAT&apos;S THE OPENING CHAPTER OF THE BOOK, THE PROLOGUE, AND </p>
<p begin="00:01:27.554" end="00:01:31.725">THAT&apos;S ONE OF THE THINGS THAT I KIND OF DISCOVERED AS I WAS WORKING ON THE BOOK THAT TAKING </p>
<p begin="00:01:31.725" end="00:01:35.495">APART INDUSTRY IS SORT OF ITS OWN INDUSTRY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:35.495" end="00:01:42.503">TRUCKING FIRMS, DEMOLITION COMPANIES, SCRAP COMPANIES, THEY ALL GET INVOLVED IN PLANT CLOSINGS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:42.503" end="00:01:46.139">AND, YEAH, THERE&apos;S AN INDUSTRY NOW THAT TAKES APART INDUSTRY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:46.139" end="00:01:47.241">THAT&apos;S SORT OF WHERE WE ARE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:47.241" end="00:01:53.046">&gt;&gt; Jon:  AND IN SOME RESPECTS, HAS SUPPLANTED ACTUAL INDUSTRY IN DETROIT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:53.046" end="00:01:55.782">IT IS A THRIVING-- THESE ARE GENTLEMEN THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN WORKING THE LINE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:55.782" end="00:01:58.519">&gt;&gt; YEAH, THAT&apos;S ONE OF THE SAD THINGS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:58.519" end="00:02:01.688">THE BOOK HAS ITS HUMOR, BUT IT&apos;S FUNDAMENTALLY A SAD STORY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:01.688" end="00:02:04.291">AND IT&apos;S THE SAME SKILL SET.</p>
<p begin="00:02:04.291" end="00:02:10.864">, YOU KNOW, IT&apos;S THE SAME SORT OF MUSCLE MEMORY THAT USED TO BE GOING TO MAKING THINGS CAN NOW </p>
<p begin="00:02:10.864" end="00:02:16.069">BE APPLIED-- DETROIT IS STILL PRODUCING CARS AND WILL CONTINUE, BUT IN PART, THAT&apos;S </p>
<p begin="00:02:16.069" end="00:02:19.973">THE SKILL SET USED TO TAKE APART THE EQUIPMENT THAT USED TO MAKE THE CARS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:19.973" end="00:02:25.078">&gt;&gt; Jon:  THE CRAZIEST THING TO ME IT&apos;S LOCATED BETWEEN TWO CHRYSLER PLANT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:25.078" end="00:02:25.979">&gt;&gt; THAT&apos;S CORRECT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:25.979" end="00:02:32.619">&gt;&gt; Jon:  AND THESE GUYS WHO ALL SEEM TO HAVE GREAT REVERENCE FOR THE COUPLE-- THE PLANT WAS </p>
<p begin="00:02:32.619" end="00:02:33.320">NOT FUNCTIONING.</p>
<p begin="00:02:33.320" end="00:02:36.323">THIS IS A YEAR YOU SPENT WITH THEM AS IT&apos;S DISASSEMBLING.</p>
<p begin="00:02:36.323" end="00:02:38.225">&gt;&gt; AFTER IT CLOSED, CORRECT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:38.225" end="00:02:42.496">&gt;&gt; Jon:  WHERE DID THEY SEND THE PLANT ONCE THEY DISASSEMBLED IT?</p>
<p begin="00:02:42.496" end="00:02:45.098">&gt;&gt; WELL, A LOT OF SCRAP STEEL WENT ABROAD.</p>
<p begin="00:02:45.098" end="00:02:48.402">ONE OF THE LINES, STAMPING LINE IN THE PLANT -- </p>
<p begin="00:02:48.402" end="00:02:49.937">&gt;&gt; LINE 16.</p>
<p begin="00:02:49.937" end="00:02:52.506">&gt;&gt; YEAH, THAT ONE WENT TO CENTRAL MEXICO.</p>
<p begin="00:02:52.506" end="00:02:54.508">AND ANOTHER LINE WENT TO BRAZIL.</p>
<p begin="00:02:54.508" end="00:02:59.279">IT WAS A REALLY DIVERSE CAST OF CHARACTERS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:59.279" end="00:03:03.217">PORTUGUESE, SPANISH, GERMAN ON ANY GIVEN DAY IN THE PLANT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:03.217" end="00:03:05.819">THAT&apos;S-- THOSE ARE THE COUNTRIES-- BRAZIL AND MEXICO -- </p>
<p begin="00:03:05.819" end="00:03:13.927">&gt;&gt; THE INTERESTING THING AND WHO-- WHAT COMPANY BOUGHT THE MATERIALS TO REASSEMBLE IT IN MEXICO?</p>
<p begin="00:03:13.927" end="00:03:22.002">&gt;&gt; A SPANISH COMPANY NAMED GURKS, STAMP BUT THEY ARE MAKING PARTS FOR THE DODGE JOURNEY, A </p>
<p begin="00:03:22.002" end="00:03:22.436">CHRYSLER CAR.</p>
<p begin="00:03:22.436" end="00:03:28.208">YOU MOVED A LINE THAT WAS IN A PLANT BETWEEN TWO CHRYSLER PLANT 1800 MILES SOUTHWEST TO PRODUCE </p>
<p begin="00:03:28.208" end="00:03:31.111">A CHRYSLER CAR.</p>
<p begin="00:03:31.111" end="00:03:33.914">&gt;&gt; Jon:  THIS IS THE POINT I WAS GETTING TO.</p>
<p begin="00:03:33.914" end="00:03:41.855">( LAUGHTER ) HOW ARE WE GOING TO COMPETE WHEN THE COMPANY THAT IS RIGHT THERE </p>
<p begin="00:03:41.855" end="00:03:48.462">BELIEVES IT IS IN THEIR BEST INTEREST TO LITERALLY PICK UP SOMETHING, AND IT TAKES THEM A </p>
<p begin="00:03:48.462" end="00:03:54.134">YEAR TO UNBOLT IT FROM WHERE IT WAS, AND MOVE IT TO ANOTHER COUNTRY?</p>
<p begin="00:03:54.134" end="00:03:57.371">HOW DO WE IN AND WAY BATTLE THAT KIND OF-- </p>
<p begin="00:03:57.371" end="00:04:01.842">&gt;&gt; THAT&apos;S WHY THE BOOK IS CALLED &quot;ONE YEAR IN A CLOSING AUTO PLANT.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:04:01.842" end="00:04:05.679">THE BOOK DOESN&apos;T REALLY HAVE A THESIS BECAUSE I DON&apos;T REALLY HAVE AN ANSWER.</p>
<p begin="00:04:05.679" end="00:04:07.014">IT&apos;S DESCRIPTIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:07.014" end="00:04:12.286">AND IT JUST STARTS TO LAY OUT THE PROCESS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:12.286" end="00:04:16.256">I HADN&apos;T SEEN ANYONE DESCRIBE IT AND I TRIED TO DESCRIBE IT AS BEST I COULD.</p>
<p begin="00:04:16.256" end="00:04:18.458">I WISH I HAD A THESIS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:18.458" end="00:04:22.329">WHEN I FINISHED IT MY EDITOR SAID,&quot;THIS IS KIND OF A WEIRD BOOK.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:04:22.329" end="00:04:24.231">&gt;&gt; Jon:  A GOOD THING TO HEAR FROM YOUR EDITOR.</p>
<p begin="00:04:24.231" end="00:04:25.866">&gt;&gt; IT&apos;S NOT WHAT YOU WANT TO HEAR.</p>
<p begin="00:04:25.866" end="00:04:31.371">AND I THINK WHAT HE MEANT AND HE WAS RIGHT, THERE WASN&apos;T SOMETHING I WAS TRYING TO PROVE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:31.371" end="00:04:38.612">IT WASN&apos;T HOW UNION GREED RUINED AMERICA OR HOW NASA RUINED EVERYTHING.</p>
<p begin="00:04:38.612" end="00:04:40.380">( LAUGHTER ) </p>
<p begin="00:04:40.380" end="00:04:45.819">&gt;&gt; Jon:  ARE YOU-- ARE YOU GOING TO BE USING ANY OF THOSE TITLE OR IS THAT NOW UP FOR GRABS?</p>
<p begin="00:04:45.819" end="00:04:47.254">&gt;&gt; YOU CAN HAVE THEM.</p>
<p begin="00:04:47.254" end="00:04:47.821">&gt;&gt; Jon:  ALL RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:47.821" end="00:04:50.224">&gt;&gt; BECAUSE PEOPLE HAVE THEIR OPINIONS, AND HONESTLY, I DON&apos;T </p>
<p begin="00:04:50.224" end="00:04:52.759">REALLY KNOW ENOUGH ABOUT IT TO ARTICULATE A GOOD ARGUMENT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:52.759" end="00:04:55.696">I JUST WANTED TO DESCRIBE WHAT HAPPENS-- WE SEE HEADLINES ALL </p>
<p begin="00:04:55.696" end="00:04:59.266">THE TIME-- &quot;PLANT TO CLOSE.&quot; AND IT&apos;S NOT JUST DETROIT OR </p>
<p begin="00:04:59.266" end="00:05:02.569">AUTO OR THE UPPER MIDWEST OR MICHIGAN.</p>
<p begin="00:05:02.569" end="00:05:05.205">IT&apos;S ALL OVER THE COUNTRY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:05.205" end="00:05:08.809">THE SITING IS DETROIT AND AUTO BUT IT&apos;S NOT THE SUBJECT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:08.809" end="00:05:12.646">THE SUBJECT OF THE BOOK IS BLUE COLLAR DECLINE AND HOW WE GOT WHERE WE ARE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:12.646" end="00:05:16.350">&gt;&gt; Jon:  THE HEART OF THE BOOK REALLY IS THESE CHARACTERS THAT YOU SPEND YOUR TIME WITH </p>
<p begin="00:05:16.350" end="00:05:21.288">AND THE ARKANSAS BOYS AND THIS GUY NEDRAS FROM BOSNIA.</p>
<p begin="00:05:21.288" end="00:05:26.460">THE INTERESTING THING I THOUGHT IN THE BOOK WAS THIS DELINEATION OF BLUE COLLAR WORKERS, PROUNION </p>
<p begin="00:05:26.460" end="00:05:31.131">AND ANTIUNION, WHO COME FROM THE SAME NEIGHBORHOODS, SAME WORK ETHIC, GO TO THE SAME CHURCH,</p>
<p begin="00:05:31.131" end="00:05:35.369">HAVE THE SAME SORT OF POLITICAL BELIEFS, JUST ON ALMOST OPPOSITE SIDE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:35.369" end="00:05:35.736">&gt;&gt; YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:05:35.736" end="00:05:44.611">BUT I THINK THE PRIDE, THE WORKING CLASS AND BLUE COLLAR PRIDE IN THE-- THAT JOINS PEOPLE  PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:44.611" end="00:05:45.846">AND THERE ARE A COUPLE OF GUYS FROM THE BOOK.</p>
<p begin="00:05:45.846" end="00:05:50.517">THERE&apos;S ONE MOVING PASSAGE WHERE A GUY TALKS ABOUT THE CARE HE WANTED TO TAKE IN TAKING APART </p>
<p begin="00:05:50.517" end="00:05:55.656">THE PRESS LINES THAT HAD SUPPORTED NILD-CLASS AMERICAN FAMILIES FOR YEARS, AND HE HOPED </p>
<p begin="00:05:55.656" end="00:05:59.960">IT WOULD DO THE SAME FOR MEXICAN FAMILIES AND I FOUND THAT A REALLY MOVING MONOLOGUE WHEN I </p>
<p begin="00:05:59.960" end="00:06:02.062">HEARD IT, AND THAT&apos;S WHY IT&apos;S IN THE BOOK.</p>
<p begin="00:06:02.062" end="00:06:06.867">&gt;&gt; Jon:  IT&apos;S A TERRIFIC BOOK AND FOR ANYBODY WHO WANTS TO UNDERSTAND THE HUMAN ASPECT </p>
<p begin="00:06:06.867" end="00:06:09.570">OF THIS PROSPECT, OUT OF SIGHT,</p>
<p begin="00:06:09.570" end="00:06:12.372">OUT OF MIND, YOU HAVE TO PICK IT UP.</p>
<p begin="00:06:12.372" end="00:06:14.374">&quot;PUNCHING OUT.&quot; IT&apos;S ON THE BOOKSHELVES  </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
