<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:06.607" end="00:00:07.207">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELCOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:07.207" end="00:00:12.112">MY GUEST TONIGHT, THE HOST OF MSNBC THE RACHEL MADDOW BOOK, HER NEW BOOK CALLED </p>
<p begin="00:00:12.112" end="00:00:14.448">DRIFT, THE UNMOORING OF AMERICAN MILITARY POWER.</p>
<p begin="00:00:14.448" end="00:00:15.449">WELCOME BACK TO THE PROGRAM,</p>
<p begin="00:00:15.449" end="00:00:16.483">RACHEL MADDOW.</p>
<p begin="00:00:16.483" end="00:00:25.559">(APPLAUSE) OH MY GOD.</p>
<p begin="00:00:25.559" end="00:00:28.362">YOU-- WAIT, YOU HAVE A COPY OF YOUR OWN BOOK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:28.362" end="00:00:29.763">YOU HAVE NOT READ IT?</p>
<p begin="00:00:29.763" end="00:00:34.835">&gt;&gt; I HAVE BEEN TRYING TO MEM ORIZE SIGNIFICANT PORTIONS SO I CAN JUST-- .</p>
<p begin="00:00:34.835" end="00:00:38.572">&gt;&gt; Jon: THE BOOK IS CALLED DRIFT, THE UNMOORING OF AMERICAN MILITARY POWER.</p>
<p begin="00:00:38.572" end="00:00:45.379">YOU KNOW, A LOT OF TELEVISION HOSTS, A LOT OF PEOPLE IN THIS INDUSTRY WRITE BOOKS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:45.379" end="00:00:49.883">WE TRY AND DO THEM AS CHEAPLY AND EASILY AND AS SUPERFICIALLY AS WE CAN.</p>
<p begin="00:00:49.883" end="00:00:52.653">YOU APPEAR TO HAVE INVESTED A GREAT DEAL OF RESEARCH IN THIS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:52.653" end="00:00:56.356">&gt;&gt; YEAH, I JUST TREATED IT LIKE A SECOND JOB.</p>
<p begin="00:00:56.356" end="00:00:58.792">&gt;&gt; Jon: IT&apos;S MAKING EVERYBODY LOOK BAD IS WHAT I AM SAYING.</p>
<p begin="00:00:58.792" end="00:01:01.461">I DON&apos;T THINK ANY OF US PRAERBT THAT, IN ANY WAY,</p>
<p begin="00:01:01.461" end="00:01:02.496">SHAPE OR FORM.</p>
<p begin="00:01:02.496" end="00:01:03.163">&gt;&gt; I&apos;M SORRY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:03.163" end="00:01:09.069">&gt;&gt; Jon: WHAT MAKES YOU DECIDE I WANT TO DIVE INTO THIS MILITARY INDUSTRIAL </p>
<p begin="00:01:09.069" end="00:01:11.371">COMPLEX WHICH NO ONE HAS BEEN ABLE TO STOP.</p>
<p begin="00:01:11.371" end="00:01:15.475">AND YOU DO IT AT THE END SU HAVE PRESCRIPTION, ACTUAL PRESCRIPTION OF WHAT PEOPLE MAY DO.</p>
<p begin="00:01:15.475" end="00:01:18.645">&gt;&gt; I FELT LIKE, WHEN I GOT THE BOOK CONTRACT I HAD A RADIO SHOW.</p>
<p begin="00:01:18.645" end="00:01:20.747">I WAS JUST ABOUT TO GET A TV SHOW.</p>
<p begin="00:01:20.747" end="00:01:23.317">AND THIS WAS, I WAS REPORTING A LOT ON THE WARS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:23.317" end="00:01:24.718">AND WHAT WAS GOING ON.</p>
<p begin="00:01:24.718" end="00:01:28.121">BUT I FELT LIKE HI THIS THING I WANTED TO GET OFF MY CHEST, THIS THING WANTED TO </p>
<p begin="00:01:28.121" end="00:01:31.625">SAY, AN ARGUMENT I WANTED TO MAKE THAT I DIDN&apos;T KNOW HOW TO MAKE IN A SHORT FORM WAY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:31.625" end="00:01:34.962">THAT I NEEDED TO LAY OUT A BUNCH OF EVIDENCE AND SAY WHAT I THOUGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:34.962" end="00:01:38.432">AND I DON&apos;T THINK THERE IS A WAY TO HAVE DONE IT EXCEPT IN A BOOK.</p>
<p begin="00:01:38.432" end="00:01:39.466">AND SO I HATE WRITING.</p>
<p begin="00:01:39.466" end="00:01:40.501">IT MAKES ME CRAZY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:40.501" end="00:01:43.270">I&apos;M REALLY SLOW AT IT I DON&apos;T THINK I&apos;M VERY GOOD IT </p>
<p begin="00:01:43.270" end="00:01:46.507">ALTHOUGH I&apos;M HAPPY WITH THE WAY THE BOOK TURNED OUT,</p>
<p begin="00:01:46.507" end="00:01:47.374">PLEASE READ IT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:47.374" end="00:01:50.110">&gt;&gt; Jon: I WAS GOING TO JUMP IN, THAT IS NOT THE HARD SELL.</p>
<p begin="00:01:50.110" end="00:01:52.813">&gt;&gt; I DIDN&apos;T WANT TO WRITE A BACK AND THEN LOOK FOR A TOPIC.</p>
<p begin="00:01:52.813" end="00:01:55.949">HAD THIS TOPIC I COULDN&apos;T DO ANY OTHER WAY INSTEAD OF A BOOK.</p>
<p begin="00:01:55.949" end="00:01:56.950">AND SO IT&apos;S ABOUT-- .</p>
<p begin="00:01:56.950" end="00:02:00.687">&gt;&gt; Jon: SO ARE YOU DOING THIS OR ARE YOU TALKING AND THEN SENDING IT, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?</p>
<p begin="00:02:00.687" end="00:02:04.157">&gt;&gt; I&apos;M A NOTE SCRIBBLERS,</p>
<p begin="00:02:04.157" end="00:02:07.895">LIKE I&apos;M WRITING-- I HAND WRITE IT AND REWRITE IT TYPING.</p>
<p begin="00:02:07.895" end="00:02:12.633">YOU KNOW, I JUST, WE FEEL LIKE WE&apos;RE A COUNTRY THAT,</p>
<p begin="00:02:12.633" end="00:02:15.402">WE DIDN&apos;T FEEL LIKE WE WENT TO WAR AS A COUNTRY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:15.402" end="00:02:18.172">WE FEEL LAKE A COUNTRY THAT SENT THE MILITARY TO THE WAR,</p>
<p begin="00:02:18.172" end="00:02:22.309">AND THE MILITARY FOUGHT THE WARS AND WE WEREN&apos;T INVESTED AND DIDN&apos;T SACRIFICE AND </p>
<p begin="00:02:22.309" end="00:02:24.077">DIDN&apos;T FEEL IT WE STILL FEEL THAT WAY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:24.077" end="00:02:27.881">AND I THINK WE OUGHT TO FEEL THAT WAY IT OUGHT TO MAKE US WANT TO CHANGE THE WAY WE </p>
<p begin="00:02:27.881" end="00:02:30.884">ARE AS A COUNTRY AND I DON&apos;T THINK IT WOULD BE IMPOSSIBLE TO DO.</p>
<p begin="00:02:30.884" end="00:02:35.822">&gt;&gt; Jon: DON&apos;T YOU THINK THAT THAT IS A PURPOSEFUL CREATION BY THE GOVERNMENT,</p>
<p begin="00:02:35.822" end="00:02:40.127">TO ISOLATE THE MILITARY FROM THE GENERAL POP LAS BECAUSE THEN ARE YOU ABLE TO DO </p>
<p begin="00:02:40.127" end="00:02:45.566">THINGS WITH THE MILITARY YOU CAN&apos;T-- IF THE SACRIFICE IS SPREAD OUT TO EVERYBODY BY A </p>
<p begin="00:02:45.566" end="00:02:47.267">DRAFT OR THAT TYPE OF THING,</p>
<p begin="00:02:47.267" end="00:02:53.373">THE PUSHBACK IS MUCH MORE ENORMOUS FROM THE POPULATION FOR HOW YOU USE THE WARS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:53.373" end="00:02:55.609">YOU THINK THAT&apos;S SOMETHING THEY DESIGNED PURPOSEFULLY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:55.609" end="00:02:59.713">&gt;&gt; I THINK INCREMENTALLY THAT IS WHAT WE ACHIEVED IT IS CALLED DRIFT IF PART </p>
<p begin="00:02:59.713" end="00:03:02.316">BECAUSE I DIDN&apos;T WANT PEOPLE TO THINK IT WAS A CONSPIRACY,</p>
<p begin="00:03:02.316" end="00:03:05.385">THAT SOMEBODY SET OUT TO CHANGE THE COUNTRY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:05.385" end="00:03:07.487">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU REALLY DON&apos;T KNOW HOW TO SELL BOOKS, DO YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:03:07.487" end="00:03:12.960">ARE YOU SUPPOSED TO HAVE THE WHOLE CONSPIRACY THING HERE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:12.960" end="00:03:13.894">&gt;&gt; I KNOW.</p>
<p begin="00:03:13.894" end="00:03:16.363">&gt;&gt; CONSPIRACY IS EASIER TO UNDERSTAND THAN COMPLEXITY,</p>
<p begin="00:03:16.363" end="00:03:16.697">RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:16.697" end="00:03:21.435">BUT IT IS ALL OF THESE REALLY REASONABLE DECISIONS MADE BY POLITICIANS WHO HAD </p>
<p begin="00:03:21.435" end="00:03:22.469">UNDERSTANDABLE FRUSTRATIONS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:22.469" end="00:03:26.273">THEY SEE US, NATIONAL SECURITY NEEDS, THEY FEEL LIKE NEEDS TO BE ADDRESSED </p>
<p begin="00:03:26.273" end="00:03:27.741">BUT THE CONGRESS DOESN&apos;T WANT THEM TO.</p>
<p begin="00:03:27.741" end="00:03:30.077">THEY FIGURE OUT HOW TO DO IT AROUND THE CONGRESS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:30.077" end="00:03:33.080">THEY SEE A NATIONAL SECURITY NEED THEY WANT TO ADDRESS BUT THEY DON&apos;T WANT TO </p>
<p begin="00:03:33.080" end="00:03:35.482">EXPLAIN IT TO THE PUBLIC SO THEY DO IT IN SECRET.</p>
<p begin="00:03:35.482" end="00:03:39.286">THEY FIGURE OUT A WAY TO DO IT BUT IT LOOKS TOO EXPENSIVE, TELL PEOPLE IT&apos;S FREE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:39.286" end="00:03:42.356">WE MAKE ALL OF THESE INCREMENTAL CHANGES TO MAKE IT LESS HASSLE TO GET AROUND </p>
<p begin="00:03:42.356" end="00:03:45.425">THE THINGS THAT WE NEED TO GET AROUND TO DO WHAT WE KNOW IS RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:45.425" end="00:03:51.565">&gt;&gt; Jon: I LOVE HOW YOU CALL THESE INCREMENTAL CHANGES RATHER THAN LIKE LIES.</p>
<p begin="00:03:51.565" end="00:03:54.968">THEY HAVE THESE LITTLE LIES THAT THEY TELL AS WE GO ALONG.</p>
<p begin="00:03:54.968" end="00:03:59.773">IS IT THE KIND OF THING, YOU KNOW, THERE WAS SUCH A DRASTIC CHANGE AFTER THE </p>
<p begin="00:03:59.773" end="00:04:03.877">VIETNAM AND WATERGATE ERAS IN TERMS OF CURTAILING EXECUTIVE POWER.</p>
<p begin="00:04:03.877" end="00:04:04.244">&gt;&gt; YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:04:04.244" end="00:04:08.048">&gt;&gt; Jon: THAT SEAMED TO HAVE LASTED UP UNTIL 189-- THERE IS ABOUT A TENNIER PERIOD </p>
<p begin="00:04:08.048" end="00:04:09.716">WHERE THEY WERE ABLE TO ACCOMPLISH THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:09.716" end="00:04:13.287">IS IT JUST IMPOSSIBLE, THEN TO, BECAUSE A LOT OF THIS,</p>
<p begin="00:04:13.287" end="00:04:17.324">YOU POST LATE IS THE EXECUTIVE BRANCH, REALLY OVERSTEPPING.</p>
<p begin="00:04:17.324" end="00:04:21.361">IS IT IMPOSSIBLE TO REIGN THAT IN AT SOME LEVEL WHEN YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT WAGING A WAR?</p>
<p begin="00:04:21.361" end="00:04:26.466">&gt;&gt; I THINK THAT WE CAN&apos;T EVER EXPECT PRESIDENTS TO GIVE BACK POWER THAT THEY HAVE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:26.466" end="00:04:28.235">I JUST DON&apos;T THINK HUMAN DOES THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:28.235" end="00:04:31.905">AND I THINK ANYBODY WHO HAS THE PERSONALITY TO BE PRESIDENT ISN&apos;T GOING TO SAY </p>
<p begin="00:04:31.905" end="00:04:34.274">YOU KNOW WHAT, I HAVE APPROVED TOO MUCH POWER.</p>
<p begin="00:04:34.274" end="00:04:35.309">WHY DON&apos;T YOU TAKE SOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:04:35.309" end="00:04:40.080">CONGRESS ACTUALLY HAS TO TAKE IT AND AFTER VIETNAM CONGRESS GOT UP ON A ITS </p>
<p begin="00:04:40.080" end="00:04:44.918">BEHIND LEGS AND ASSERTED ITS CONSTITUTIONAL PREROGATIVE TO DO IT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:44.918" end="00:04:45.953">&gt;&gt; Jon: CONGRESS IS A CENTER?</p>
<p begin="00:04:45.953" end="00:04:47.654">CONGRESS IS SOME TYPE OF LABRADOR.</p>
<p begin="00:04:47.654" end="00:04:48.655">ALL RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:48.655" end="00:04:52.092">&gt;&gt; IT&apos;S VERY UNBALANCED, BUT IMPRESSIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:52.092" end="00:04:55.529">&gt;&gt; Jon: HOW ABOUT A SCABBY SCENTS, THERE YOU GO.</p>
<p begin="00:04:55.529" end="00:05:00.234">BUT THEY HAVE FALLEN BACK DOWN ON TO ALL FOUR AND THEY OUGHT TO BE MORE ASSERTIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:00.234" end="00:05:04.371">&gt;&gt; Jon: DO YOU THINK-- IS IT THE ONLY REASON WE HAVE THE POLITICAL WILL TO DO THAT </p>
<p begin="00:05:04.371" end="00:05:06.707">AFTER WATERGATE AND VIETNAM,</p>
<p begin="00:05:06.707" end="00:05:12.880">WAS THE EXTENSIVE AND OBVIOUS DAMAGE THAT THOSE TWO EVENTS CAUSED IF AMERICA,</p>
<p begin="00:05:12.880" end="00:05:19.052">DO WE NEED SOMETHING THAT EXTREME TO OCCUR BEFORE WE CAN RECENT THAT IN AGAIN,</p>
<p begin="00:05:19.052" end="00:05:20.387">THAT YOU KNOW, AS YOU SAID,</p>
<p begin="00:05:20.387" end="00:05:25.158">IT&apos;S SO DIFFICULT AND CONGRESS IS IN MANY WAYS COMPLICITY WITH THIS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:25.158" end="00:05:25.826">&gt;&gt; YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:05:25.826" end="00:05:28.061">&gt;&gt; Jon: ISN&apos;T IT SO DIFFICULT FOR THEM TO GIVE THAT POWER BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:05:28.061" end="00:05:32.699">&gt;&gt; I THINK WE HAVE HAD SOMETHING THAT BIG IN THE LONGEST WAR IN AMERICAN HISTORY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:32.699" end="00:05:33.400">&gt;&gt; Jon: RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:33.400" end="00:05:37.771">&gt;&gt; FOUGHT SIMULTANEOUSLY WITH AN 8.5 YEAR LONG WAR IN IRAQ AND ONLY 1% OF THE </p>
<p begin="00:05:37.771" end="00:05:41.942">POPULATION FATING IT, DOING 3, 4, 5, 6, 7 TOURS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:41.942" end="00:05:44.344">WHILE WE GAVE OURSELVES MULTIPLE TAX CUTS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:44.344" end="00:05:46.713">WE GAVE OURSELVES A TAX CUT RIGHT BEFORE 9/11.</p>
<p begin="00:05:46.713" end="00:05:49.850">THEN 9/11 HAPPENED, WE INVADED AFGHANISTAN.</p>
<p begin="00:05:49.850" end="00:05:53.987">WE DIDN&apos;T GIVE THE TAX CUT BACK AND GAVE ANOTHER TAX CUT RIGHT BEFORE INVADING IRAQ.</p>
<p begin="00:05:53.987" end="00:05:54.621">WITHOUT DOES THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:54.621" end="00:05:56.156">WHAT KIND OF COUNTRY DOES THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:56.156" end="00:05:59.393">THAT IS NOT A COUNTRY THINKING OF ITSELF AS GOING TO WAR.</p>
<p begin="00:05:59.393" end="00:06:02.129">(APPLAUSE) </p>
<p begin="00:06:02.129" end="00:06:05.465">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU HAVE TO LOOK AT TAX CUTS LIKE EXECUTIVE POWER.</p>
<p begin="00:06:05.465" end="00:06:07.034">IT IS HARD TO GIVE THEM BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:06:07.034" end="00:06:11.038">&gt;&gt; BUT I THINK THAT THE FACT THAT REPUBLICANS ARE UP SET ABOUT THIS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:11.038" end="00:06:13.740">CONSERVATIVES, LIBERALS ARE UP SET ABOUT THIS DEMOCRATS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:13.740" end="00:06:16.043">IT&apos;S VERY, THIS IS A NONPARTISAN THING.</p>
<p begin="00:06:16.043" end="00:06:21.582">&gt;&gt; Jon: THE BOOK SHOWED ME T WAS NICE TO SEE, NON-- IT DOESN&apos;T PHRASE THINGS IN </p>
<p begin="00:06:21.582" end="00:06:23.317">THAT SORT OF STRANGE RIGHT,</p>
<p begin="00:06:23.317" end="00:06:25.652">LEFT PARADIGM THAT ALWAYS EVERYTHING HAS TO FALL UNDER.</p>
<p begin="00:06:25.652" end="00:06:27.421">THAT IS A NICE PIECE OF WORK.</p>
<p begin="00:06:27.421" end="00:06:29.122">&gt;&gt; IT&apos;S NOT A RIGHT LEFT FIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:29.122" end="00:06:36.530">THERE IS A LOT OF BAD DECISIONS MADE BY PEOPLE OF BOTH PARTIES.</p>
<p begin="00:06:36.530" end="00:06:38.932">&gt;&gt; Jon: WE&apos;RE REALLY IN VERY POOR HANDS, AREN&apos;T WE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:38.932" end="00:06:42.769">EVERYBODY SUCKS VERY NICE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:42.769" end="00:06:45.138">BUT THE THING THAT I REALLY ENJOYED ABOUT IT WAS AT THE END THERE IS A SORT OF, I </p>
<p begin="00:06:45.138" end="00:06:49.877">WOULD SAY FOUR PAGE KIND OF BULLET POINTED, LIKE 12 PRESCRIPTIONS OF THINGS IT </p>
<p begin="00:06:49.877" end="00:06:56.350">THAT I THOUGHT REALLY WERE VERY INTERESTING, SEEMED SOMEWHAT ATTAINABLE AND WOULD HAVE SOME EFFECT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:56.350" end="00:06:56.683">&gt;&gt; YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:06:56.683" end="00:07:00.754">&gt;&gt; Jon: ON THE WAY THAT WE DO, WAGE THESE THINGS IN TERMS OF REIGNING IN THE POWER.</p>
<p begin="00:07:00.754" end="00:07:01.788">&gt;&gt; AND WHEN THE U.S.</p>
<p begin="00:07:01.788" end="00:07:03.891">MILITARY IS THE LARGEST ORGANIZATION IN THE WORLD.</p>
<p begin="00:07:03.891" end="00:07:08.161">SO YOU MAKE EVEN A SMALL DECISION ABOUT THAT ORGANIZATION, IT HAS A REALLY BIG IMPACT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:08.161" end="00:07:10.430">SO I THINK WE OCCASIONALLY NEED TO GO TO WARP.</p>
<p begin="00:07:10.430" end="00:07:14.134">I THINK WE NEED A GREAT MILITARY BUT I DON&apos;T THINK WE NEED PRIVATE CONTRACTORS </p>
<p begin="00:07:14.134" end="00:07:14.902">PEELING POTATOES.</p>
<p begin="00:07:14.902" end="00:07:16.637">I THINK THE MILITARY CAN DO THAT ITSELF.</p>
<p begin="00:07:16.637" end="00:07:20.741">I DON&apos;T THINK WE NEED 1800 NUCLEAR WEAPONS, OR A SECRET MILITARY OR CIA.</p>
<p begin="00:07:20.741" end="00:07:24.478">THERE ARE CHANGES THAT WE&apos;VE MADE RELATIVELY RECENTLY THAT WE COULD DIAL BACK THAT </p>
<p begin="00:07:24.478" end="00:07:28.048">WOULDN&apos;T BE A HUGE PARTISAN DEAL AND THAT WOULD MAKE ALL THE DIFFERENCE TO MAKING US </p>
<p begin="00:07:28.048" end="00:07:32.386">FEEL CONNECTED ONCE AGAIN TO THE PEOPLE WHO FIGHT IN OUR NAMES.</p>
<p begin="00:07:32.386" end="00:07:35.122">&gt;&gt; Jon: I KNOW-- GOOD, GREAT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:35.122" end="00:07:38.225">THE BOOK IS CALLED DRIFT, BY THE WAY, I LOVE THESE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:38.225" end="00:07:40.227">THE LITTLE ARMY MEN?</p>
<p begin="00:07:40.227" end="00:07:42.462">I PRETEND THAT MY SON LOVES THEM.</p>
<p begin="00:07:42.462" end="00:07:44.064">BUT IT&apos;S ME.</p>
<p begin="00:07:44.064" end="00:07:47.067">&gt;&gt; FINDING THE GUY WITH THE RADIO, THAT WAS ALWAYS FUN TO ME.</p>
<p begin="00:07:47.067" end="00:07:48.502">&gt;&gt; Jon: THAT IS THE ONE THAT MELTS FIRST.</p>
<p begin="00:07:48.502" end="00:07:50.504">THE RADIO ALWAYS MELTS FIRST.</p>
<p begin="00:07:50.504" end="00:07:52.673">DRIFT ON THE BOOK SHELVES NOW, RACHEL MADDOW.</p>
<p begin="00:07:52.673" end="00:07:53.407">&gt;&gt; THANK YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:07:53.407" end="00:07:54.074">(APPLAUSE) </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
