<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:06.607" end="00:00:13.780">&gt;&gt; SEPTEMBER 29, 2011, FROM COMEDY CENTRAL WORLD NEWS HEADQUARTERS IN NEW YORK, THIS </p>
<p begin="00:00:13.780" end="00:00:17.451">IS THE &quot;DAILY SHOW&quot; WITH JON STEWART.</p>
<p begin="00:00:17.985" end="00:00:18.652"> <span tts:color="#ffff00">Captioning sponsored by</span> </p>
<p begin="00:00:18.652" end="00:00:27.261"> <span tts:color="#ffff00">COMEDY CENTRAL</span> ( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ) </p>
<p begin="00:00:27.261" end="00:00:29.129">&gt;&gt; Barry:  WELCOME TO THE DAILY SHOW.</p>
<p begin="00:00:29.129" end="00:00:30.597">MY NAME IS JON STEWART.</p>
<p begin="00:00:30.597" end="00:00:33.133">OUR GUEST TONIGHT WILL BE CAROLINE KENNEDY, NO RELATION.</p>
<p begin="00:00:33.133" end="00:00:40.874">AND BUT LET&apos;S BEGIN TONIGHT WITH BARACK OBAMA.</p>
<p begin="00:00:40.874" end="00:00:45.979">( LAUGHTER ) YOU KNOW HOW YOU HATE BARACK OBAMA?</p>
<p begin="00:00:45.979" end="00:00:46.780">NOT DISAPPOINTED.</p>
<p begin="00:00:46.780" end="00:00:51.752">NOT WISH HE HANDLED CERTAIN ISSUES IN ONE WAY OR ANOTHER,</p>
<p begin="00:00:51.752" end="00:00:54.421">BUT HATE HIM, JUST REALLY WANT TO NAIL HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:00:54.421" end="00:01:00.060">HE HAD A GOOD RUN ON THE BIRTH CERTIFICATE THING, BUT TURNS OUT HE HAD ONE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:00.060" end="00:01:05.732">WORKED REAL HARD AT THE SECRET MUSLIM, AND THEN HE WENT OUT AND KILLED OSAMA BIN LADEN.</p>
<p begin="00:01:05.732" end="00:01:12.673">AKONG REVEREND WRIGHT, BILL AYERS, TONIES AREICO, HIGH NEW JERSEY TWO OR THREE WARS AND GUY </p>
<p begin="00:01:12.673" end="00:01:15.909">IS STILL HANGING AROUND 40% APPROVAL.</p>
<p begin="00:01:15.909" end="00:01:20.480">FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO HAVE LOST HOPE, I SAY MERRY CHRISTMAS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:20.480" end="00:01:31.425">AND WELCOME TO OUR NEW SEGMENT-- THE CUSTOM-TAILORED OBAMA SCANDAL YOU ORDERED IS FINALLY HERE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:31.425" end="00:01:33.527">I&apos;LL LET THE NEWS MEDIA FILL YOU IN.</p>
<p begin="00:01:33.527" end="00:01:37.497">&gt;&gt; THE WIDENING SCANDAL INVOLVING A COMPANY HIGHLY TOUTED BY THE WHITE HOUSE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:37.497" end="00:01:39.600">&gt;&gt; THE CENTERPIECE OF THE PRESIDENT OBAMA&apos;S PITCH TO THE </p>
<p begin="00:01:39.600" end="00:01:41.435">AMERICAN PEOPLE, THE CREATION OF MORE GREEN JOBS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:41.435" end="00:01:46.907">&gt;&gt; THE COMPANY THAT HAS NOW DECLARED BANKRUPTCY, LAID OFF ALL 1100 OF ITS WORKERS AND WAS </p>
<p begin="00:01:46.907" end="00:01:53.680">RAIDED BY THE F.B.I. LAST WEEK.</p>
<p begin="00:01:53.680" end="00:01:56.183">&gt;&gt; Jon:  COMPANIES COME AND GO ALL THE TIME.</p>
<p begin="00:01:56.183" end="00:02:02.256">IT&apos;S NOT LIKE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE LONED THIS COMPANY HALF A BILLION DOLLARS AND THE COMPANY </p>
<p begin="00:02:02.256" end="00:02:06.226">NAME SOUNDS LIKE ONE OF THOSE WEIRD PLANETS CAPTAIN KIRK FOUND HIMSELF ON, YOU KNOW THE ONES </p>
<p begin="00:02:06.226" end="00:02:10.130">THAT WERE JUST LIKE EARTH ONLY ALL THE WOMEN WEAR ORANGE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:10.130" end="00:02:14.768">&gt;&gt; THE CALIFORNIA SOLAR PANEL COMPANY SOLYNDRA, WHICH RECEIVED A MAJOR LONE FROM THE FEDERAL </p>
<p begin="00:02:14.768" end="00:02:17.171">GOVERNMENT ONLY TO COLLAPSE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:17.171" end="00:02:24.678">&gt;&gt; SOLYNDRA RECEIVED $535 BILLION IN HELENE GUARANTEES TO EXPAND PRODUCTION OF CUTTING </p>
<p begin="00:02:24.678" end="00:02:29.082">EDGE SOLAR PANELS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:29.082" end="00:02:32.853">&gt;&gt; EARTH TO ENTERPRIZE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:32.853" end="00:02:35.222">HOW MANY MONEY DID WE GIVE THOSE...</p>
<p begin="00:02:35.222" end="00:02:38.825">IDIOTS?</p>
<p begin="00:02:38.825" end="00:02:42.162">SPOCK, WHY DIDN&apos;T YOU WARN ME?</p>
<p begin="00:02:42.162" end="00:02:43.797">TERRIBLE, CAPTAIN KIRK.</p>
<p begin="00:02:43.797" end="00:02:44.131">SORRY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:44.131" end="00:02:49.770">ALL RIGHT, FINE, SO A SOLAR PANEL COMPANY THAT WE GAVE $500 MILLION TO COLLAPSED.</p>
<p begin="00:02:49.770" end="00:02:55.943">$500 MILLION IS ONLY 1.3% OF THE MONEY GIVEN OUT BY THE GOVERNMENT&apos;S GREEN ENERGY PROGRAM.</p>
<p begin="00:02:55.943" end="00:03:00.714">MOST OF THE OTHER COMPANIES THAT BENEFITED FROM THAT MONEY, SOLE AWIND, NUCLEAR, THEY&apos;RE DOING FINE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:00.714" end="00:03:05.385">IN TRUTH THANK YOU SCANDAL WOULD ONLY BE EXPLOITABLE IF THE PRESIDENT HAD MADE THIS ONE </p>
<p begin="00:03:05.385" end="00:03:10.057">PARTICULAR COMPANY THE POSTAR CHILD FOR THE PROGRAM IF HE HAD TOURED THE SOLYNDRA FACILITIES </p>
<p begin="00:03:10.057" end="00:03:18.198">OR MET WITH THE C.E.O. OR PRAISED ITS CUTTING EDGE INGENUITY IN A SPEECH THAT IN </p>
<p begin="00:03:18.198" end="00:03:20.067">RETROSPECT WILL SEEM ILL-ADVISED.</p>
<p begin="00:03:20.067" end="00:03:24.771">&gt;&gt; THE TRUE ENGINE OF ECONOMIC GROWTH WILL ALWAYS BE COMPANIES LIKE SOLYNDRA.</p>
<p begin="00:03:24.771" end="00:03:31.378">IT&apos;S HERE THAT COMPANIES LIKE SOLYNDRA ARE A LEADING THE WAY TOWARD A BRIGHTER AND MORE </p>
<p begin="00:03:31.378" end="00:03:33.380">PROSPEROUS FUTURE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:33.380" end="00:03:41.221">&gt;&gt; Jon:  GENERATIONS FROM NOW, WHEN INTELLIGENT APES RULE OVER THIS LAND, ONLY TWO </p>
<p begin="00:03:41.221" end="00:03:44.625">ARTIFACTS OF OUR CIVILIZATION WILL WEMAIN.</p>
<p begin="00:03:44.625" end="00:03:50.297">HALF THE STATUE OF LIBERTY AND THIS BEAUTIFUL FACTORY, WHICH WILL STILL BE HIM ALONG AND PIG </p>
<p begin="00:03:50.297" end="00:03:53.100">AS MEMBERSHIP AS 1100 APES.</p>
<p begin="00:03:53.100" end="00:04:01.675">( LAUGHTER ) SO DOES FAILURE OF ONE COMPANY DISCREDIT THE ENTIRE IDEA OF A GREEN ENERGY ECONOMY?</p>
<p begin="00:04:01.675" end="00:04:04.745">OF COURSE NOT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:04.745" end="00:04:08.815">BUT IF IN, LET&apos;S SAY, 1936, YOU SPOKE ABOUT THE GROWING IMPORTANCE OF AIR TRAVEL IN </p>
<p begin="00:04:08.815" end="00:04:16.590">FRONT OF, I DON&apos;T KNOW, THE HIND&apos;D HINDENBURG, YOU&apos;D BE </p>
<p begin="00:04:16.590" end="00:04:19.159">RIGHT ABOUT THE FUTURE OF AIR TRAVEL.</p>
<p begin="00:04:19.159" end="00:04:23.297">BUT YOU&apos;D STILL BE ON ( BLEEP ) FIRE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:23.297" end="00:04:26.767">( LAUGHTER ) OH, THE STUPIDITY!</p>
<p begin="00:04:26.767" end="00:04:33.674">( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ) SO THE ADMINISTRATION, MAYBE THEIR HEARTS ARE IN THE RIGHT </p>
<p begin="00:04:33.674" end="00:04:36.176">PLACE AND THEY JUST BET ON THE WRONG HORSE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:36.176" end="00:04:41.481">IT&apos;S NOT LIKE THERE&apos;S ANY DAMNING EVIDENCE THEY KNEW IN ADVANCE THAT THE HORSE WAS A DONKEY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:41.481" end="00:04:46.153">&gt;&gt; HOUSE REPUBLICAN INVESTIGATORS HAVE UNEARTHED E-MAILS REVIEWED BY NBC WHICH </p>
<p begin="00:04:46.153" end="00:04:49.756">REVEAL REPEATED WARNINGS BY GOVERNMENT STAFF BEARS THE LOAN.</p>
<p begin="00:04:49.756" end="00:04:54.761">&quot;THIS DEAL IS NOT RETREAD FOR PRIME TIME&quot; DAYS BEFORE FINAL APPROVAL A </p>
<p begin="00:04:54.761" end="00:05:01.101">WARNING THAT ONE MODEL SHOWED THE PROJECT WOULD RUN OUT OF CASH IN SEPTEMBER 2011.</p>
<p begin="00:05:01.101" end="00:05:10.177">( LAUGHTER ) </p>
<p begin="00:05:10.177" end="00:05:11.712">&gt;&gt; Jon:  BURN ON YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:05:11.712" end="00:05:15.749">SOLYNDRA WENT OUT OF BUSINESS,</p>
<p begin="00:05:15.749" end="00:05:17.050">SEPTEMBER 6, 2011.</p>
<p begin="00:05:17.050" end="00:05:22.589">ON THE PLUS SIDE, HOW ABOUT A LITTLE SOMETHING FOR FACELESS BUREAUCRATS?</p>
<p begin="00:05:22.589" end="00:05:24.091">I ALMOST HESITATE TO ASK THIS,</p>
<p begin="00:05:24.091" end="00:05:29.530">BUT IS THERE ANY FORMULATION OF THE SOLYNDRA BUSINESS MODEL THAT WOULD PERHAPS PAINT THIS IN EVEN </p>
<p begin="00:05:29.530" end="00:05:32.266">MORE STARK WAYS THE FOOLISHNESS OF OUR INVESTMENT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:32.266" end="00:05:36.870">&gt;&gt; SOME FINANCIAL ANALYSTS WHO STUDIED THE INDUSTRY SAYS SOLYNDRA&apos;S BUSINESS PLAN TO </p>
<p begin="00:05:36.870" end="00:05:39.506">BUILD SOLAR PANELS OF FATALLY FLAWED FROM BEGINNING.</p>
<p begin="00:05:39.506" end="00:05:43.510">&gt;&gt; THEIR PRICE IS OVER $6 TO PRODUCE THE PRODUCT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:43.510" end="00:05:46.079">THEY WERE SELLING IT AT ABOUT $3.</p>
<p begin="00:05:46.079" end="00:05:49.082">BUT WHEN YOU LOOKED AT THE NUMBERS, IT JUST DIDN&apos;T WORK.</p>
<p begin="00:05:49.082" end="00:05:51.451">( LAUGHTER ) </p>
<p begin="00:05:51.451" end="00:05:57.558">&gt;&gt; Jon:  I WONDER IF THAT&apos;S WHY MY BUSINESS, JOHNNY&apos;S CAPITOL HILL 10 BILL GET ONE </p>
<p begin="00:05:57.558" end="00:06:01.361">FREE BUY ONE EMPORIUM, DIDN&apos;T WORK BECAUSE I HAD PLENTY OF VOLUME.</p>
<p begin="00:06:01.361" end="00:06:10.170">( LAUGHTER ) YOU KNOW, STORIES ABOUT INCOMPETENCE IN GOVERNMENT ARE ONLY GOING TO GET YOU SO FAR,</p>
<p begin="00:06:10.170" end="00:06:10.504">THOUGH.</p>
<p begin="00:06:10.504" end="00:06:13.140">FOR THIS TO TRULY BECOME A WEAPONS-GRADE POLITICAL FODDER,</p>
<p begin="00:06:13.140" end="00:06:18.345">YOU&apos;RE GOING TO NEED INCOMPETENCE WITH MORE THAN JUST A WHIFF OF SINISTER CRONYISM.</p>
<p begin="00:06:18.345" end="00:06:23.717">&gt;&gt; ACCORDING TO WHITE HOUSE LOGES, ONE OF SOLYNDRA&apos;S PRINCIPAL INVEST ORGANIZE GEORGE </p>
<p begin="00:06:23.717" end="00:06:29.389">KAISER, WHO WAS A BIG OBAMA FUND-RAISER, VISITED THE WHITE HOUSE AT LEAST FOUR TIMES BEFORE </p>
<p begin="00:06:29.389" end="00:06:33.927">THE LOPE&apos;S FINAL APPROVAL TO SEE AIDES.</p>
<p begin="00:06:33.927" end="00:06:39.700">&gt;&gt; Jon:  I RARELY USE THIS LINE FOR BLATANT PUBLIC SERVICE ANNOUNCEMENT, BUT IF I MAY, FOX </p>
<p begin="00:06:39.700" end="00:06:45.472">NEWS, CALL YOUR DOCTOR BECAUSE THE ERECTION YOU CURRENTLY HAVE HAVE...</p>
<p begin="00:06:45.472" end="00:06:50.644">( LAUGHTER ) ( APPLAUSE ) IS GOING TO LAST LONGER THAN FOUR HOURS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:50.644" end="00:06:54.348">( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ) WOW.</p>
<p begin="00:06:54.348" end="00:06:56.817">JUST HOW BAD IS IT?</p>
<p begin="00:06:56.817" end="00:06:59.086">JUST HOW BAD IS THIS FOR THE ADMINISTRATION?</p>
<p begin="00:06:59.086" end="00:07:02.823">YOU KNOW HOW WHENEVER THERE&apos;S A SCANDAL CONGRESS HOLDS A HEARING TO INVESTIGATE THE MATTER BUT </p>
<p begin="00:07:02.823" end="00:07:08.562">THEY USUALLY JUST PROVE THEMSELVES TO BE CLUELESS GRAND STANDERS.</p>
<p begin="00:07:08.562" end="00:07:13.166">WATCH THE CONGRESS FROM CALIFORNIA LAY SERIOUS SOLAR SHAQ DOWN ON THE DIRECTOR OF THE </p>
<p begin="00:07:13.166" end="00:07:14.601">DEPARTMENT OF ENERGY&apos;S LOAN PROGRAM.</p>
<p begin="00:07:14.601" end="00:07:20.774">&gt;&gt; WERE YOU INFORMED THERE HAVE BEEN MORE FALSE STARTS AND FAILURES IN THIN FILMS.</p>
<p begin="00:07:20.774" end="00:07:27.281">WERE YOU AWARE AS WE TALK ABOUT CHINA, CHINA HAS CONCENTRATED ALMOST OSTENSIBLY IN POLLY </p>
<p begin="00:07:27.281" end="00:07:29.750">CRYSTAL TECHNOLOGY AND AVOID THIN FILM?</p>
<p begin="00:07:29.750" end="00:07:36.056">&gt;&gt; Jon:  AT LOT OF LONGLAST HAVE YOU NO CALCULATION OF THE ABILITY OF SOLAR FLARES AND THE </p>
<p begin="00:07:36.056" end="00:07:38.659">PHOTO SYNTHETIC ALGORITHM, SIR.</p>
<p begin="00:07:38.659" end="00:07:42.429">I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THE ( BLEEP ) THAT CONGRESSMAN FROM CALIFORNIA IS TALKING ABOUT, BUT </p>
<p begin="00:07:42.429" end="00:07:47.734">HERE&apos;S THE THING-- HE DOES.</p>
<p begin="00:07:47.734" end="00:07:51.104">DEAR LORD, IN A SITUATION LIKE THIS, WHO WILL HAVE THE LAST WORD?</p>
<p begin="00:07:51.104" end="00:07:58.345">THE MOST IRONIC WORD, WORDS THAT WERE PERHAPS SPOKEN BY A VIDEO CHAT ON THE OCCASION OF THE </p>
<p begin="00:07:58.345" end="00:08:02.015">GROUNDBREAKING OF SOLYNDRA&apos;S NOW-SHUTTERED PLANT?</p>
<p begin="00:08:02.015" end="00:08:04.685">&gt;&gt; ONCE YOUR FACILITY OPENS,</p>
<p begin="00:08:04.685" end="00:08:09.857">THERE WILL BE ABOUT 1,000 PERMANENT NEW JOBS HERE AT SOLYNDRA, AND IN THE SURROUNDING </p>
<p begin="00:08:09.857" end="00:08:15.662">BUSINESS COMMUNITY, AND HUNDREDS MORE TO INSTALL YOUR GROWING OUTPUT OF SERIAL PANELS </p>
<p begin="00:08:15.662" end="00:08:17.831">THROUGHOUT THE COUNTRY.</p>
<p begin="00:08:17.831" end="00:08:21.435">IT&apos;S IMPORTANT, IT&apos;S IMPORTANT BECAUSE THESE JOBS ARE GOING TO BE PERMANENT JOBS.</p>
<p begin="00:08:21.435" end="00:08:22.836">( LAUGHTER ) </p>
<p begin="00:08:22.836" end="00:08:28.475">&gt;&gt; Jon:  YOU KNOW, JOE, I HATE TO SAY THIS, BUT THERE&apos;S REALLY NO SUCH THING AS A </p>
<p begin="00:08:28.475" end="00:08:30.177">PERMANENT JOB.</p>
<p begin="00:08:30.177" end="00:08:32.613">( LAUGHTER ) WE&apos;LL BE RIGHT BACK.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
