<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:04.605" end="00:00:05.239">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE).</p>
<p begin="00:00:05.239" end="00:00:06.440">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELCOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:06.440" end="00:00:10.477">MY GUEST TONIGHT SERVED FOR 18 YEARS AS A UNITED STATES SENATOR FROM WISCONSIN.</p>
<p begin="00:00:10.477" end="00:00:15.249">HIS NEW BOOK IS CALLED &quot;WHILE AMERICA SLEEPS: A WAKEUP CALL FOR THE POST-9/11 ERA.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:00:15.249" end="00:00:19.219">WELCOME BACK TO THE PROGRAM RUSS FEINGOLD.</p>
<p begin="00:00:19.219" end="00:00:25.192">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) HOW ARE YOU?</p>
<p begin="00:00:25.192" end="00:00:27.494">&gt;&gt; VERY GOOD.</p>
<p begin="00:00:27.494" end="00:00:28.595">THANKS FOR HAVING ME ON.</p>
<p begin="00:00:28.595" end="00:00:32.699">&gt;&gt; Jon: THE BOOK IS CALLED &quot;WHILE AMERICA SLEEPS.&quot; IT IS ONE OF THE SCARIEST </p>
<p begin="00:00:32.699" end="00:00:34.568">BEDTIME STORIES YOU COULD EVER READ.</p>
<p begin="00:00:34.568" end="00:00:37.371">(LAUGHTER) IT&apos;S A CHILDREN&apos;S BOOK, AM I RIGHT?</p>
<p begin="00:00:37.371" end="00:00:37.905">PICTURES TO COME.</p>
<p begin="00:00:37.905" end="00:00:39.439">&gt;&gt; ABSOLUTELY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:39.439" end="00:00:46.380">&gt;&gt; Jon: IT SORT OF BEGINS 9/11 AND SORT OF HOW... TALKS ABOUT HOW THE GOVERNMENT LOST OUR </p>
<p begin="00:00:46.380" end="00:00:49.550">MINDS A LITTLE BIT, WENT INTO IRAQ, DID A LOT OF THINGS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:49.550" end="00:00:52.586">AS YOU&apos;RE WATCHING NOW-- AND WE WERE TALKING ABOUT THIS WITH THE </p>
<p begin="00:00:52.586" end="00:01:00.827">AUDIENCE EARLIER-- DO YOU FEEL US MOVING IN THAT DIRECTION AGAIN WITH IRAN?</p>
<p begin="00:01:00.827" end="00:01:07.835">AND DO YOU THINK... IS IT EASY FOR AMERICA TO BOMB THEM SINCE IT&apos;S ONLY REALLY ONE LETTER OFF ANYWAY?</p>
<p begin="00:01:07.835" end="00:01:08.202">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:01:08.202" end="00:01:10.170">&gt;&gt; THERE MIGHT BE SOME CONFUSION.</p>
<p begin="00:01:10.170" end="00:01:13.507">THE PROBLEM IS AFTER 9/11 WE SORT OF HAD THINGS RIGHT FOR A WHILE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:13.507" end="00:01:18.078">THERE WAS SORT OF A FEELING OF UNITY, WE WERE GOING TO PAY ATTENTION TO THE REST OF THE WORLD.</p>
<p begin="00:01:18.078" end="00:01:20.080">THE WAY WE WENT INTO AFGHANISTAN WAS MEASURED.</p>
<p begin="00:01:20.080" end="00:01:25.152">BUT THEN IRAQ OCCURRED AND ALL OF A SUDDEN WE DECIDED WE HAD TO DO SOMETHING... IT WAS LIKE A </p>
<p begin="00:01:25.152" end="00:01:25.919">GAME OF RISK.</p>
<p begin="00:01:25.919" end="00:01:29.156">YOU HAD TO INVADE A COUNTRY AND YOU HAVE TO KEEP YOUR TROOPS THERE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:29.156" end="00:01:30.557">THEN YOU INVADE ANOTHER COUNTRY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:30.557" end="00:01:35.295">SO WE DID AFGHANISTAN, WE DID IRAQ, AND NOW IT FEELS LIKE INSTEAD OF LOOKING AT THE GLOBAL </p>
<p begin="00:01:35.295" end="00:01:37.965">THREAT OF AL QAEDA AND OTHER ISSUES, NOW IT&apos;S ALL IRAN.</p>
<p begin="00:01:37.965" end="00:01:42.102">IRAN 24 HOURS A DAY BECAUSE IT SUIT IT IS PURPOSES OF THE CONSERVATIVE CANDIDATES WHO WANT </p>
<p begin="00:01:42.102" end="00:01:43.937">TO TRY TO EMBARRASS THE PRESIDENT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:43.937" end="00:01:48.675">SO WE DON&apos;T HAVE THE GLOBAL ATTENTION THAT I THOUGHT WE ALL AGREED WE HAD TO HAVE AFTER WE </p>
<p begin="00:01:48.675" end="00:01:51.778">WERE SURPRISED AND AWAKENED ON 9/11.</p>
<p begin="00:01:51.778" end="00:01:59.520">&gt;&gt; Jon: COULDN&apos;T WE-- IF IT IS RISK-- JUST, AS I WOULD END THOSE GAMES, KNOCK THE BOARD OVER?</p>
<p begin="00:01:59.520" end="00:01:59.887">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:01:59.887" end="00:02:01.054">&gt;&gt; IT&apos;S AN IDEA.</p>
<p begin="00:02:01.054" end="00:02:03.190">I&apos;D PREFER THE GAME OF SCRABBLE IN THIS SITUATION.</p>
<p begin="00:02:03.190" end="00:02:04.391">&gt;&gt; Jon: SURE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:04.391" end="00:02:04.691">SURE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:04.691" end="00:02:07.160">&gt;&gt; WHERE YOU HAVE TO KIND OF THINK IN TWO DIRECTIONS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:07.160" end="00:02:12.165">YOU MIGHT NOTICE THAT YEMEN IS CLOSE TO SOMALIA AND THAT&apos;S CLOSE TO WHERE THERE&apos;S AN </p>
<p begin="00:02:12.165" end="00:02:17.538">ISLAMIC GROUP IN NORTHERN AFRICA WHO ARE CREATING SOME OF THESE PROBLEMS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:17.538" end="00:02:21.175">&gt;&gt; Jon: WAIT, YOU&apos;RE NOT SAYING THAT WE SHOULD BOMB THEM?</p>
<p begin="00:02:21.175" end="00:02:22.943">&gt;&gt; HERE&apos;S WHAT WE OUGHT TO DO.</p>
<p begin="00:02:22.943" end="00:02:24.878">WE OUGHT TO AT LEAST KNOW WHAT&apos;S GOING ON.</p>
<p begin="00:02:24.878" end="00:02:27.481">AND WE DON&apos;T HAVE A PRESENCE IN THE REST OF THE WORLD.</p>
<p begin="00:02:27.481" end="00:02:29.883">&gt;&gt; Jon: IT&apos;S CHANGING SO QUICKLY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:29.883" end="00:02:37.391">EVEN THE TIME IT TOOK TO JUST PRINT UP A BOOK-- A LOT OF THIS FOCUSES ON YEMEN AND SOMALIA-- </p>
<p begin="00:02:37.391" end="00:02:40.761">NOW IT&apos;S SHIFTED TO SYRIA AND IRAN AND SO MANY OTHER PLACES.</p>
<p begin="00:02:40.761" end="00:02:43.096">IT MOVES SO QUICKLY WE ALMOST DON&apos;T HAVE TIME.</p>
<p begin="00:02:43.096" end="00:02:44.164">&gt;&gt; IT&apos;S HARD.</p>
<p begin="00:02:44.164" end="00:02:47.601">THE ANALOGY I USE IS WHEN WE WERE KIDS THERE WERE JUST SEVEN OR EIGHT...</p>
<p begin="00:02:47.601" end="00:02:49.136">&gt;&gt; Jon: IS THIS ABOUT RISK AGAIN?</p>
<p begin="00:02:49.136" end="00:02:50.270">&gt;&gt; THIS ISN&apos;T ABOUT RISK.</p>
<p begin="00:02:50.270" end="00:02:52.806">THIS IS ABOUT SEVEN OR EIGHT BASEBALL TEAMS WHEN WE WERE KID.</p>
<p begin="00:02:52.806" end="00:02:54.107">WE KNEW ALL THE BASEBALL TEAMS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:54.107" end="00:02:58.478">NOW THE WORLD IS ALSO VERY COMPLICATED COMPARED TO WHAT IT WAS WHEN WE WERE KIDS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:58.478" end="00:03:00.614">WHEN WE WERE KIDS IT WAS THE SOVIET UNION AND THE UNITED STATES.</p>
<p begin="00:03:00.614" end="00:03:02.616">YES, THERE ARE MANY PLACES WE HAVE TO BE CONCERNED ABOUT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:02.616" end="00:03:03.383">BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?</p>
<p begin="00:03:03.383" end="00:03:05.052">WE DON&apos;T HAVE A CHOICE ANYMORE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:05.052" end="00:03:06.720">WE HAVE TO LEARN ABOUT THE REST OF THE WORLD.</p>
<p begin="00:03:06.720" end="00:03:11.725">WE HAVE TO KNOW ABOUT WHO IS ACTUALLY WILLING TO WORK WITH US IN PLACES LIKE NORTHERN AFRICA </p>
<p begin="00:03:11.725" end="00:03:12.926">AND SOUTHEAST ASIA.</p>
<p begin="00:03:12.926" end="00:03:15.762">WE CAN&apos;T GO &quot;GEE, TODAY IT&apos;S IRAN.</p>
<p begin="00:03:15.762" end="00:03:19.166">TOMORROW IT&apos;S YEMEN, THE NEXT DAY IT&apos;S INDONESIA.&quot; IT DOESN&apos;T WORK.</p>
<p begin="00:03:19.166" end="00:03:25.272">&gt;&gt; Jon: TO SUM UP, YOU&apos;RE SUGGESTING THAT WE SHOULD DO LIKE THEY DO IN BASEBALL-- CONSOLIDATE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:25.272" end="00:03:27.140">THERE SHOULD ONLY BE SIX TO EIGHT COUNTRIES?</p>
<p begin="00:03:27.140" end="00:03:28.108">&gt;&gt; THAT&apos;S EXACTLY RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:28.108" end="00:03:33.480">TO MAKE IT LIKE A GAME OF RISK WHERE YOU HAVE THESE HUGE GLOBS OF COUNTRIES.</p>
<p begin="00:03:33.480" end="00:03:38.519">&gt;&gt; Jon: CAMPAIGN FINANCE WAS AN ENORMOUS UNDERTAKING FOR YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:03:38.519" end="00:03:41.255">McCAIN-FEINGOLD OBVIOUSLY TOOK YOU... HOW LONG DID IT TAKE TO PUT THAT?</p>
<p begin="00:03:41.255" end="00:03:43.357">&gt;&gt; IT TOOK EIGHT YEARS TO GET THAT DONE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:43.357" end="00:03:44.958">&gt;&gt; Jon: EIGHT YEARS TO GET THAT DONE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:44.958" end="00:03:53.800">SO WHAT IS YOUR FEELING ON THE STATE OF CAMPAIGN FINANCE IN AMERICA TODAY VIS-A-VIS IS THERE ANY?</p>
<p begin="00:03:53.800" end="00:03:54.168">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:03:54.168" end="00:03:54.902">&gt;&gt; IT COULD BE BETTER.</p>
<p begin="00:03:54.902" end="00:04:00.307">THE TRUTH IS THAT McCAIN-FEINGOLD WAS BIT ON THIS FOUNDATION AND ACTUALLY WORKED TO STOP DIRECT </p>
<p begin="00:04:00.307" end="00:04:03.744">CONTRIBUTIONS TO THE POLITICAL PARTIES AND POLITICIANS RAISING IT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:03.744" end="00:04:08.081">WHAT THE SUPREME COURT DID IS N CITIZENS UNITED WAS DESTROY THE ENTIRE FOUNDATION AND NOW WE </p>
<p begin="00:04:08.081" end="00:04:13.187">HAVE CORPORATIONS AND UNIONS ABLE TO USE THEIR TREASURIES DIRECTLY TO DO THE STUFF THEY&apos;VE </p>
<p begin="00:04:13.187" end="00:04:17.624">NEVER BEEN ABLE TO DO SINCE THE GILDED AGE, SINCE TEDDY ROOSEVELT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:17.624" end="00:04:22.329">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU KNOW I REMEMBER AFTER McCAIN-FEINGOLD PASSED THE 527s CAME OUT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:22.329" end="00:04:24.498">WAS THIS A LOOPHOLE THEY FOUND ALMOST IMMEDIATELY?</p>
<p begin="00:04:24.498" end="00:04:28.101">&gt;&gt; NO, THEY COULD NOT DO THAT DIRECTLY FROM THE CORPORATE TREASURIES AND ACTUALLY I </p>
<p begin="00:04:28.101" end="00:04:30.704">BELIEVE THAT WAS ILLEGAL AS WELL AT THE TIME.</p>
<p begin="00:04:30.704" end="00:04:31.605">THAT SHOULD HAVE BEEN IN COURT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:31.605" end="00:04:35.642">WE DON&apos;T HAVE AN AGENCY IN THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT... THE FEDERAL ELECTIONS COMMISSION </p>
<p begin="00:04:35.642" end="00:04:36.577">DOESN&apos;T ENFORCE THE LAW.</p>
<p begin="00:04:36.577" end="00:04:41.281">SO WE HAVE A TERRIBLE SITUATION UNLESS THE SUPREME COURT REVERSES, WHICH I THINK IT MAY </p>
<p begin="00:04:41.281" end="00:04:45.285">AT SOME POINT IN THE FUTURE, IF THE PRESIDENT IS REELECTED AND ABLE TO GET DIFFERENT SUPREME </p>
<p begin="00:04:45.285" end="00:04:45.853">COURT JUSTICES.</p>
<p begin="00:04:45.853" end="00:04:51.992">IN THE MEANTIME, WE HAVE A MELTDOWN AND A VERY... THE WORST CORRUPTION PERHAPS IN 100 YEARS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:51.992" end="00:04:57.130">&gt;&gt; Jon: IS CITIZENS UNITED THE ISSUE OR IS IT THE ISSUE WHEN THEY ULTIMATELY DECIDED MONEY </p>
<p begin="00:04:57.130" end="00:04:57.698">EQUALS SPEECH?</p>
<p begin="00:04:57.698" end="00:05:01.735">IS THAT THE MORE FUNDAMENTAL FOUNDATION OF THIS THAT MAKES IT MORE DIFFICULT?</p>
<p begin="00:05:01.735" end="00:05:05.239">BECAUSE ONCE YOU DECIDE THAT, AS LONG AS YOUR MONEY DOESN&apos;T YELL </p>
<p begin="00:05:05.239" end="00:05:07.374">&quot;FIRE&quot; IN A CROWDED THEATER...</p>
<p begin="00:05:07.374" end="00:05:07.774">(LAUGHTER).</p>
<p begin="00:05:07.774" end="00:05:12.079">&gt;&gt; WELL, THE COURT NEVER ACTUALLY CONCLUDED THAT MONEY IS SPEECH IN ALL CASES.</p>
<p begin="00:05:12.079" end="00:05:16.083">THEY SAID IF IT CAUSES CORRUPTION OR APPEARANCE OF CORRUPTION YOU CAN REGULATE IT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:16.083" end="00:05:19.052">THAT&apos;S WHY YOU HAVE LIMITS ON CAMPAIGN CONTRIBUTIONS UNDER FEDERAL LAW.</p>
<p begin="00:05:19.052" end="00:05:21.421">SO THE PROBLEM IS CITIZENS UNITED.</p>
<p begin="00:05:21.421" end="00:05:25.559">IT OVERTURNED A LAW FROM 1907 THAT NOBODY EVER QUESTIONED AND ANOTHER LAW FROM 1947.</p>
<p begin="00:05:25.559" end="00:05:27.394">SO BASICALLY THE SUPREME COURT JUST MADE IT UP.</p>
<p begin="00:05:27.394" end="00:05:31.899">IT WAS ONE OF THE WORST DECISIONS IN THE HISTORY OF THE COUNTRY AND IT&apos;S THE ONLY DECISION...</p>
<p begin="00:05:31.899" end="00:05:36.470">(APPLAUSE).</p>
<p begin="00:05:36.470" end="00:05:41.208">IT&apos;S THE ONLY DECISION I CAN REMEMBER THAT THE AVERAGE CITIZEN KNOWS ABOUT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:41.208" end="00:05:43.677">THEY KNOW SOMETHING&apos;S WRONG AND THIS WHOLE THING IS GOING TO </p>
<p begin="00:05:43.677" end="00:05:45.379">COLLAPSE AND WE&apos;LL HAVE TO CLEAN IT UP.</p>
<p begin="00:05:45.379" end="00:05:47.514">&gt;&gt; Jon: EVERYBODY YOU TALKED TO SAYS THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:47.514" end="00:05:50.517">THERE&apos;S NOT A POLITICIAN YOU TALK TO DOESN&apos;T SAY &quot;THE BIGGEST </p>
<p begin="00:05:50.517" end="00:05:55.489">PROBLEM IN OUR SYSTEM IS THE INFLUENCE OF MONEY.&quot; &quot;WHAT SHOULD WE DO ABOUT THAT?&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:05:55.489" end="00:05:57.858">&quot;I DON&apos;T KNOW, WE SHOULD DO SOMETHING ABOUT THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:57.858" end="00:05:58.091">&quot;.</p>
<p begin="00:05:58.091" end="00:06:01.261">(LAUGHTER) EVEN McCAIN-FEINGOLD, YOU&apos;RE STILL... THE FOUNDATION IS STILL </p>
<p begin="00:06:01.261" end="00:06:05.365">THE TERMITE-INFESTED FOUNDATION WE STARTED WITH.</p>
<p begin="00:06:05.365" end="00:06:08.168">WHY WON&apos;T... WHY DOESN&apos;T PUBLIC FINANCING OF ELECTIONS JUST...</p>
<p begin="00:06:08.168" end="00:06:12.906">IF WE HAVE THE ABILITY TO REGULATE IT, WHY NOT JUST SAY THIS IS THE WAY WE&apos;RE GOING TO DO IT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:12.906" end="00:06:16.443">THE ELECTIONS ARE 12 WEEKS, IT&apos;S PUBLICLY FINANCED, THIS IS HOW IT GOES.</p>
<p begin="00:06:16.443" end="00:06:18.812">&gt;&gt; WELL, PUBLIC FINANCING IS THE ANSWER.</p>
<p begin="00:06:18.812" end="00:06:23.050">WE USED TO HAVE A GOOD SYSTEM FOR PRESIDENTIAL PUBLIC FINANCING AND IT SORT OF WENT BY </p>
<p begin="00:06:23.050" end="00:06:24.852">THE WAYSIDE, IT NEEDS TO BE FIXED.</p>
<p begin="00:06:24.852" end="00:06:26.920">WE&apos;VE NEVER HAD IT FOR CONGRESSIONAL ELECTIONS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:26.920" end="00:06:29.256">&gt;&gt; Jon: WHEN DID IT GO BY THE WAYSIDE?</p>
<p begin="00:06:29.256" end="00:06:33.327">&gt;&gt; UNFORTUNATELY IN THE LAST ELECTION PRESIDENT OBAMA DECIDED THAT... CANDIDATE OBAMA DECIDED </p>
<p begin="00:06:33.327" end="00:06:35.395">NOT TO TAKE PUBLIC FINANCING AND...</p>
<p begin="00:06:35.395" end="00:06:38.665">&gt;&gt; Jon: AND HE&apos;S GOING TO DO SUPERPACS NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:06:38.665" end="00:06:41.768">&gt;&gt; HE&apos;S GOING TO BE INVOLVED WITH HIS CABINET MEMBERS WITH </p>
<p begin="00:06:41.768" end="00:06:47.574">THIS AND I DISAGREE AND SANTORUM AND ROMNEY AND GINGRICH ARE GOING TO THEIR ACTUAL SUPER PAC </p>
<p begin="00:06:47.574" end="00:06:48.375">EVENTS THEMSELVES.</p>
<p begin="00:06:48.375" end="00:06:51.512">&gt;&gt; Jon: BUT THEY&apos;RE NOT COORDINATING WITH THEM, JUST TELLING THEM WHAT TO DO.</p>
<p begin="00:06:51.512" end="00:06:54.181">&gt;&gt; NO MORE THAN YOUR SUPER PAC IS DOING THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:54.181" end="00:06:56.450">&gt;&gt; Jon: I WOULD NEVER COORDINATE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:56.450" end="00:06:58.151">YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT YOU CAN WRITE CHECKS FOR.</p>
<p begin="00:06:58.151" end="00:06:59.553">&gt;&gt; THAT&apos;S WHAT I WANT TO KNOW.</p>
<p begin="00:06:59.553" end="00:07:00.654">&gt;&gt; Jon: KING OF THE WORLD.</p>
<p begin="00:07:00.654" end="00:07:08.395">ARE YOU FEELING HOPEFUL ABOUT THE FUTURE OF THE POLITICAL WILL TO GO TO A DIFFERENT SYSTEM OF ELECTIONS?</p>
<p begin="00:07:08.395" end="00:07:09.196">&gt;&gt; OH, YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:07:09.196" end="00:07:12.266">I THINK THIS THING IS GOING TO COME TO A HEAD.</p>
<p begin="00:07:12.266" end="00:07:16.803">I THINK PEOPLE ARE GOING TO FIND OUT WHAT IS GOING ON IN SOME OF THESE CONVERSATIONS YOU AND </p>
<p begin="00:07:16.803" end="00:07:21.708">OTHERS ARE HAVING WITH YOUR SUPER PACS AND THERE&apos;S GOING TO BE AN EXPLOSION OF CORRUPTION </p>
<p begin="00:07:21.708" end="00:07:24.611">THAT BRINGS CHANGE JUST LIKE McCAIN-FEINGOLD.</p>
<p begin="00:07:24.611" end="00:07:25.913">IT WAS THE SCANDALS THAT CAME UP...</p>
<p begin="00:07:25.913" end="00:07:26.547">&gt;&gt; Jon: WATERGATE?</p>
<p begin="00:07:26.547" end="00:07:33.420">&gt;&gt; WATERGATE WAS THE FIRST ONE AND THEN THE $400,000 CHECK FROM THE INDONESIAN GARDENER UNDER </p>
<p begin="00:07:33.420" end="00:07:34.121">PRESIDENT CLINTON.</p>
<p begin="00:07:34.121" end="00:07:37.424">&gt;&gt; Jon: I LOVE HOW THAT ROLLS OFF YOUR TONGUE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:37.424" end="00:07:42.362">$400,000 FROM THE INDONESIAN GARDENER UNDER PRESIDENT CLINTON.&quot; DO YOU HAVE TWO SECONDS?</p>
<p begin="00:07:42.362" end="00:07:44.398">WE&apos;LL THROW THIS UP ON THE WEB.</p>
<p begin="00:07:44.398" end="00:07:47.401">&quot;WHILE AMERICA SLEEPS.&quot; IT&apos;S ON THE BOOKSHELVES NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:07:47.401" end="00:07:47.734">RUSS </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
