<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:03.570" end="00:00:06.406">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) </p>
<p begin="00:00:06.406" end="00:00:09.810">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELCOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:09.810" end="00:00:20.621">YOU KNOW, IT&apos;S BEEN NEARLY A YEAR SINCE THE UNITED STATES MILITARY ENDED ITS BAN ON OPENLY </p>
<p begin="00:00:20.621" end="00:00:24.758">GAY AND LESBIAN TROOPS AND SINCE THEN THE UNITED STATES HASN&apos;T WON A SINGLE WAR!</p>
<p begin="00:00:24.758" end="00:00:26.927">BUT YOU WON&apos;T HEAR ABOUT THAT ON THE LAME STREAM NEWS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:26.927" end="00:00:27.261">NOPE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:27.261" end="00:00:33.133">(LAUGHTER) MAYBE BRIAN ROSS WILL THROW IT OUT THERE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:33.133" end="00:00:36.403">(LAUGHTER) THIS GUY WAS IN THE TEA PARTY,</p>
<p begin="00:00:36.403" end="00:00:39.706">HE MIGHT BE A KILLER!</p>
<p begin="00:00:39.706" end="00:00:44.278">(LAUGHTER) IT&apos;S ALL BEEN COMING UP ROSES FOR THE GAY EQUALITY MOVEMENT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:44.278" end="00:00:44.945">NOT TONIGHT!</p>
<p begin="00:00:44.945" end="00:00:47.214">TONIGHT WE&apos;LL TALK ABOUT THE PEOPLE DIGGING IN THEIR HEELS,</p>
<p begin="00:00:47.214" end="00:00:56.623">LIKE THE JAPANESE SOLDIERS ON GUAM WHO BRAVELY FOUGHT WORLD WAR II WELL INTO THE 1970s.</p>
<p begin="00:00:56.623" end="00:00:58.992">THIS IS GAY WATCH, HOLDOUTS EDITION.</p>
<p begin="00:00:58.992" end="00:01:03.730">THE ARMY MAY NOW BE HOS PIT TO BELIEVE GAY PEOPLE BUT THE FAKE ARMY FOR CHILDREN ISN&apos;T GIVING IN.</p>
<p begin="00:01:03.730" end="00:01:08.569">&gt;&gt; THE BOY SCOUTS OF AMERICA REAFFIRMING ITS BAN ON OPENLY GAY BOYS AND ADULT LEADERS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:08.569" end="00:01:12.806">THE SCOUTS MAKING THIS ANNOUNCEMENT AFTER CONDUCTING AN INTERNAL REVIEW AND, DESPITE </p>
<p begin="00:01:12.806" end="00:01:18.478">PROTESTS FROM THE PUBLIC, IT PUT OUT A NEWS RELEASE SAYING ITS EXCLUSIONARY POLICY &quot;REFLECTS </p>
<p begin="00:01:18.478" end="00:01:21.748">THE BELIEFS AND PERSPECTIVES OF THE ORGANIZATION.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:01:21.748" end="00:01:24.084">&gt;&gt; Jon: WOW.</p>
<p begin="00:01:24.084" end="00:01:30.224">I&apos;VE NEVER SEEN A NEWS ORGANIZATION TAKE SUCH A HARSH STAND GOENS SEXUALITY SINCE THE </p>
<p begin="00:01:30.224" end="00:01:33.627">GIRL SCOUTS DISCONTINUED THE CHALET CREEM.</p>
<p begin="00:01:33.627" end="00:01:38.732">WHATEVER YOUR TAKE ON THIS ISSUE YOU HAVE TO ADMIT THAT WAS A PRETTY GAY COOKIE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:38.732" end="00:01:46.640">(LAUGHTER) LOOK, I DON&apos;T WANT TO MINIMIZE THE CONCERNS OF THE BOY SCOUTS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:46.640" end="00:01:55.015">(LAUGHTER) BUT YOU ALREADY... YOU&apos;RE THERE ARE GAYEST ORGANIZATION IN AMERICA.</p>
<p begin="00:01:55.015" end="00:02:03.290">(LAUGHTER) (CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) I MEAN, IF YOU ARE IN ANY WAY CONCERNED ABOUT COMING OFF LIKE </p>
<p begin="00:02:03.290" end="00:02:12.332">A GAY ORGANIZATION, I&apos;M NOT SURE THE NECKERCHIEF IS THE BEST ACCESSORY CHOICE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:12.332" end="00:02:14.601">AND THIS DOESN&apos;T HELP &quot;WAIT,</p>
<p begin="00:02:14.601" end="00:02:20.107">GUYS, I&apos;M JUST GOING TO SEW MY BASKET WEAVING PATCH TO MY SASH BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, I WANT TO </p>
<p begin="00:02:20.107" end="00:02:26.580">LOOK GOOD FOR THE JAMBOREE.&quot; (LAUGHTER) HEY, THE NEW ISSUE OF BOYS LIFE&quot; IS HERE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:26.580" end="00:02:29.583">&quot;HEY, I JUST GOT IT!</p>
<p begin="00:02:29.583" end="00:02:30.918">WOW!</p>
<p begin="00:02:30.918" end="00:02:42.095">CHECK OUT THIS GUY&apos;S... OUT DOORSMANSHIP.&quot; (LAUGHTER) THE BOY SCOUTS DON&apos;T STAND ALONE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:42.095" end="00:02:45.132">THERE&apos;S ANOTHER IMPORTANT CULTURAL INSTITUTION ALSO HOLDING OUT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:45.132" end="00:02:49.736">&gt;&gt; CHICK-FIL-A HAS MADE NO SECRET OF ITS CHRISTIAN VALUES AND NOW ITS PRESIDENT IS MAKING </p>
<p begin="00:02:49.736" end="00:02:55.108">IT CLEAR THAT WHEN IT COMES TO OPPOSING GAY MARRIAGE HE AND HIS COMPANY ARE GUILTY AS CHARGED.</p>
<p begin="00:02:55.108" end="00:02:57.511">&gt;&gt; REALLY?</p>
<p begin="00:02:57.511" end="00:02:58.579">HAS ANYBODY TOLD THIS GUY?</p>
<p begin="00:02:58.579" end="00:03:20.334">(LAUGHTER) THAT IS HOW A COW WOULD SPELL (BLEEP).</p>
<p begin="00:03:20.334" end="00:03:21.602">COWS SOUND THINGS OUT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:21.602" end="00:03:21.969">(BLEEP).</p>
<p begin="00:03:21.969" end="00:03:29.676">(LAUGHTER) SO WHAT EXACTLY IS CHICK-FIL-A C.E.O.&apos;S PROBLEM WITH SAME-SEX MARRIAGE?</p>
<p begin="00:03:29.676" end="00:03:34.181">&gt;&gt; I THINK WE&apos;RE INVITING GOD&apos;S JUDGMENT ON OUR NATION WHEN WE </p>
<p begin="00:03:34.181" end="00:03:38.685">SHAKE OUR FIST AT HIM AND SAY &quot;WE KNOW BETTER THAN YOU AS TO </p>
<p begin="00:03:38.685" end="00:03:45.092">WHAT CONSTITUTES A MARRIAGE.&quot; WE HAVE THE AUDACITY TO REDEFINE WHAT MARRIAGE IS ALL ABOUT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:45.092" end="00:03:48.595">&gt;&gt; Jon: I AGREE WITH THIS MAN WHO MAKES DELICIOUS SANDWICHES!</p>
<p begin="00:03:48.595" end="00:03:53.467">THAT IS WHY I HAVE AND WE AS A CULTURE HAVE ALWAYS DEFINED MARRIAGE AS IT WAS DESIGNED IN </p>
<p begin="00:03:53.467" end="00:03:54.001">THE FINAL.</p>
<p begin="00:03:54.001" end="00:03:57.471">YES, LET&apos;S SEE HOW IT&apos;S DEFINED IN... YES!</p>
<p begin="00:03:57.471" end="00:04:05.445">(LAUGHTER) &quot;IF BROTHERS ARE LIVING TOGETHER AND ONE OF THEM DIES WITHOUT A </p>
<p begin="00:04:05.445" end="00:04:08.415">SON HIS WIDOW MUST NOT MARRY OUTSIDE THE FAMILY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:08.415" end="00:04:12.586">HER HUSBAND&apos;S BROTHER SHALL TAKE HER AND MARRY HER AND FULFILL THE DUTY OF A BROTHER-IN-LAW TO </p>
<p begin="00:04:12.586" end="00:04:14.321">HER.&quot; DUET RONNIE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:14.321" end="00:04:23.197">WAIT &quot;IF A MAN HAPPENS TO MEET A VIRGIN WHO IS NOT PLEDGED HE SHALL PAY HER FATHER 50 </p>
<p begin="00:04:23.197" end="00:04:26.200">SCHECKELS OF SILVER.&quot; HE&apos;S NOT AN ASS (BLEEP).</p>
<p begin="00:04:26.200" end="00:04:30.070">(LAUGHTER) &quot;HE MUST MARRY THE YOUNG WOMAN FOR HE HAS VIOLATED HER.</p>
<p begin="00:04:30.070" end="00:04:33.073">HE CANNOT DIVORCE HER AS LONG AS HE LIVES.&quot; MARRIAGE!</p>
<p begin="00:04:33.073" end="00:04:40.647">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) MARRIAGE!</p>
<p begin="00:04:40.647" end="00:04:45.519">SAMUEL 18 &quot;DAVID TOOK HIS MEN WITH HIM AND KILLED 200 PHILISTINES AND BROUGHT BACK </p>
<p begin="00:04:45.519" end="00:04:52.259">THEIR FORE SKINS.&quot; (LAUGHTER) NOT AS EASY AS IT SOUNDS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:52.259" end="00:04:57.164">(LAUGHTER) THEY COUNTED OUT THE FULL NUMBER TO THE KING.</p>
<p begin="00:04:57.164" end="00:05:10.744">(LAUGHTER) (CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) SO DAVID MIGHT BECOME THE KING&apos;S SON-IN-LAW.</p>
<p begin="00:05:10.744" end="00:05:15.148">THEN SAUL GAVE HIM HIS DAUGHTER IN MARRIAGE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:15.148" end="00:05:15.682">YUP.</p>
<p begin="00:05:15.682" end="00:05:21.288">THAT&apos;S ABOUT AS MANY FORESKINS AS SHE&apos;S WORTH.</p>
<p begin="00:05:21.288" end="00:05:23.056">NATURALLY THERE WAS BOUND TO BE BUSH PAC.</p>
<p begin="00:05:23.056" end="00:05:28.896">THIS WEEKEND THE MUPPETS TOOK TO FACEBOOK TO SAY THE JIM HENSON COMPANY HAS NOTIFIED CHICK-FIL-A </p>
<p begin="00:05:28.896" end="00:05:33.600">THAT WE DON&apos;T WISH TO PARTNER THEM ON ANY FUTURE ENDEAVORS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:33.600" end="00:05:40.107">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) THE MUPPETS WERE PARTNERED WITH CHICK-FIL-A?</p>
<p begin="00:05:40.107" end="00:05:43.243">(LAUGHTER) THE DOES BIG BIRD KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT THAT?</p>
<p begin="00:05:43.243" end="00:05:51.485">(LAUGHTER) (AS BIG BIRD&quot;) HEY, GUYS, WHAT&apos;S EVERYBODY EATING?</p>
<p begin="00:05:51.485" end="00:05:52.553">&gt;&gt; NOTHING, BIG BIRD,</p>
<p begin="00:05:52.553" end="00:05:53.220">EVERYTHING&apos;S COOL?</p>
<p begin="00:05:53.220" end="00:05:54.555">&gt;&gt; HAS ANYONE SEEN MY KIDS?</p>
<p begin="00:05:54.555" end="00:06:00.360">(LAUGHTER) ANYWAY, NOT JUST THE MUPPETS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:00.360" end="00:06:03.864">BOSTON MAYOR TOM MENINO HAD A MESSAGE FOR CHICK-FIL-A.</p>
<p begin="00:06:03.864" end="00:06:07.868">&gt;&gt; MAYOR MENINO SAYS THE SOUTHERN FAST FOOD CHAIN&apos;S POLICY WON&apos;T FLY IN BOSTON.</p>
<p begin="00:06:07.868" end="00:06:11.505">&gt;&gt; HE WON&apos;T ALLOW CHICK-FIL-A INTO BOSTON UNLESS THEY CHANGE THEIR POLICY.</p>
<p begin="00:06:11.505" end="00:06:12.439">&gt;&gt; Jon: WOW.</p>
<p begin="00:06:12.439" end="00:06:15.475">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) OPEN YOUR EYES.</p>
<p begin="00:06:15.475" end="00:06:21.114">OPEN YOUR EYES, OWNER OF CHICK-FIL-A.</p>
<p begin="00:06:21.114" end="00:06:25.152">YOU&apos;RE BEING SUCH AN AS (BLEEP) NOT EVEN BOSTON WILL TOLERATE YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:06:25.152" end="00:06:30.090">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) WE&apos;LL BE RIGHT </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
