<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:02.269" end="00:00:14.314">&gt;&gt; Stewart: IN A NEW STORY, A SEGMENT WE CALL BACK IN BLACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:14.314" end="00:00:16.517">&gt;&gt; I HAVE SAD NEWS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:16.517" end="00:00:18.151">IF YOU ARE EATING RIGHT NOW,</p>
<p begin="00:00:18.151" end="00:00:22.189">CHANCES ARE YOU ARE NOT EATING WHAT YOU THINK YOU ARE EATING.</p>
<p begin="00:00:22.189" end="00:00:24.758">UNLESS YOU ARE HAVING A HOT DOG.</p>
<p begin="00:00:24.758" end="00:00:31.431">THEN YOU KNOW YOU ARE EATING PIG ANUSES.</p>
<p begin="00:00:31.431" end="00:00:34.201">HAVE YOU EVER EATEN KOBE BEEF?  NO, YOU HAVEN&apos;T.</p>
<p begin="00:00:34.201" end="00:00:36.603">YOU JUST PAID FOR KOBE BEEF.</p>
<p begin="00:00:36.603" end="00:00:40.340">IN FACT, YOU CAN&apos;T EVEN BUY KOBE BEEF IN THIS COUNTRY BECAUSE IT </p>
<p begin="00:00:40.340" end="00:00:44.711">IS ONLY MADE IN JAPAN, AND IT IS ILLEGAL TO IMPORT IT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:44.711" end="00:00:51.218">SO IF YOUR LOCAL BISTRO IS SERVING KOBE SLIDERS, JUST GO ACROSS THE STREET TO WHITE </p>
<p begin="00:00:51.218" end="00:00:55.689">CASTLE, HAVE THAT (BLEEP), HAVE THE EXACT SAME (BLEEP) THING.</p>
<p begin="00:00:55.689" end="00:01:03.096">THESE PEOPLE ARE PISSING ON OUR LEGS AND TELLING US IT IS CHAMPAGNE!  AND IT IS NOT JUST MEAT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:03.096" end="00:01:08.769">A REPORT BE ADVOCACY GROUP ASSOCIATION IA TESTED SEAFOOD AROUND LOS ANGELES AND FOUND </p>
<p begin="00:01:08.769" end="00:01:10.637">CONSUMERS BUYING ONE FISH BUT GETTING ANOTHER.</p>
<p begin="00:01:10.637" end="00:01:16.310">&gt;&gt; THE WORD FOR SUSHI RESTAURANTS, 87 PERCENT, JOHN,</p>
<p begin="00:01:16.310" end="00:01:20.347">100 PERCENT OF THE SNAPPER THAT WAS TESTED WAS WRONG.</p>
<p begin="00:01:20.347" end="00:01:26.453">&gt;&gt; Stewart: SNAPPER CALAMITY LAP I CAN&apos;T, WHO GIVES A (BLEEP)!  THAT&apos;S WHAT THE </p>
<p begin="00:01:26.453" end="00:01:35.095">KETCHUP IS FOR!  LOOK, LIE ALL YOU WANT ABOUT YOUR BAKED BEEF OR YOUR MYSTERY FISH, BUT THIS </p>
<p begin="00:01:35.095" end="00:01:35.929">IS INEXCUSABLE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:35.929" end="00:01:42.236">&gt;&gt; DUNKIN&apos;&apos;S ARTISAN BEIGE CRIMINAL AS AUTHENTIC AS IT GETS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:42.236" end="00:01:45.839">&gt;&gt; REALLY, AUTHENTIC BAGELS?  BECAUSE UNLESS YOU CHANGE YOUR </p>
<p begin="00:01:45.839" end="00:01:50.244">NAME FROM DUNKIN&apos; DONUTS AND ELLIS ISLAND, THEN I DOUBT IT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:50.244" end="00:01:56.149">&gt;&gt; IN FACT, A BAKE NEVER QUEENS IS EVEN FILED A LEGAL COMPLAINT,</p>
<p begin="00:01:56.149" end="00:02:00.787">NOT ABOUT THE LOUSY BAGELS BUT THAT THEY ARE ABUSING THE WORD ARTISAN.</p>
<p begin="00:02:00.787" end="00:02:02.422">&gt;&gt; WHAT DO YOU THINK ARTISAN MEANS?</p>
<p begin="00:02:02.422" end="00:02:09.696">&gt;&gt; I BELIEVE IT IS WELL CRAFTED AND SAN MEANS ONE WHO CARES.</p>
<p begin="00:02:09.696" end="00:02:10.864">I THINK BATTER DOES REALLY,</p>
<p begin="00:02:10.864" end="00:02:11.431">REALLY GOOD THINGS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:11.431" end="00:02:17.905">&gt;&gt; WHAT A SURPRISE, A HIPSTER TALKING OUT OF HIS BUTT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:17.905" end="00:02:27.080">&gt;&gt; WELL, LET ME HELP YOU OUT AND WHATEVER (BLEEP) YOUR NAME IS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:27.080" end="00:02:27.414">ARTISAN.</p>
<p begin="00:02:27.414" end="00:02:32.920">A CRAFTS PERSON WHO PRODUCES SOMETHING IN LIMITED QUANTITIES,</p>
<p begin="00:02:32.920" end="00:02:34.087">OFTEN USING TRADITIONAL METHODS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:34.087" end="00:02:37.424">&gt;&gt; IN OTHER WORDS, NOT THIS STUFF!</p>
<p begin="00:02:37.424" end="00:02:39.893">&gt;&gt; AND DUNKIN&apos; DONUTS ISN&apos;T ALONE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:39.893" end="00:02:49.536">PLENTY OF COMPANIES ARE TRYING TO CONVINCE US THEIR CHEESE IS LOVINGLY CRAFTED BY PEASANTS AND </p>
<p begin="00:02:49.536" end="00:02:55.175">THE FISH IS INDIVIDUALLY INSPECTED FROM LAKE WATER ON THE CHOCOLATE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:55.175" end="00:02:57.344">HERE IS A GOOD RULE OF THUMB.</p>
<p begin="00:02:57.344" end="00:03:05.285">IF YOU YOUR PRODUCT IS SERVED BY DUMPING IT OUT OF A PLASTIC BAG INTO A BOWL OF MICROWAVE JELLY,</p>
<p begin="00:03:05.285" end="00:03:07.521">IT IS NOT ARTISAN.</p>
<p begin="00:03:07.521" end="00:03:14.228">AND IF IT TAKES LESS THAN 30 MINUTES TO MAKE AND DELIVER, I AM NOT SURE IT IS EVEN FOOD.</p>
<p begin="00:03:14.228" end="00:03:18.532">&gt;&gt; AT DOMINOES WE ALWAYS SAID YES YOU WANT YOUR PIZZA DELIVERED WE SAID YES BUT WHEN </p>
<p begin="00:03:18.532" end="00:03:23.070">IT COMES TO OUR ARTISAN PIZZAS WE ARE SAYING, NO.</p>
<p begin="00:03:23.070" end="00:03:24.471">STORY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:24.471" end="00:03:24.805">SORRY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:24.805" end="00:03:25.439">I CAN&apos;T DO THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:25.439" end="00:03:27.241">CAN I HAVE A PEPPERONI.</p>
<p begin="00:03:27.241" end="00:03:27.908">&gt;&gt; NO.</p>
<p begin="00:03:27.908" end="00:03:33.180">WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE?  GORDON RANS DAY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:33.180" end="00:03:38.919">THE ONLY TIME SOMEONE AT DOMINO&apos;S SAYS NO TO ME IS IF I JUST WALKED IN AND ASKED, HEY,</p>
<p begin="00:03:38.919" end="00:03:50.397">CAN I TAKE A DUMP IN YOUR SINK?  SHORT OF THAT, THE ANSWER IS YES, SIR!  THIS IS AMERICA.</p>
<p begin="00:03:50.397" end="00:03:56.603">AND THERE IS ONLY ONE THING IN THIS COUNTRY THAT IS MADE IN SMALL BATCHES, THE TRADITIONAL </p>
<p begin="00:03:56.603" end="00:04:09.383">WAY, AND DESERVES TO BE CALLED ARTISMAL, AND THAT IS OUR -- HAND CRAFTED.</p>
<p begin="00:04:09.383" end="00:04:19.860">HAND CRAFTED IN A SINGLE BATHTUB, USING ONLY THE FINEST DRANO, THE WAY GRANDMA USED TO MAKE IT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:19.860" end="00:04:20.127">JON.</p>
<p begin="00:04:20.127" end="00:04:22.062">&gt;&gt; Stewart: THANK YOU, LOUIS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:22.062" end="00:04:23.130">WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
