<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:09.276" end="00:00:17.417">&gt;&gt; Jon: RIGHT BEFORE MITT ROMNEY&apos;S SUCCESSION SPEECH CONVENTIONEERS WILL AS ALWAYS BE </p>
<p begin="00:00:17.417" end="00:00:21.255">EXPOSED I MEAN TREATED TO A BRIEF BIOGRAPHICAL FILM ABOUT THE NOMINEE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:21.255" end="00:00:22.689">YOU MAY NOT HAVE SEEN IT,</p>
<p begin="00:00:22.689" end="00:00:24.558">LUCKILY WE HAVE RECEIVED IT,</p>
<p begin="00:00:24.558" end="00:00:29.229">RECEIVED AN ADVANCED COPY OF SAID FILM AND AS A PUBLIC SERVICE WE WOULD LIKE TO SHOW </p>
<p begin="00:00:29.229" end="00:00:32.165">YOU MITT ROMNEY&apos;S BIOGRAPHICAL FILM SHOWN AT THE CONVENTION.</p>
<p begin="00:00:32.165" end="00:00:39.006">&gt;&gt; THIS YEAR, THE AMERICAN PEOPLE FACE A CHOICE BETWEEN A SELF-MADE BUSINESSMAN.</p>
<p begin="00:00:39.006" end="00:00:42.676">&gt;&gt; I KNOW HOW EXTRAORDINARILY DIFFICULT IT IS TO BUILD SOMETHING FROM NOTHING.</p>
<p begin="00:00:42.676" end="00:00:49.316">&gt;&gt; AND A RADICAL COLLECTIVIST WHO SAYS THINGS LIKE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:49.316" end="00:00:51.485">&gt;&gt; IF YOU HAVE A BUSINESS YOU DIDN&apos;T BUILD THIS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:51.485" end="00:00:53.420">&gt;&gt; I WAS NOT BORN IN THIS COUNTRY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:53.420" end="00:00:54.488">&gt;&gt; AND THE LEADER OF AL QAEDA.</p>
<p begin="00:00:54.488" end="00:01:00.961">&gt;&gt; THIS IS THE STORY OF MITT ROMNEY, A HUMAN BEING WHO BUILT THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:00.961" end="00:01:05.933">&gt;&gt; GEORGE W ROMNEY WAS A WELL WITH THINK AUTO EXECUTIVE AND FUTURE MICHIGAN GOVERNOR, BUT </p>
<p begin="00:01:05.933" end="00:01:09.369">BEING BORN HIS SON WAS ANYTHING BUT LUCK.</p>
<p begin="00:01:09.369" end="00:01:15.709">LITTLE MITT ROMNEY WON THE COVETED POSITION ONLY BY OUTCOMPETING THOUSANDS OF LESS MOTIVATED SPERM.</p>
<p begin="00:01:15.709" end="00:01:20.113">AND THOUGH WHEN HE WAS A TEENAGER THE ROMNEY FAMILY WAS FOR A TIME FORCED TO TAKE </p>
<p begin="00:01:20.113" end="00:01:27.788">SHELTER IN PUBLIC HOUSING, YOUNG MITT REFUSED ON PRINCE BILLION TO TAKE TAXPAYER MONEY FOR HIS </p>
<p begin="00:01:27.788" end="00:01:33.327">SCHOOLING, INSTEAD CONVINCE AGO LOCAL BUSINESSMAN TO INVEST IN HIS FUTURE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:33.327" end="00:01:36.964">AND THEN THE VIETNAM.</p>
<p begin="00:01:36.964" end="00:01:42.469">ROMNEY VOLUNTEERED TO SERVE IN FRANCE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:42.469" end="00:01:46.940">A MORMON MISSIONARY BRAVELY FIGHTING THE FRENCH PEOPLE&apos;S LOVE OF WINE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:46.940" end="00:01:48.442">&gt;&gt; IT WAS A QUAGMIRE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:48.442" end="00:01:55.148">SOMETIMES AT NIGHT HE FEELS HE IS STILL THERE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:55.148" end="00:02:02.923">&gt;&gt; BACK STATESIDE, THE HANDSOME CONNECTED YOUNG MAN BUCKS THE ODDS, FEIGNING ADMISSION TO </p>
<p begin="00:02:02.923" end="00:02:08.729">HARVARD, RENICING ON PRINCIPLE TO GO TO SCHOOL WITH TAXPAYER MONEY INSTEAD WITH HIS OWN HARD </p>
<p begin="00:02:08.729" end="00:02:13.800">EARNED STOCK GIVEN TO HIM BY A LOCAL BUSINESSMAN.</p>
<p begin="00:02:13.800" end="00:02:21.441">HER NAME WAS ANN DAVIS AND THE MOMENT MITT SAW HER HE KNEW HE WAS TOTALLY GOING TO BUILD THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:21.441" end="00:02:25.646">SHE WAS THE IDEAL GENDER, FOR A WIFE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:25.646" end="00:02:30.851">THEY WED ACCORDING TO HUMAN CUSTOM AND THEN MESHING THEIR PRIVATE SECTORS PRODUCED FIVE </p>
<p begin="00:02:30.851" end="00:02:34.321">MALE OFFSPRING, TAG, CRAIG,</p>
<p begin="00:02:34.321" end="00:02:38.192">BLIG, MARBLE AND FLAPJACK.</p>
<p begin="00:02:38.192" end="00:02:46.133">&gt;&gt; ARMED ONLY WITH IVY LEAGUE BUSINESS AND LAW DEGREES, AND THE MITT ROMNEY TRAILED BLAZES </p>
<p begin="00:02:46.133" end="00:02:52.940">HIS WAY TO A PIONEERING NEW BOSTON FIRM, WHERE HE LEARNED HOW TO SECRETE MONEY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:52.940" end="00:02:59.713">FROM THERE, IT WAS A SERIES OF PERSONAL TRIUMPHS, FROM SINGLE-HANDEDLY SAVING 2002 SALT </p>
<p begin="00:02:59.713" end="00:03:04.952">LAKE OLYMPICS TO ELECTING HIMSELF GOVERNOR OF MASSACHUSETTS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:04.952" end="00:03:10.958">BUT THERE IS STILL ONE THING LEFT FOR MITT ROMNEY TO BUILD, A PRESIDENCY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:10.958" end="00:03:17.197">AS THE ELITE EAST COAST HARVARD EDUCATED CREATOR OF ROMNEY CARE STARTED TO RUN, IN THE MOST </p>
<p begin="00:03:17.197" end="00:03:22.236">CONSERVATIVE REPUBLICAN FIELD IN HISTORY, ROMNEY REALIZED THAT TERRIBLE TRUTH.</p>
<p begin="00:03:22.236" end="00:03:26.440">&gt;&gt; I AM SOMEONE WHO IS A MODERATE AND MY VIEWS ARE PROGRESSIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:26.440" end="00:03:28.976">&gt;&gt; I WILL PRESERVE AND PROTECT A WOMEN&apos;S RIGHT TO CHOOSE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:28.976" end="00:03:34.314">&gt;&gt; WE ALSO SHOULD KEEP WEAPONS OF -- TO BE ON THE STREET.</p>
<p begin="00:03:34.314" end="00:03:38.085">&gt;&gt; HE BILLED HIMSELF THE WRONG WAY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:38.085" end="00:03:42.389">IT WOULD TAKE A MONUMENTAL FEAT OF SELF RECONSTRUCTION.</p>
<p begin="00:03:42.389" end="00:03:43.490">&gt;&gt; I AM PRO-LIFE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:43.490" end="00:03:44.992">&gt;&gt; $122 BILLION.</p>
<p begin="00:03:44.992" end="00:03:47.961">&gt;&gt; I DON&apos;T HAPPEN TO BELIEVE THAT AMERICA NEEDS NEW GUN LAWS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:47.961" end="00:03:53.267">&gt;&gt; AROUND THE CLOCK OPERATIONS ACROSS 14 TIME ZONES UNTIL FINALLY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:53.267" end="00:03:57.504">&gt;&gt; I WAS A SEVERELY CONSERVATIVE REPUBLICAN GOVERNOR.</p>
<p begin="00:03:57.504" end="00:04:03.177">&gt;&gt; MITT ROMNEY HAD DONE IT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:03.177" end="00:04:07.848">ALL BY HIMSELF.</p>
<p begin="00:04:07.848" end="00:04:13.954">MITT ROMNEY DID IT ALL BY HIMSELF.</p>
<p begin="00:04:13.954" end="00:04:19.693">MITT ROMNEY, HE IS A HUMAN BEING AND HE BUILT THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:19.693" end="00:04:20.961">&gt;&gt; Jon: WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
