<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:05.372" end="00:00:10.677">&gt;&gt; Jon: WOW!  WOW!  WELCOME BACK!  I&apos;M SORRY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:10.677" end="00:00:13.380">I AM EXHAUSTED.</p>
<p begin="00:00:13.380" end="00:00:17.551">I JUST GAVE MYSELF A LAP DANCE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:17.551" end="00:00:19.853">IT IS NOT AS EASY AS IT SOUNDS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:19.853" end="00:00:24.758">AS YOU MAY KNOW, LAST WEEK BEFORE WE GOT TO TAMPA, THERE WAS A BIT OF AN UPROAR CAUSE BID </p>
<p begin="00:00:24.758" end="00:00:28.362">THE REPUBLICAN SENATE CANDIDATE IN THE GREAT STATE OF MISSOURI,</p>
<p begin="00:00:28.362" end="00:00:33.667">AN INTERESTING POSITION ON THE QUESTION OF PREGNANCIES RESULTING FROM RAPE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:33.667" end="00:00:38.805">&gt;&gt; FIRST OF ALL, AT THAT WHAT I UNDERSTAND FROM DOCTORS THAT IS REALLY RARE, IF IT IS A </p>
<p begin="00:00:38.805" end="00:00:45.379">LEGITIMATE RAPE, THE FEMALE BODY HAS WAYS TO TRY TO SHUT THAT WHOLE THING DOWN.</p>
<p begin="00:00:45.379" end="00:00:46.413">&gt;&gt; Jon: STOP IT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:46.413" end="00:00:49.183">THAT IS SCIENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:49.183" end="00:00:52.352">&gt;&gt; IT IS SO TRUE, THE FEMALE BODY IS AMAZING.</p>
<p begin="00:00:52.352" end="00:01:00.294">DID YOU KNOW THAT THE HUMAN VAGINA -- BESIDES BEING ABLE TO REPEL RAPE SPERM IS ALSO, CAN BE </p>
<p begin="00:01:00.294" end="00:01:04.131">USED AS A WIFI HOT SPOT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:04.131" end="00:01:12.539">AND FROM WHAT I UNDERSTAND, CAN DETECT RADON AND CARBON MONOXIDE KNOCKS SIDE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:12.539" end="00:01:20.948">AND CONVERT STANDARD DVDS TO BLU-RAYS AND .. IF YOU ARE IN A CAR CHASE, CAN SHOOT OUT TACKS </p>
<p begin="00:01:20.948" end="00:01:23.684">OR AN OIL SLICK.</p>
<p begin="00:01:23.684" end="00:01:27.855">TO THROW OFF YOUR PURSUERS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:27.855" end="00:01:30.090">THE VAGINA.</p>
<p begin="00:01:30.090" end="00:01:33.093">THE MORE YOU KNOW.</p>
<p begin="00:01:33.093" end="00:01:48.208">SO YOU CAN SEE WHY THIS REMARK -- YOU CAN SEE WHY THIS REMARK COMING FROM A MAN WHO SITS ON </p>
<p begin="00:01:48.208" end="00:01:53.814">THE HOUSE SCIENCE COMMITTEE CAN BE QUITE A STORY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:53.814" end="00:01:55.916">BUT GUESS WHAT THE REAL STORY IS?</p>
<p begin="00:01:55.916" end="00:02:00.754">&gt;&gt; WITH THE MEDIA REFUSING TO LET THIS STORY GO, HOW DOES THE MITT ROMNEY CAMPAIGN GET HIS </p>
<p begin="00:02:00.754" end="00:02:01.488">MESSAGES OUT THERE?</p>
<p begin="00:02:01.488" end="00:02:04.791">&gt;&gt; THE MEDIA HAVE A REPUBLICAN IN THEIR CROSS HAIRS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:04.791" end="00:02:07.261">&gt;&gt; LIBERAL MEDIA WON&apos;T TALK ABOUT NOTHING ELSE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:07.261" end="00:02:12.266">&gt;&gt; LAST NIGHT HE SENT OUT A SERIES OF TWEETS, HE SAID AND I QUOTE, I APOLOGIZE FOR THE </p>
<p begin="00:02:12.266" end="00:02:14.468">LIBERAL MEDIA IS TRYING TO MAKE ME DROP OUT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:14.468" end="00:02:22.543">&gt;&gt; Jon: OH!  IF ONLY THAT POOR MAN HAD ONE OF THOSE MAGIC VAGINAS TO PROTECT HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:02:22.543" end="00:02:33.120">HE COULD HAVE REPELLED THE MEDIA!  WHY WOULD THE MEDIA PILE ON THIS POOR MAN LIKE THIS?</p>
<p begin="00:02:33.120" end="00:02:39.826">&gt;&gt; THE MEDIA HAS A LOVE AFFAIR WITH BARACK OBAMA AND THE PRESS OFFICE OF THE OBAMA REELECTION </p>
<p begin="00:02:39.826" end="00:02:41.595">CAMPAIGN, KNOWN AS NBC NEWS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:41.595" end="00:02:45.566">YOU WATCH ALL OF THOSE COMEDY CENTRAL SHOWS, THEY ARE IN THE TANK FOR BARACK OBAMA.</p>
<p begin="00:02:45.566" end="00:02:55.976">&gt;&gt; Jon: WHAT?  WORK HOLICS AND THE NEW SERIES FICKLE BERRY PREMIERING SEPTEMBER 25TH ARE IN </p>
<p begin="00:02:55.976" end="00:02:57.444">THE TANK FOR OBAMA?  I CAN&apos;T -- </p>
<p begin="00:02:57.444" end="00:03:01.515">&gt;&gt; OH!</p>
<p begin="00:03:01.515" end="00:03:07.921">&gt;&gt; Jon: COLBERT!  ..</p>
<p begin="00:03:07.921" end="00:03:10.290">&gt;&gt; I CAN&apos;T BELIEVE THIS GUY IS IN THE TANK.</p>
<p begin="00:03:10.290" end="00:03:12.426">LOOK, I WILL TELL YOU THIS, I DON&apos;T WANT TO BE IN THE TANK.</p>
<p begin="00:03:12.426" end="00:03:15.062">THE TANK IS WHERE FISH POOP IS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:15.062" end="00:03:16.063">I DON&apos;T WANT TO BE IN THERE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:16.063" end="00:03:19.233">I JUST WANT TO HAVE A FAIR CONVERSATION ABOUT SOME OF THE THINGS THAT SEEM RELEVANT TO </p>
<p begin="00:03:19.233" end="00:03:20.734">THIS ELECTION.</p>
<p begin="00:03:20.734" end="00:03:24.438">THE ISSUE, ROMNEY IS RUNNING ON HIS BUSINESS EXPERIENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:24.438" end="00:03:26.373">LET&apos;S TALK ABOUT HIS EXPERIENCE IN BAIN CAPITAL.</p>
<p begin="00:03:26.373" end="00:03:32.546">&gt;&gt; GOING AFTER MITT ROMNEY&apos;S RECORD AS A BUSINESSMAN ARE NOT </p>
<p begin="00:03:32.546" end="00:03:35.782">THINGS THAT THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ARE CONCERNED WITH.</p>
<p begin="00:03:35.782" end="00:03:37.818">&gt;&gt; Jon: THEY DON&apos;T WANT TO HEAR ABOUT HIS BUSINESS RECORD,</p>
<p begin="00:03:37.818" end="00:03:38.719">THAT&apos;S FINE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:38.719" end="00:03:42.523">ALTHOUGH HERE IS A PROBLEM IF WE ONLY TALK ABOUT THINGS AMERICAN PEOPLE ARE CONCERNED WITH THEN </p>
<p begin="00:03:42.523" end="00:03:48.996">THE WHOLE CAMPAIGN WOULD BE ABOUT HOARDERS AND TODDLER BEAUTY PAGEANTS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:48.996" end="00:03:51.164">&gt;&gt; </p>
<p begin="00:03:51.164" end="00:03:59.106">&gt;&gt; Jon: LOOK, MITT ROMNEY, I GET IT, ALL YOU ARE ASKING IS FOR YOU TO MAKE YOU THE MOST,</p>
<p begin="00:03:59.106" end="00:04:04.545">THE WORLD&apos;S MOST POWERFUL HUMAN BEING, WHAT ELSE SHOULD WE NOT TALK ABOUT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:04.545" end="00:04:06.613">&gt;&gt; BUSINESS OR FAMILY OR TAXES,</p>
<p begin="00:04:06.613" end="00:04:10.450">THINGS OF THIS NATURE, THIS IS -- A DIVERSION.</p>
<p begin="00:04:10.450" end="00:04:11.752">&gt;&gt; Jon: I SEE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:11.752" end="00:04:16.890">SO WHILE TYPICALLY THOSE WOULD BE THE THREE CRITERION THAT ARE EXAMINED, JOB INTERVIEW FOR THE </p>
<p begin="00:04:16.890" end="00:04:18.258">PRESIDENCY, BUT, ALL RIGHT,</p>
<p begin="00:04:18.258" end="00:04:23.630">PERHAPS YOU WOULD PREFER TO STICK TO SOME BASIC HEIGHT AND WEIGHT, SQUARENESS OF JAW LINE,</p>
<p begin="00:04:23.630" end="00:04:28.335">YOU KNOW, JC PENNEY MODEL CRITERIA, WE ALREADY KNOW YOU WON&apos;T GIVE SPECIFICS ON WHICH </p>
<p begin="00:04:28.335" end="00:04:34.975">PROGRAMS YOU CUT.  I DON&apos;T WANT TO BE IN THE TANK, BUT WOULD YOU LIKE TO VOLUNTEER SOME </p>
<p begin="00:04:34.975" end="00:04:36.844">INFORMATION FOR US?</p>
<p begin="00:04:36.844" end="00:04:41.148">&gt;&gt; TELL US SOMETHING THAT WE MAY NOT KNOW ABOUT THE GOVERNOR.</p>
<p begin="00:04:41.148" end="00:04:44.952">&gt;&gt; WELL, I THINK PEOPLE DON&apos;T APPRECIATE ACTUALLY HIS SENSE OF HUMOR.</p>
<p begin="00:04:44.952" end="00:04:45.752">&gt;&gt; IS SHE RIGHT?</p>
<p begin="00:04:45.752" end="00:04:46.987">&gt;&gt; YEAH, YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:04:46.987" end="00:05:01.134">I MEAN, YOU KNOW, I LIVE FOR LAUGHTER.</p>
<p begin="00:05:01.134" end="00:05:02.503">&gt;&gt; Jon: NOW, WE ARE COOKING.</p>
<p begin="00:05:02.503" end="00:05:05.038">NOW WE GOT SOMETHING.</p>
<p begin="00:05:05.038" end="00:05:05.806">I TOO -- ALL RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:05.806" end="00:05:07.474">HIT ME WITH SOME OF YOUR BEST STUFF.</p>
<p begin="00:05:07.474" end="00:05:10.444">&gt;&gt; NO ONE EVER ASKED TO SEE MY BIRTH CERTIFICATE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:10.444" end="00:05:19.953">THEY KNOW THIS IS THE PLACE WE WERE BORN AND RAISED.</p>
<p begin="00:05:19.953" end="00:05:23.724">&gt;&gt; Jon: HE WAS BORN IN AMERICA, IN MICHIGAN.</p>
<p begin="00:05:23.724" end="00:05:28.795">HE NEVER HAS BEEN -- OH.</p>
<p begin="00:05:28.795" end="00:05:31.665">I GOT A BETTER ONE ABOUT MICHIGAN.</p>
<p begin="00:05:31.665" end="00:05:33.467">WHY DOES MICHIGAN MAKE SO MANY CARS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:33.467" end="00:05:35.602">SO THEY CAN GET THE (BLEEP) OUT OF MICHIGA </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
