<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:04.438" end="00:00:05.172"> <span tts:color="#ffff00">Captioning sponsored by</span> </p>
<p begin="00:00:05.172" end="00:00:08.008"> <span tts:color="#ffff00">COMEDY CENTRAL</span> FEBRUARY 15, 2012.</p>
<p begin="00:00:08.008" end="00:00:09.443">FROM COMEDY CENTRAL&apos;S WORLD NEWS HEADQUARTERS IN NEW YORK, THIS </p>
<p begin="00:00:09.443" end="00:00:14.982">IS &quot;THE DAILY SHOW&quot; WITH JON STEWART.</p>
<p begin="00:00:14.982" end="00:00:27.127">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) </p>
<p begin="00:00:27.127" end="00:00:29.963">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELCOME TO &quot;THE DAILY SHOW.&quot; MY NAME IS JON STEWART.</p>
<p begin="00:00:29.963" end="00:00:35.035">MY GUEST TONIGHT REPRESENTATIVE LOUISE SLAUGHTER WILL BE HERE VIA SATELLITE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:35.035" end="00:00:35.435">SATELLITE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:35.435" end="00:00:36.670">THAT&apos;S RIGHT, SPACE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:36.670" end="00:00:38.539">(LAUGHTER) OOH.</p>
<p begin="00:00:38.539" end="00:00:44.545">HAPPY OH MY GOD YESTERDAY WAS VALENTINE&apos;S DAY (BLEEP).</p>
<p begin="00:00:44.545" end="00:00:47.748">(LAUGHTER) THAT&apos;S THE DAY WHEN YOU REMEMBER THAT YESTERDAY WAS VALENTINE&apos;S DAY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:47.748" end="00:00:51.151">AND NOW YOU&apos;RE ALONE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:51.151" end="00:00:53.754">(LAUGHTER) LET&apos;S BEGIN TONIGHT WITH THE STATE OF OUR CAPITAL MARKET.</p>
<p begin="00:00:53.754" end="00:00:58.225">I KNOW YOU&apos;VE BEEN GETTING A LOT OF REQUESTS ON THE SHOW TO DO MORE CAPITAL MARKETS BITS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:58.225" end="00:01:00.661">THEY&apos;VE BEEN THROUGH A BIT OF A ROUGH PATCH.</p>
<p begin="00:01:00.661" end="00:01:01.595">REPUTATIONS HAVE SUFFERED.</p>
<p begin="00:01:01.595" end="00:01:04.431">NOT LEAST OF WHICH DUE TO A RASH OF INSIDER TRADING.</p>
<p begin="00:01:04.431" end="00:01:06.433">WE KNOW INSIDER TRADING IS BAD.</p>
<p begin="00:01:06.433" end="00:01:12.072">WHY ELSE WOULD JOHN CRYER&apos;S DEAD BROTHER HAVE GONE TO JAIL IN THAT &apos;80s MOVIE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:12.072" end="00:01:13.907">YOU KNOW, THE MOVIE ABOUT...</p>
<p begin="00:01:13.907" end="00:01:14.508">WALL STREET.</p>
<p begin="00:01:14.508" end="00:01:16.076">I CAN&apos;T REMEMBER THE NAME OF THAT MOVIE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:16.076" end="00:01:16.810">BUT WHATEVER IT WAS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:16.810" end="00:01:19.446">IT HAPPENS ALL THE TIME AND IT WAS NOT TOLERATED.</p>
<p begin="00:01:19.446" end="00:01:22.716">&gt;&gt; GOLDMAN SACHS TECHNOLOGY ANALYST IS REPORTED UNDER INVESTIGATION BY FEDERAL </p>
<p begin="00:01:22.716" end="00:01:25.118">AUTHORITIES FOR LEAKING INSIDE INFORMATION TO HEDGE FUNDS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:25.118" end="00:01:27.221">&gt;&gt; Jon: GOOD!</p>
<p begin="00:01:27.221" end="00:01:28.288">(LAUGHTER) I&apos;M GLAD.</p>
<p begin="00:01:28.288" end="00:01:31.191">NOT THAT HE&apos;S LEAKING.</p>
<p begin="00:01:31.191" end="00:01:35.095">(LAUGHTER) I&apos;M GLAD THAT PEOPLE TRADING ON SECRET INFORMATION WHICH </p>
<p begin="00:01:35.095" end="00:01:37.497">UNDERMINES THE VERY INTEGRITY OF OUR MARKETS IS A PROBLEM.</p>
<p begin="00:01:37.497" end="00:01:43.337">YOU TRADE ON NONPUBLIC INFORMATION, YOU GET IN TROUBLE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:43.337" end="00:01:45.639">THAT&apos;S SOMETHING THE GOVERNMENT SHOULD INVESTIGATE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:45.639" end="00:01:48.308">UNLESS THEY&apos;RE DOING IT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:48.308" end="00:01:50.511">FOR EXAMPLE, INSIDER TRADING ON THE STOCK MARKET.</p>
<p begin="00:01:50.511" end="00:01:51.812">IF YOU ARE A MEMBER OF CONGRESS,</p>
<p begin="00:01:51.812" end="00:01:55.115">THOSE LAWS ARE DEEMED NOT TO APPLY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:55.115" end="00:02:00.721">THERE ARE ALL SORTS OF FORMS OF HONEST GRAFTS THAT CONGRESSMEN ENGAGE IN THAT ALLOW THEM TO </p>
<p begin="00:02:00.721" end="00:02:02.422">BECOME VERY, VERY WEALTHY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:02.422" end="00:02:05.826">&gt;&gt; Jon: JUST LIKE THE FOUNDING FATHERS INTENDED.</p>
<p begin="00:02:05.826" end="00:02:08.061">(LAUGHTER) IT&apos;S OUR SYSTEM OF CHECKS AND BALANCES.</p>
<p begin="00:02:08.061" end="00:02:14.501">THEY T DEPOSIT CHECKS, IT INCREASES THEIR BALANCES.</p>
<p begin="00:02:14.501" end="00:02:22.509">(LAUGHTER) LOOK, CONGRESSIONAL TRADING ON NONPUBLIC INFORMATION IS SURPRISINGLY COMMON.</p>
<p begin="00:02:22.509" end="00:02:27.614">&quot;60 MINUTES&quot; REPORTED IN NOVEMBER FINANCIAL SERVICES COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN SPENCER </p>
<p begin="00:02:27.614" end="00:02:31.485">BACHUS MADE INVESTMENTS AFTER CLOSED-DOOR BRIEFINGS ON THE ECONOMY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:31.485" end="00:02:34.454">JOHN BOEHNER DABBLED IN INSURANCE STOCKS DURING THE HEALTH CARE DEBATE AND NANCY </p>
<p begin="00:02:34.454" end="00:02:40.861">PELOSI TOOK PART IN AN EXCLUSIVE VISA I.P.O. WHILE CONSIDERING LEGISLATION ON CREDIT CARDS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:40.861" end="00:02:49.102">AND SEVERAL MEMBERS OF THE HOUSE ITTY-BITTY TITTY COMMITTEE ARE SHORTING THE OVER THE SHOULDER </p>
<p begin="00:02:49.102" end="00:02:53.807">BOLDER HOLDER MARKET AND HOW IS THAT NOT ILLEGAL AND HOW DID I STAY THAT WITHOUT TRIPPING UP ON </p>
<p begin="00:02:53.807" end="00:02:54.875">THE WORDS?</p>
<p begin="00:02:54.875" end="00:02:55.609">I DON&apos;T KNOW.</p>
<p begin="00:02:55.609" end="00:02:59.847">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) REALLY?</p>
<p begin="00:02:59.847" end="00:03:02.583">ARE YOUR STANDARDS FOR ME THAT LOW?</p>
<p begin="00:03:02.583" end="00:03:06.053">(LAUGHTER) THIS GENTLEMAN GOT THROUGH ITTY-BITTY TITTY COMMITTEE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:06.053" end="00:03:10.424">I SAY WE CARRY HIM OUT ON OUR SHOULDERS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:10.424" end="00:03:13.360">LOOK, THE REPORT ON &quot;60 MINUTES&quot; MADE SOME REAL WAVES ON CAPITOL HILL.</p>
<p begin="00:03:13.360" end="00:03:15.429">MEMBERS VOWED ACTION.</p>
<p begin="00:03:15.429" end="00:03:20.067">WE MUST MAKE IT UNAMBIGUOUS THAT THIS KIND OF BEHAVIOR IS ILLEGAL.</p>
<p begin="00:03:20.067" end="00:03:27.174">&gt;&gt; WE SHOULD NOT BE SHIELDING CONGRESS FROM LAWS THAT APPLY TO OTHER AMERICANS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:27.174" end="00:03:30.177">&gt;&gt; Jon: YES!</p>
<p begin="00:03:30.177" end="00:03:33.347">CONGRESS SHOULD OBEY THE SAME LAWS AS EVERYONE ELSE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:33.347" end="00:03:39.486">I BELIEVE THAT WAS IN THE NO (BLEEP) SHERLOCK ACT OF 2000 AND ALWAYS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:39.486" end="00:03:43.590">THAT&apos;S WHY LAST THURSDAY CONGRESS PASSED SOMETHING CALLED THE STOP TRADING ON </p>
<p begin="00:03:43.590" end="00:03:47.194">CONGRESSIONAL KNOWLEDGE, OR STOCK ACT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:47.194" end="00:03:49.096">IT&apos;S AN ACRONYM.</p>
<p begin="00:03:49.096" end="00:03:53.133">IT WAS DESIGNED TO PREVENT CONGRESS PEOPLE OR THEIR STAFF FROM BENEFITING FINANCIALLY FROM </p>
<p begin="00:03:53.133" end="00:03:55.736">INFORMATION THEY LEARNED IN THE COURSE OF BEING IN CONGRESS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:55.736" end="00:03:59.940">SO NOW AT LONG LAST IF YOU&apos;RE ON THE SENATE BANKING COMMITTEE YOU </p>
<p begin="00:03:59.940" end="00:04:01.775">CAN&apos;T TRADE BANK STOCKS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:01.775" end="00:04:04.845">&gt;&gt; IF YOU&apos;RE ON THE SENATE BANKING COMMITTEE, YOU&apos;RE GOING </p>
<p begin="00:04:04.845" end="00:04:08.615">TO STILL BE ABLE TO TRADE BANK STOCK.</p>
<p begin="00:04:08.615" end="00:04:10.784">(AUDIENCE REACTS).</p>
<p begin="00:04:10.784" end="00:04:13.487">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:04:13.487" end="00:04:16.156">&gt;&gt; Jon: THAT SEEMS TO NOT BE SOLVING THE PROBLEM THEN.</p>
<p begin="00:04:16.156" end="00:04:21.061">BUT TO FULLY APPRECIATE THE SIZE OF CONGRESS&apos; BALL AND THE BILL&apos;S </p>
<p begin="00:04:21.061" end="00:04:27.067">LACK OF THEM YOU&apos;VE GOT TO LOOK AT ANOTHER PROVISION DEALING WITH SO-CALLED POLITICAL INTELLIGENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:27.067" end="00:04:29.636">I&apos;LL LET &quot;60 MINUTES&quot; EXPLAIN USING FOOTAGE OF PEOPLE WHOSE </p>
<p begin="00:04:29.636" end="00:04:31.572">FACES HAVE BEEN SURGICALLY REMOVED.</p>
<p begin="00:04:31.572" end="00:04:36.076">&gt;&gt; A WHOLE NEW TOTALLY UNREGULATED $100 MILLION INDUSTRY HAS GROWN UP IN </p>
<p begin="00:04:36.076" end="00:04:37.644">WASHINGTON CALLED POLITICAL INTELLIGENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:37.644" end="00:04:43.383">IT EMPLOYS FORMER CONGRESSMEN AND FORMER STAFFERS TO SCOUR THE HALLS OF THE CAPITOL GATHERING </p>
<p begin="00:04:43.383" end="00:04:47.321">VALUABLE NONPUBLIC INFORMATION THEN SELLING IT TO HEDGE FUNDS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:47.321" end="00:04:51.124">&gt;&gt; Jon: HEADLESS ZOMBIES!</p>
<p begin="00:04:51.124" end="00:04:52.092">ROAMING THE HALLS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:52.092" end="00:04:56.096">THERE&apos;S A WHOLE INDUSTRY OF PARASITES JUST RIDING ON THE BACKS OF OUR CONGRESS PEOPLE </p>
<p begin="00:04:56.096" end="00:05:02.269">LIKE TICKS ON A WATER BUFFALO OR MICE ON AN EAGLE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:02.269" end="00:05:12.145">(LAUGHTER) I&apos;M BEING TOLD THAT WAS NOT HOW MICE GET AROUND.</p>
<p begin="00:05:12.145" end="00:05:13.480">HERE&apos;S AN EXAMPLE AT WORK.</p>
<p begin="00:05:13.480" end="00:05:18.752">A FIRM CALLED J.N.K. SECURITIES SET UP A MEETING BETWEEN SEVERAL HEDGE FUNDS AND SENATOR CHRIS </p>
<p begin="00:05:18.752" end="00:05:21.054">DODD, THE GUY THAT WROTE ALL THE FINANCIAL LEGISLATION.</p>
<p begin="00:05:21.054" end="00:05:25.726">THE SENATOR TOLD THEM HE WOULDN&apos;T BE PURSUING A PRO VISION TO CAP DEBIT CARD FEES.</p>
<p begin="00:05:25.726" end="00:05:28.595">NO ONE OUTSIDE THE MEETING HAS THE INFORMATION.</p>
<p begin="00:05:28.595" end="00:05:33.834">THEN ONE OF THE HEDGE FUNDS THAT WAS THERE BOUGHT OVER 300,000 SHARES IN VISA.</p>
<p begin="00:05:33.834" end="00:05:38.238">HERE&apos;S WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE IF THE SAME TYPE OF ACTIVITY HAPPENS IN THE REGULAR NON-CONGRESS ECONOMY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:38.238" end="00:05:43.677">&gt;&gt; PRIMARY GLOBAL SALES MANAGER JAMES FLEISCHMAN GUILTY OF CONSPIRACY IN AN INSIDER TRADING CASE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:43.677" end="00:05:48.815">&gt;&gt; SECURITIES AND EXCHANGE COMMISSION FILED SUIT AGAINST ANGLO MA ZILLO, FORMER HEAD OF </p>
<p begin="00:05:48.815" end="00:05:52.419">COUNTRYWIDE MORTGAGE ACCUSING HIM OF INSIDER TRADING AND FRAUD.</p>
<p begin="00:05:52.419" end="00:05:57.291">&gt;&gt; A FORMER MANAGING DIRECTOR OF THE NASDAQ HAS BEEN CHARGED WITH INSIDER TRADING.</p>
<p begin="00:05:57.291" end="00:06:02.029">&gt;&gt; I FORMER GOLDMAN SACHS BOARD MEMBER HAS BEEN CHARGED WITH INSIDER TRADING.</p>
<p begin="00:06:02.029" end="00:06:07.701">&gt;&gt; SENTENCED TO 11 YEARS IN PRISON, THE HARSHEST PUNISHMENT EVER FOR AN INSIDER TRADING CASE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:07.701" end="00:06:12.206">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU KNOW WHO I BET FINDS THE JUXTAPOSITION OF WHAT CONGRESS PEOPLE CAN DO AND </p>
<p begin="00:06:12.206" end="00:06:14.608">REGULAR PEOPLE CAN DO HYSTERICAL?</p>
<p begin="00:06:14.608" end="00:06:15.209">MARTHA STEWART.</p>
<p begin="00:06:15.209" end="00:06:19.746">I BET SHE&apos;S JUST LAUGHING AND LAUGHING AS SHE TAKES A RECLAIMED BARN WOOD BASEBALL </p>
<p begin="00:06:19.746" end="00:06:25.686">FOOT A SHELF FULL OF VASES SHE RAFTD FROM RECYCLED NEW ENGLANDC LOBSTER TRAPS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:25.686" end="00:06:27.120">(LAUGHTER) SHE&apos;S MAD.</p>
<p begin="00:06:27.120" end="00:06:31.124">THE SENATE VERSION OF THE STOCK ACT DEALT WITH THESE POLITICAL INTELLIGENCE PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:31.124" end="00:06:34.561">IT DIDN&apos;T BAN THEM FROM SHUTTLING INFORMATION FROM CONGRESS TO HEDGE FUNDS BUT IT </p>
<p begin="00:06:34.561" end="00:06:36.897">DID REQUIRE THEM TO DO ONE THING.</p>
<p begin="00:06:36.897" end="00:06:42.135">&gt;&gt; IT TAKES THESE PEOPLE THAT YOU CALL POLITICAL INTELLIGENCE PROFESSIONALS AND HAVE THEM </p>
<p begin="00:06:42.135" end="00:06:47.241">REGISTER JUST LIKE EVERY LOBBYIST REGISTERS SO IT&apos;S TOTALLY TRANSPARENT SO WHEN </p>
<p begin="00:06:47.241" end="00:06:52.880">THESE PEOPLE COME AROUND TO GET INFORMATION FROM YOU THAT THEY SELL TO HEDGE FUNDS...</p>
<p begin="00:06:52.880" end="00:06:57.751">&gt;&gt; Jon: OH, MY GOD, THEY&apos;RE GOING TO MAKE THEM REGISTER LIKE LOBBYISTS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:57.751" end="00:07:01.455">NOW THEY&apos;LL NEVER BE ABLE TO GET IN AND SEE CONGRESS PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:01.455" end="00:07:05.459">(LAUGHTER) EXCEPT ALWAYS.</p>
<p begin="00:07:05.459" end="00:07:06.894">BUT IT&apos;S BETTER THAN NOTHING.</p>
<p begin="00:07:06.894" end="00:07:09.796">DOES GIVE IT A LITTLE TRANSPARENCY.</p>
<p begin="00:07:09.796" end="00:07:10.531">WHO COULD OBJECT TO THAT?</p>
<p begin="00:07:10.531" end="00:07:14.868">&gt;&gt; HOUSE REPUBLICANS REJECTED A PROVISION THAT REQUIRES SO-CALLED POLITICAL INTELLIGENCE </p>
<p begin="00:07:14.868" end="00:07:20.240">FIRMS TO REGISTER THE SAME AS LOBBYISTS.</p>
<p begin="00:07:20.240" end="00:07:24.278">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:07:24.278" end="00:07:29.416">&gt;&gt; Jon: THANK YOU FOR TAKING (BLEEP) ON OUR CHESTS.</p>
<p begin="00:07:29.416" end="00:07:34.855">NOW TO BE FAIR THE OPPONENTS OF REGISTERING POLITICAL OPERATIVES HAD A GOOD POINT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:34.855" end="00:07:37.925">&gt;&gt; THINK OF THE WORDING &quot;POLITICAL INTELLIGENCE.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:07:37.925" end="00:07:39.393">THERE&apos;S SO MUCH QUESTION ABOUT WHAT THAT MEANS.</p>
<p begin="00:07:39.393" end="00:07:43.797">&gt;&gt; POLITICAL INTELLIGENCE IS DEFINED AS INFORMATION WHICH IS INTENDED FOR USE IN ANALYZING </p>
<p begin="00:07:43.797" end="00:07:47.167">SECURITIES OR COMMODITY MARKETS OR INFORMING INVESTMENT DECISIONS.</p>
<p begin="00:07:47.167" end="00:07:48.569">BUT WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?</p>
<p begin="00:07:48.569" end="00:07:49.703">&gt;&gt; Jon: WHAT DOES IT MEAN?</p>
<p begin="00:07:49.703" end="00:07:51.405">YOU WROTE THE (BLEEP) THING!</p>
<p begin="00:07:51.405" end="00:07:53.373">WHAT DO YOU MEAN WHAT DOES IT MEAN?</p>
<p begin="00:07:53.373" end="00:07:55.709">YOU WROTE IT!</p>
<p begin="00:07:55.709" end="00:08:01.248">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) REALLY, LIEBERMAN?</p>
<p begin="00:08:01.248" end="00:08:07.054">(AS LIEBERMAN) POLITICAL INTELLIGENCE, ARE THOSE EVEN WORDS?</p>
<p begin="00:08:07.054" end="00:08:15.128">WHEN I SEE THE COLOR BLUE, DO I KNOW YOU&apos;RE SEEING THE SAME COLOR I&apos;M SEEING?</p>
<p begin="00:08:15.128" end="00:08:24.137">I MEAN, WHAT IF CONGRESS IS JUST LIKE THE DREAM OF A SLEEPING BUTTERFLY?</p>
<p begin="00:08:24.137" end="00:08:26.807">(LAUGHTER) YOU WRITE LAWS, NOT POETRY.</p>
<p begin="00:08:26.807" end="00:08:29.476">BUT SUDDENLY SENATORS SOUND LIKE ENGLISH PROFESSORS.</p>
<p begin="00:08:29.476" end="00:08:32.746">WELL, THAT SENTENCE, WHAT DOES IT MEAN TO YOU?</p>
<p begin="00:08:32.746" end="00:08:34.815">(LAUGHTER) HERE&apos;S WHAT I THINK IT MEANS,</p>
<p begin="00:08:34.815" end="00:08:39.920">&quot;PACK YOUR SHUTES, PEOPLES, NO ONE&apos;S FLYING THIS (BLEEP)ING PLANE.&quot; </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
