<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:05.672" end="00:00:09.610">FROM AUSTAN GOOLSBEE, THE OUTGOING CHAIRMAN ON THE COMMITTEE OF ECONOMIC... I DON&apos;T </p>
<p begin="00:00:09.610" end="00:00:11.011">KNOW WHAT YOU CALL IT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:11.011" end="00:00:16.116">SO HERE&apos;S WHERE... SO WE&apos;RE TALKING ABOUT THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO GO OUT AND FOCUS ON </p>
<p begin="00:00:16.116" end="00:00:17.417">MANUFACTURING AND THE GROWTH AGENDA.</p>
<p begin="00:00:17.417" end="00:00:18.819">WE WANT TO GET BACK TO IT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:18.819" end="00:00:22.489">HERE&apos;S WHERE IT FALLS APART FOR SOMEONE LIKE ME.</p>
<p begin="00:00:22.489" end="00:00:30.063">SO THE PRESIDENT SAYS TO US FOR QUITE A WHILE, THE ONLY WAY TO GROW THE ECONOMY IS THE </p>
<p begin="00:00:30.063" end="00:00:34.368">STIMULUS, AND SO WE POUR A TON OF STIMULUS IN, AND HE SAYS,</p>
<p begin="00:00:34.368" end="00:00:35.969">THIS WORKED.</p>
<p begin="00:00:35.969" end="00:00:38.505">WE GREW TWO MILLION... WE DID...</p>
<p begin="00:00:38.505" end="00:00:39.473">THIS STIMULUS IS GREAT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:39.473" end="00:00:41.675">IT&apos;S GOTTEN US BACK ON TRACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:41.675" end="00:00:48.215">SO NOW I AGREE, LET&apos;S CUT EVERYTHING, LIKE ISN&apos;T THAT THE...</p>
<p begin="00:00:48.215" end="00:00:50.884">&gt;&gt; I DON&apos;T THINK THAT&apos;S EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED.</p>
<p begin="00:00:50.884" end="00:00:53.086">IF THE STIMULUS WAS WHAT WORKED,</p>
<p begin="00:00:53.086" end="00:00:57.791">WHY WOULD THE NEXT STEP BE THE OPPOSITE TO THE STIMULUS?</p>
<p begin="00:00:57.791" end="00:01:00.527">&gt;&gt; I WOULD SAY TWO THINGS ABOUT THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:00.527" end="00:01:07.668">ONE, THE DESIGN, THE RECOVERY ACT, WHY WE HAD TO RELY ON THE GOVERNMENT IS THE PRIVATE SECTOR </p>
<p begin="00:01:07.668" end="00:01:09.069">IS IN FREEFALL.</p>
<p begin="00:01:09.069" end="00:01:14.274">YOU COULDN&apos;T SAY, AH, WE&apos;RE GOING TO PASS A TAX CREDIT, TRY TO GET THE PRIVATE SECTOR TO </p>
<p begin="00:01:14.274" end="00:01:19.613">LEAD THE RECOVERY IN THE SPRING OF 2009 EVERYTHING IS GOING DOWN THE TUBES.</p>
<p begin="00:01:19.613" end="00:01:22.082">WE&apos;RE JUST TRYING TO PREVENT A DEPRESSION.</p>
<p begin="00:01:22.082" end="00:01:25.085">&gt;&gt; OKAY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:25.085" end="00:01:30.324">&gt;&gt; NOW, IF YOU LOOK AT THIS DEBT DEAL, WE HAVE TO ADDRESS LONG-RUN FISCAL IMBALANCES IN </p>
<p begin="00:01:30.324" end="00:01:33.427">THE COUNTRY, AND THIS IS A SUBSTANTIAL CUT TO THE DEFICIT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:33.427" end="00:01:34.661">&gt;&gt; Jon: I SAW THE CHART.</p>
<p begin="00:01:34.661" end="00:01:38.131">&gt;&gt; WELL, WE&apos;LL DISAGREE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:38.131" end="00:01:42.703">&gt;&gt; Jon: ARE YOU QUESTIONING MY PARALLELOGRAM?</p>
<p begin="00:01:42.703" end="00:01:44.137">&gt;&gt; I&apos;LL GIVE YOU THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:44.137" end="00:01:47.374">LOOK, $2 TRILLION IS... I DON&apos;T THINK THERE&apos;S EVER BEEN A BIGGER </p>
<p begin="00:01:47.374" end="00:01:50.544">CUT TO THE DEFICIT THAN THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:50.544" end="00:01:54.815">SOMETHING LIKE 1/1,000th OF THE MONEY IS IN THE YEAR 2012,</p>
<p begin="00:01:54.815" end="00:01:56.216">AND THAT&apos;S BY DESIGN.</p>
<p begin="00:01:56.216" end="00:02:02.789">IF YOU&apos;RE GOING TO GO CUT $500 BILLION RIGHT NOW, YOU WOULD LIKELY ADD ANOTHER HEAVY BLOW TO </p>
<p begin="00:02:02.789" end="00:02:05.225">THE ECONOMY, WHICH BECOULDN&apos;T AFFORD.</p>
<p begin="00:02:05.225" end="00:02:10.297">THOUGH I MIGHT ALSO ADD, DESPITE SOME MEMBERS OF THE GOVERNMENT SAYING, WELL, MAYBE A DEFAULT </p>
<p begin="00:02:10.297" end="00:02:14.801">WOULD BE OKAY, IT WOULD-BE -- WOULDN&apos;T HAVE BEEN OKAY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:14.801" end="00:02:17.571">THE TREASURY SENDS OUT 80 MILLION CHECKS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:17.571" end="00:02:20.073">WE WOULD HAVE BEEN...</p>
<p begin="00:02:20.073" end="00:02:24.711">&gt;&gt; Jon: WOULD WE HAVE PAID OUR CREDITORS AND THEN JUST GONE INTO LIKE I GUESS YOU CALL IT </p>
<p begin="00:02:24.711" end="00:02:25.979">THE FETAL POSITION?</p>
<p begin="00:02:25.979" end="00:02:27.648">&gt;&gt; WELL, IT DEPENDS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:27.648" end="00:02:32.352">WHEN THEY SAID WE WOULDN&apos;T DEFAULT AS LONG AS WE PAID THE CHINESE AND PAID THE </p>
<p begin="00:02:32.352" end="00:02:41.228">BONDHOLDERS, TO NOT PAY THE MILITARY IN A WAR, TO NOT PAY SOCIAL SECURITY FOR THE RETIREE </p>
<p begin="00:02:41.228" end="00:02:43.363">RETIREES... YOU&apos;RE DEFAULTING ON THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:43.363" end="00:02:45.866">&gt;&gt; Jon: THEY WEREN&apos;T EVEN TALKING STRATEGY AND INSURGENCY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:45.866" end="00:02:48.235">THEY WERE WONDERING IN AFGHANISTAN, ARE WE GETTING PAID.</p>
<p begin="00:02:48.235" end="00:02:53.440">THEY WERE ASKING ME, AND I DIDN&apos;T BRING MY WALLET.</p>
<p begin="00:02:53.440" end="00:02:53.841">[LAUGHTER]</p>
<p begin="00:02:53.841" end="00:02:57.811">THE THING IS WHAT&apos;S GOOD ABOUT GETTING THIS DEBT SCREELG DISCUSSION OUT OF THE WAY, WE&apos;RE </p>
<p begin="00:02:57.811" end="00:02:59.646">ADDRESSING SOME OF THE LONG-TERM FISCAL CHALLENGES.</p>
<p begin="00:02:59.646" end="00:03:03.684">BUT IT ALLOWS US TO GET BACK TO LET&apos;S STOP PAYING ATTENTION TO </p>
<p begin="00:03:03.684" end="00:03:09.790">WHAT KIND OF EYEBROW CUTTINGS DO THE MEMBERS OF CONGRESS HAVE AND WHAT HAVE YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:03:09.790" end="00:03:14.595">LET&apos;S GET BACK TO THE BUSINESS OF THE COUNTRY, WHICH ARE, AS WE WERE SAYING BEFORE THE BREAK,</p>
<p begin="00:03:14.595" end="00:03:19.933">LOOK, LET&apos;S PASS AN INFRASTRUCTURE BANK WHERE IT TAKES ONLY A LITTLE MONEY FROM </p>
<p begin="00:03:19.933" end="00:03:22.169">THE GOVERNMENT, IT WILL EVERYAGES PRIVATE CAPITAL.</p>
<p begin="00:03:22.169" end="00:03:27.140">WE CAN BUILD OUT THE INFRASTRUCTURE THAT WE NEED TO COMPETE AGAINST OTHER NATIONS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:27.140" end="00:03:29.376">&gt;&gt; Jon: THAT SEEMS PERFECT BECAUSE THAT&apos;S THE ONE PLACE </p>
<p begin="00:03:29.376" end="00:03:32.346">WHERE YOU CAN&apos;T ACTUALLY HIRE,</p>
<p begin="00:03:32.346" end="00:03:35.082">OUTSOURCE CHINESE WORKERS TO COME AND BUILD OUR BRIDGES.</p>
<p begin="00:03:35.082" end="00:03:37.084">WE HAVE TO DO THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:37.084" end="00:03:39.987">&gt;&gt; AND IT&apos;S IMPORTANT IF YOU TALK TO... THIS IS A PLACE WHERE </p>
<p begin="00:03:39.987" end="00:03:42.155">BOTH LABOR AND THE CHAMBER OF COMMERCE AGREE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:42.155" end="00:03:46.126">THEY&apos;RE SAYING, WE NEED MORE ECONOMIC INFRASTRUCTURE IN THE COUNTRY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:46.126" end="00:03:50.764">WE HAVE A PATENT BILL THAT WOULD ALLOW ENTREPRENEURS TO GET...</p>
<p begin="00:03:50.764" end="00:03:52.132">INSTEAD OF WAITING THREE YEARS,</p>
<p begin="00:03:52.132" end="00:03:56.336">WHICH IS HOW LONG IT TAKES ON AVERAGE TO GET A PATENT, WE CAN GET IT DOWN TO ONE YEAR.</p>
<p begin="00:03:56.336" end="00:03:59.873">YOU CAN GET AN ANSWER SO YOU WOULDN&apos;T BE BROKE BEFORE YOU GOT IT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:59.873" end="00:04:01.675">&gt;&gt; Jon: THAT SPEAKS TO A LARGER ISSUE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:01.675" end="00:04:05.045">DOES THE PRESIDENT BELIEVE BUSINESS IS OVERREGULATED?</p>
<p begin="00:04:05.045" end="00:04:10.784">DOES HE THINK WE ARE BUREAUCRATICALLY SO SNAFUED AND ENTANGLED THAT THAT IS THE </p>
<p begin="00:04:10.784" end="00:04:12.786">PROBLEM WITH THE ECONOMY RIGHT NOW?</p>
<p begin="00:04:12.786" end="00:04:15.923">&gt;&gt; AS A GENERAL MATTER, NO.</p>
<p begin="00:04:15.923" end="00:04:20.360">THOUGH THERE CERTAINLY ARE INDIVIDUAL THINGS THAT COULD BE DONE DIFFERENT AND STREAMLINED </p>
<p begin="00:04:20.360" end="00:04:22.729">WHERE, YOU KNOW, THEY HAVE TO SUBMIT PAPER FORMS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:22.729" end="00:04:26.834">THEY CAN&apos;T DO IT ON THE WEB, YOU KNOW, THINGS OF THIS NATURE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:26.834" end="00:04:35.776">BUT THE PRESIDENT SAID FROM WAY BACK WHEN, JUST BEING FOR RULES OF THE ROAD DOESN&apos;T MAKE YOU ANTI-MARKET.</p>
<p begin="00:04:35.776" end="00:04:39.913">WHAT WE SAW IN THE FINANCIAL SYSTEM, WHAT WE SAW IN OIL DRILLING IN THE GULF AND A BUNCH </p>
<p begin="00:04:39.913" end="00:04:45.986">OF PLACES, RIPPING UP THE RULES OF THE ROAD, WE&apos;RE DEVASTATING TWO BUSINESSES.</p>
<p begin="00:04:45.986" end="00:04:50.958">IT WASN&apos;T JUST THAT IT WAS BAD FOR SOCIETY, IT WAS BAD FOR THOSE COMPANIES THAT NOBODY WAS </p>
<p begin="00:04:50.958" end="00:04:55.095">FOLLOWING THE RULES OF THE ROAD BECAUSE WHEN YOU LOSE PUBLIC TRUST, YOU DON&apos;T HAVE IT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:55.095" end="00:05:00.133">&gt;&gt; Jon: I WANT TO THANK YOU FOR ALL THE TIMES YOU&apos;VE COME ON THIS SHOW AND LET ME LIKE </p>
<p begin="00:05:00.133" end="00:05:04.505">BASKETBALL ON AT YOU BECAUSE YOU ARE A PROFESSOR OF ECONOMICS AND YOU KNOW A LOT OF THINGS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:04.505" end="00:05:11.812">AND I HAVE SAT HERE THROUGH NUMEROUS APPEARANCES AND TALKED OUT OF MY ASS, AND YOU HAVE </p>
<p begin="00:05:11.812" end="00:05:12.279">NEVER ONCE...</p>
<p begin="00:05:12.279" end="00:05:13.380">&gt;&gt; THAT&apos;S NOT TRUE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:13.380" end="00:05:14.681">YOU&apos;RE SELLING YOURSELF SHORT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:14.681" end="00:05:18.185">&gt;&gt;JON JON OH, NOW WE&apos;RE BACK TO SHORT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:18.185" end="00:05:22.122">IS THAT IT?</p>
<p begin="00:05:22.122" end="00:05:22.523">[LAUGHTER]</p>
<p begin="00:05:22.523" end="00:05:26.326">YOU ARE, I SWEAR TO GOD, YOU ARE AS GIDDY AS A SCHOOLGIRL.</p>
<p begin="00:05:26.326" end="00:05:29.530">&gt;&gt; PEOPLE FROM CHICAGO, YOU GET THAT IN YOUR BLOODSTREAM.</p>
<p begin="00:05:29.530" end="00:05:33.967">WE&apos;RE LIKE THE SALMON OR SOMETHINGMENT I&apos;M JUMPING OUT OF THE LAKE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:33.967" end="00:05:36.603">I&apos;M HEADED HOME.</p>
<p begin="00:05:36.603" end="00:05:39.806">&gt;&gt; Jon: I&apos;M NOT GOING TO TELL YOU WHAT HAPPENS AFTER THEY GO UPSTREAM.</p>
<p begin="00:05:39.806" end="00:05:41.542">I DON&apos;T WANT TO SPOIL YOUR PARTY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:41.542" end="00:05:43.977">&gt;&gt; THE ATLANTIC SALMON.</p>
<p begin="00:05:43.977" end="00:05:45.913">&gt;&gt; Jon: AUSTAN GOOLSBEE, WE WISH YOU WELL.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
