<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:05.005" end="00:00:07.975">NOW, WHILE THE REPUBLICAN CANDIDATES SPENT YESTERDAY TRYING TO BECOME PRESIDENT,</p>
<p begin="00:00:07.975" end="00:00:14.348">THERE WAS A FELLA WHO WAS THE PRESIDENT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:14.348" end="00:00:14.848">PRESS CONFERENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:14.848" end="00:00:19.786">&gt;&gt; NOW, I UNDERSTAND THERE ARE SOME POLITICAL CONTESTS GOING ON TONIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:19.786" end="00:00:23.757">BUT I THOUGHT I&apos;D START THE DAY OFF BY TAKING A FEW QUESTIONS,</p>
<p begin="00:00:23.757" end="00:00:27.127">WHICH I&apos;M SURE WILL NOT BE POLITICAL IN NATURE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:27.127" end="00:00:32.733">&gt;&gt; Jon: OH, IT APPEARS SUPER TUESDAY JUST BECAME SARCASTIC TUESDAY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:32.733" end="00:00:33.567">[LAUGHTER]</p>
<p begin="00:00:33.567" end="00:00:35.169">A LITTLE CYNICAL THERE, MY FRIEND.</p>
<p begin="00:00:35.169" end="00:00:37.171">GIVE THEM A CHANCE TO ASK WHAT THEY&apos;RE GOING TO ASK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:37.171" end="00:00:41.008">&gt;&gt; YOUR CRITICS WILL SAY ON CAPITOL HILL THAT YOU WANT GAS PRICES TO GO HIGHER BECAUSE YOU </p>
<p begin="00:00:41.008" end="00:00:47.481">HAVE SAID BEFORE THAT WILL WEAN THE AMERICAN PEOPLE OFF FOSSIL FUELS ON TO RENEWBLE FUELS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:47.481" end="00:00:49.583">HOW DO YOU RESPOND TO THAT?</p>
<p begin="00:00:49.583" end="00:00:52.319">&gt;&gt; Jon: I&apos;LL TELL YOU HOW HE&apos;S GOING TO RESPOND.</p>
<p begin="00:00:52.319" end="00:00:55.956">I THINK HE&apos;S GOING TO TAP HIS STRATEGIC DERISION RETURNS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:55.956" end="00:01:00.627">&gt;&gt; ED, FROM A POLITICAL PERSPECTIVE, DO YOU THINK THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES </p>
<p begin="00:01:00.627" end="00:01:03.363">GOING INTO AN ELECTION WANTS GAS PRICES TO GO HIGHER IS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:03.363" end="00:01:07.434">THERE ANYBODY HERE WHO THINKS THAT MAKES A LOT OF SENSE?</p>
<p begin="00:01:07.434" end="00:01:08.869">[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]</p>
<p begin="00:01:08.869" end="00:01:11.972">&gt;&gt; Jon: I&apos;LL TELL YOU WHAT,</p>
<p begin="00:01:11.972" end="00:01:16.376">I&apos;LL TELL YOU, WHAT ED, I&apos;LL ANSWER YOUR QUESTION JUST AS SOON AS I INFLATE THIS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:16.376" end="00:01:22.850">[LAUGHTER]</p>
<p begin="00:01:22.850" end="00:01:27.087">THAT MAY NOT HAVE SEEMED THE MOST PRESIDENTIAL TONE, BUT UNDERSTAND THE DERISION IS BASED </p>
<p begin="00:01:27.087" end="00:01:29.189">ON THE TYPE OF QUESTIONS THAT ARE COMING AT HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:01:29.189" end="00:01:34.561">&gt;&gt; YOUR CRITICS HERE IN THE UNITED STATES, INCLUDING JOHN McCAIN, SAID YOU SHOULD START </p>
<p begin="00:01:34.561" end="00:01:35.095">AIR STRIKES NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:01:35.095" end="00:01:40.100">&gt;&gt; MITT ROMNEY HAS CRITICIZED YOU ON IRAN AND SAID HOPE IS NOT A FOREIGN POLICY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:40.100" end="00:01:44.972">&gt;&gt; MITT ROMNEY ON SUNDAY WENT SO FAR AS TO SAY THAT IF YOU ARE </p>
<p begin="00:01:44.972" end="00:01:47.608">REELECTED, IRAN WILL GET A BOMB AND THE WORLD WILL CHANGE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:47.608" end="00:01:53.113">&gt;&gt; HE ALSO SAID THAT YOU ARE AMERICA&apos;S MOST FECKLESS PRESIDENT SINCE CARTER.</p>
<p begin="00:01:53.113" end="00:01:55.949">WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE TO SAY TO MR. ROMNEY?</p>
<p begin="00:01:55.949" end="00:01:58.685">&gt;&gt; Jon: I&apos;D TELL HIM TO GO FECK HIMSELF.</p>
<p begin="00:01:58.685" end="00:02:00.487">THAT&apos;S WHAT I&apos;D SAY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:00.487" end="00:02:02.389">FECK.</p>
<p begin="00:02:02.389" end="00:02:04.091">FECK HIMSELF.</p>
<p begin="00:02:04.091" end="00:02:10.163">AS USUAL, THE WHITE HOUSE PRESS CORPS WAS PRACTICING WHAT CAN ONLY BE CALLED INSTIGATIVE </p>
<p begin="00:02:10.163" end="00:02:14.701">JOURNALISM, LIKE INVESTIGATIVE JOURNALISM, ONLY INSTEAD OF INVESTIGATING, THEY INSTIGATE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:14.701" end="00:02:19.406">THEY PROD THE PERSON AT THE PODIUM WITH SOMEONE ELSE&apos;S TRASH TALK TO SEE IF THEY CAN GIN UP </p>
<p begin="00:02:19.406" end="00:02:19.907">THE FIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:19.907" end="00:02:22.109">IT&apos;S LIKE A FORTUNE COOKIE GAME,</p>
<p begin="00:02:22.109" end="00:02:28.148">BUT INSTEAD OF ADDING IN BED TO THE END OF EVERY ONE OF THEIR QUESTIONS, YOU JUST HAVE TO ADD,</p>
<p begin="00:02:28.148" end="00:02:29.917">ARE YOU GOING TO TAKE THAT </p>
<p begin="00:02:29.917" end="00:02:30.284">[BLEEPED]?</p>
<p begin="00:02:30.284" end="00:02:30.684">LET&apos;S PLAY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:30.684" end="00:02:36.323">&gt;&gt; ON IRAN, MITT ROMNEY WENT SO FAR TO SAY IF YOU ARE REELECTED,</p>
<p begin="00:02:36.323" end="00:02:38.926">IRAN WILL GET A BOMB AND THE WORLD WILL CHANGE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:38.926" end="00:02:41.094">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU GOING TO TAKE THAT </p>
<p begin="00:02:41.094" end="00:02:41.495">[BLEEPED]?</p>
<p begin="00:02:41.495" end="00:02:46.667">&gt;&gt; DEMOCRATS HAVE SAID THAT REPUBLICANS ON A SIMILAR ISSUE ARE ENGAGED IN A WAR ON WOMEN.</p>
<p begin="00:02:46.667" end="00:02:50.938">SOME TOP REPUBLICANS SAY IT&apos;S MORE LIKE DEMOCRATS ARE ENGAGED </p>
<p begin="00:02:50.938" end="00:02:54.107">IN A WAR FOR THE WOMEN&apos;S VOTE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:54.107" end="00:02:58.779">&gt;&gt; MR. PRESIDENT, MY QUESTION TO YOU IS ARE YOU GOING TO TAKE THAT [BLEEPED]?</p>
<p begin="00:02:58.779" end="00:03:04.852">&gt;&gt; LATINO VOTERS, SOME ARE STILL DISAPPOINTED, OTHERS UPSET ABOUT A PROMISE YOU MADE ON </p>
<p begin="00:03:04.852" end="00:03:06.720">IMMIGRATION REFORM THAT HAS YET TO COME TO PASS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:06.720" end="00:03:12.926">&gt;&gt; I GUESS MY QUESTION TO YOU THEN WOULD BE, VASA TOMAS ESA MIERDA?</p>
<p begin="00:03:12.926" end="00:03:20.100">&gt;&gt; MY QUESTION IS ABOUT THE SWITCH FROM THE G-8 SUMMIT FROM CAMP DAVID TO WASHINGTON.</p>
<p begin="00:03:20.100" end="00:03:26.373">THE REASON IS NOW YOU WANTED A MORE INTIMATE SUMMIT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:26.373" end="00:03:26.773">[LAUGHTER]</p>
<p begin="00:03:26.773" end="00:03:27.975">&gt;&gt; Jon: IN BED.</p>
<p begin="00:03:27.975" end="00:03:32.546">SOME STILL WORK WITH &quot;IN BED.&quot; IT&apos;S NOT LIKE THERE WASN&apos;T </p>
<p begin="00:03:32.546" end="00:03:37.484">PLENTY OF NON-HEARSAY NEWS FOR THE MEDIA TO ASK ABOUT JUST FROM THE PREVIOUS 24 HOURS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:37.484" end="00:03:42.656">&gt;&gt; ATTORNEY GENERAL ERIC HOLDER SAYS THAT THE U.S. CAN LEGALLY TARGET AND KILL AMERICAN </p>
<p begin="00:03:42.656" end="00:03:46.093">CITIZENS OVERSEAS IF THEY&apos;RE TIED TO TERRORISM.</p>
<p begin="00:03:46.093" end="00:03:48.896">&gt;&gt; HOLDER SAYS DEW POINT DOESN&apos;T MEAN JUDICIAL PROCESS,</p>
<p begin="00:03:48.896" end="00:03:52.132">ESPECIALLY WHEN IT COMES TO NATIONAL SECURITY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:52.132" end="00:03:54.868">&gt;&gt; Jon: WHAT, DID... HUH?</p>
<p begin="00:03:54.868" end="00:04:00.040">RIGHT THERE HE SAID &quot;DEW POINT DOESN&apos;T MEAN JUDICIAL PROCESS.&quot; ALL RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:00.040" end="00:04:05.245">DEW POINT -- DUE PROCESS DOES NOT MEAN WHAT YOU THINK.</p>
<p begin="00:04:05.245" end="00:04:07.714">HOW COME NO ONE AT THE PRESS CONFERENCE BROUGHT THAT UP,</p>
<p begin="00:04:07.714" end="00:04:09.116">DIDN&apos;T EVEN SAY A WORD ABOUT IT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:09.116" end="00:04:13.820">IF THERE WERE ONLY SOME WAY TO GET THE PRESS CORPS INTERESTED IN SOMETHING... HEY, MEDIA YOUR </p>
<p begin="00:04:13.820" end="00:04:17.624">CRITICS SAY THAT YOUR FIRST PRESIDENTIAL PRESS CONFERENCE IN THREE MONTHS YOU DIDN&apos;T SAY </p>
<p begin="00:04:17.624" end="00:04:21.361">ANYTHING ABOUT AN HISTORICALLY MASSIVE EXECUTIVE BRANCH POWER GRAB.</p>
<p begin="00:04:21.361" end="00:04:23.597">YOU GOING TO TAKE THAT </p>
<p begin="00:04:23.597" end="00:04:24.698">[BLEEPED]?</p>
<p begin="00:04:24.698" end="00:04:25.265">[LAUGHTER]</p>
<p begin="00:04:25.265" end="00:04:26.200">WE&apos;LL BE RIGHT BACK.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
