<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:01.435" end="00:00:06.240"> <span tts:fontStyle="italic">( CHEERS AND APPLAUSE )</span> </p>
<p begin="00:00:06.240" end="00:00:07.674">&gt;&gt; Jon:  WELCOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:07.674" end="00:00:13.380">MY GUEST TONIGHT A BESTSELLING AUTHOR WHOSE NEW BOOK IS CALLED </p>
<p begin="00:00:13.380" end="00:00:19.253">&quot;DO NOT ASK WHAT GOOD WE DO.&quot; PLEASE WELCOME BACK TO THE PROGRAM, ROBERT DRAPER.</p>
<p begin="00:00:19.253" end="00:00:26.460"> <span tts:fontStyle="italic">( APPLAUSE )</span> NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.</p>
<p begin="00:00:26.460" end="00:00:29.396">&gt;&gt; THANKS FOR HAVING ME IS THERE YOU HAVE DONE AN EXCELLENT JOB.</p>
<p begin="00:00:29.396" end="00:00:39.840">THIS IS ONE OF THOSE &quot;DO ALMOST ONE OF THOSE BOOKS WHERE THE AUTHOR ENDURES A GREAT </p>
<p begin="00:00:39.840" end="00:00:40.574">CHALLENGE, PERSONAL CHALLENGE,</p>
<p begin="00:00:40.574" end="00:00:46.446">LIKE TREKKING UP A MOUNTAIN, OR RETRACING SHACKELFORD&apos;S JOURNEY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:46.446" end="00:00:48.882">YOU WERE A FLY ON THE WALL IN THE HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES FOR A YEAR.</p>
<p begin="00:00:48.882" end="00:00:51.318">&gt;&gt; YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:00:51.318" end="00:00:52.452">IT WAS FULL IMMERSION.</p>
<p begin="00:00:52.452" end="00:00:56.223">BASICALLY AFTER THE MIDTERM ELECTION I DECIDE I REALLY WANT TO FOLLOW THESE GUYS,</p>
<p begin="00:00:56.223" end="00:00:58.559">PARTICULARLY THE 87 REPUBLICAN FRESHMEN.</p>
<p begin="00:00:58.559" end="00:01:01.295">I KNEW THERE WOULD BE SOME KIND OF CHANGE IN ETHOS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:01.295" end="00:01:05.966">A THIRD OF THESE GUYS NEVER SERVED IN ANY ELECTED OFFICE BEFORE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:05.966" end="00:01:07.768">&gt;&gt; Jon:  87 NEW REPRESENTATIVES.</p>
<p begin="00:01:07.768" end="00:01:11.471">&gt;&gt; THERE HASN&apos;T BEEN A WAVE ELECTION BRINGING THAT MANY FRESHMEN IN SINCE 40 YEARS OR </p>
<p begin="00:01:11.471" end="00:01:12.739">SOMETHING LIKE THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:12.739" end="00:01:18.212">AND THE FACT SO MANY OF THEM HAD NO POLITICAL EXPERIENCE AND THAT NOW THE REPUBLICANS WERE GOING </p>
<p begin="00:01:18.212" end="00:01:22.349">TO TAKE CHARGE WOULD MEAN THEY WOULD BE THE-- THE OPEN QUESTION WAS WHETHER THE REPUBLICAN </p>
<p begin="00:01:22.349" end="00:01:24.384">LEADERSHIP WAS GOING TO BE ABLE TO CONTROL THESE GUYS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:24.384" end="00:01:28.388">&gt;&gt; Jon:  AND THEY&apos;RE VERY OPEN, AND I DON&apos;T KNOW IF IT WAS </p>
<p begin="00:01:28.388" end="00:01:32.326">BECAUSE THEY WERE FRESHMEN, BUT THEY&apos;RE VERY OPEN WITH YOU ABOUT </p>
<p begin="00:01:32.326" end="00:01:36.530">WHEN THEY BECOME CONFLICTED AND WHAT THEIR ASPIRATIONS ARE AND THAT SORT OF THING.</p>
<p begin="00:01:36.530" end="00:01:39.700">&gt;&gt; ONE OF THE MAIN CHARACTERS OF THE BOOK, JEFF DUNCAN -- </p>
<p begin="00:01:39.700" end="00:01:40.467">&gt;&gt; JEFF DUNCAN.</p>
<p begin="00:01:40.467" end="00:01:42.836">&gt;&gt; A GUY FROM SOUTH CAROLINA.</p>
<p begin="00:01:42.836" end="00:01:48.141">ONE OF THE FOUR HORSEMEN, VERY CONSERVATIVE FELLOW, BUT HIS ONGOING STRUGGLE WAS JUST SIMPLY </p>
<p begin="00:01:48.141" end="00:01:51.678">TO BE HEARD, TO BE MORE THAN ONE OF 435.</p>
<p begin="00:01:51.678" end="00:01:53.413">IT&apos;S A VERY BIG BODY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:53.413" end="00:02:01.121">HE CAME FROM THE STATE SENATE IN SOUTH CAROLINA WHERE HE HAD BEEN A VOICE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:01.121" end="00:02:05.959">&gt;&gt; Jon:  EVEN AMONG THE DELEGATION IN SOUTH CAROLINA,</p>
<p begin="00:02:05.959" end="00:02:08.495">THERE&apos;S-- SOMETHING HAPPENS AND HE IS NOT MENTIONED.</p>
<p begin="00:02:08.495" end="00:02:10.597">THE OTHER THREE ARE MENTIONED AND QUOTED.</p>
<p begin="00:02:10.597" end="00:02:13.534">IT&apos;S AN ARTICLE ABOUT THE FOUR HORSEMEN.</p>
<p begin="00:02:13.534" end="00:02:14.268">&gt;&gt; BY THE &quot;NEW YORK TIMES.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:02:14.268" end="00:02:17.104">&gt;&gt; Jon:  BY THE &quot;NEW YORK TIMES,&quot; AND HE IS NOT QUOTED AND </p>
<p begin="00:02:17.104" end="00:02:20.774">YOU GET THAT SENSE HE&apos;S BATTLING FOR HIS PRINCIPLES BUT ALSO WONDERING WHEN THE SPOTLIGHT </p>
<p begin="00:02:20.774" end="00:02:21.508">MIGHT COME TO HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:02:21.508" end="00:02:24.945">&gt;&gt; YEAH, NO, AS IF HE&apos;S LIKE A BLACK HOLE OR SOMETHING AND </p>
<p begin="00:02:24.945" end="00:02:28.682">EVERY TIME HE SAYS SOMETHING IT IMPLODES UPON ITSELF AND NO ONE HEARS IT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:28.682" end="00:02:31.818">&gt;&gt; Jon:  YOU DID A REALLY NICE JOB OF PRESENTING THEM AS HUMANS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:31.818" end="00:02:34.087"> <span tts:fontStyle="italic">(  LAUGHTER  )</span> AND I WAS VERY UNCOMFORTABLE WITH THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:34.087" end="00:02:43.130">I PREFER TO THINK OF THEM AS TWO-DIMENSIONAL CARICATURES THAT ARE REPTILIAN IN THEIR-- IN </p>
<p begin="00:02:43.130" end="00:02:44.865">THEIR POLITICAL REFLEXIVENESS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:44.865" end="00:02:46.967">MUCH EASIER TO DEMONIZE THEM.</p>
<p begin="00:02:46.967" end="00:02:49.803">BUT YOU INSIST THAT THEY&apos;RE THREE-DIMENSIONAL CHARACTERS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:49.803" end="00:02:51.305">&gt;&gt; SORRY TO INCONVENIENCE YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:02:51.305" end="00:02:53.373">NO, ALAN WEST IS A GOOD CASE IN POINT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:53.373" end="00:02:53.841">&gt;&gt; Jon:  SURE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:53.841" end="00:02:57.744">&gt;&gt; HE SAYS THINGS LIKE 41 DEMOCRATS ARE COMMUNISTS AND ALL THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:57.744" end="00:03:00.714">&gt;&gt; Jon:  78, I THINK 78.</p>
<p begin="00:03:00.714" end="00:03:02.115">&gt;&gt; REALLY?</p>
<p begin="00:03:02.115" end="00:03:02.783">&gt;&gt; Jon:  YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:03:02.783" end="00:03:05.352">&gt;&gt; BUT AT THE SAME TIME, HE&apos;S AN EQUAL OPPORTUNITY OFFENDER.</p>
<p begin="00:03:05.352" end="00:03:07.621">HE&apos;S OPINION A THORN IN THE SIDE TO THE REPUBLICANS BECAUSE HE </p>
<p begin="00:03:07.621" end="00:03:13.961">HAS-- HE&apos;S CALLED THEM OUT WHEN THEY HAVE NOT SUPPORTED DEFENSE CUTS ON CERTAIN ITEMS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:13.961" end="00:03:18.899">HE&apos;S CALLED THEM OUT FOR HAVING THIS CALENDAR THAT HAS THE REPRESENTATIVES IN THE DISTRICT </p>
<p begin="00:03:18.899" end="00:03:23.070">MORE OFTEN THAN IN WASHINGTON WHEN HE FEELS THERE OUGHT TO BE MORE THINGS GETTING DONE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:23.070" end="00:03:27.941">&gt;&gt; Jon:  DURING THE STATE OF THE UNION HE IS SITTING AND HE IS MARKING UP HIS THING AND </p>
<p begin="00:03:27.941" end="00:03:31.612">CERTAIN THINGS THE PRESIDENT SAYS, THAT&apos;S A GOOD POINT-- AND IT REALLY-- IF YOU WERE TO JUST </p>
<p begin="00:03:31.612" end="00:03:39.253">LOOK AT THOSE NOTES AND NOT REMEMBER THE FOOTAGE OF HIM GOING, &quot;STRAP YOUR BAYONETS AND </p>
<p begin="00:03:39.253" end="00:03:42.122">CHARGE!&quot; YOU&apos;D GO, OH, THAT&apos;S A VERY REASONABLE-- </p>
<p begin="00:03:42.122" end="00:03:46.093">&gt;&gt; SURE, BUT THEN HE VOTED FOR THE DEBT CEILING BILL AND WENT BACK HOME AND SOME OF HIS TEA </p>
<p begin="00:03:46.093" end="00:03:48.962">PARTY CONSTITUENTS SAID YOU DROPPED YOUR BAYONET.</p>
<p begin="00:03:48.962" end="00:03:51.798">HE&apos;S BEEN TO SOME DEGREE A DISAPPOINTMENT EVEN TO THEM.</p>
<p begin="00:03:51.798" end="00:03:54.334">&gt;&gt; Jon:  AND THAT WAS THE INTERESTING PART.</p>
<p begin="00:03:54.334" end="00:03:59.106">YOU&apos;VE GOT ANTHONY WEANER, AND OBVIOUSLY YOU CATALOGED WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM, AND ALAN WEST.</p>
<p begin="00:03:59.106" end="00:04:09.249">THERE&apos;S ALMOST A STRANGE ADMIRATION WITHIN THE HOUSE FOR THE GUYS THAT HAVE GLOAD </p>
<p begin="00:04:09.249" end="00:04:13.787">BRIGHTLY BECAUSE THEY SAY CRAZY THINGS ON TV OR PAUSE THEY ARE LOUDER AND BRASSIER THAN THEIR COLLEAGUES.</p>
<p begin="00:04:13.787" end="00:04:15.455">&gt;&gt; AND WEANER IS A CASE IN POINT YOU SAID.</p>
<p begin="00:04:15.455" end="00:04:19.860">THIS IS A GUY WHO IS UNDERSTOOD THE CAPITOL STAGE AS PERFORMANCE ART, BASICALLY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:19.860" end="00:04:21.361">THE PROBLEM WITH WEINER-- WELL,</p>
<p begin="00:04:21.361" end="00:04:24.464">MANY PROBLEMS WITH WEINER, BUT BEFORE HE UNDID HIMSELF-- YEAH,</p>
<p begin="00:04:24.464" end="00:04:25.399">OKAY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:25.399" end="00:04:28.068">&gt;&gt; Jon:  IT&apos;S LIKE WE&apos;RE ON A DIFFERENT SHOW RIGHT NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:04:28.068" end="00:04:31.104"> <span tts:fontStyle="italic">(  LAUGHTER  )</span> LET ME TELL YOU THE PROBLEM WITH WEINER.</p>
<p begin="00:04:31.104" end="00:04:32.239"> <span tts:fontStyle="italic">(  LAUGHTER  ).</span> </p>
<p begin="00:04:32.239" end="00:04:33.807">&gt;&gt; YEAH, THAT&apos;S RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:33.807" end="00:04:39.980">HE-- HE-- YOU KNOW, BEING THE ULTIMATE ENTREPRENEUR IN A BODY OF 435, HE ALIENATED ALL OF HIS COLLEAGUES.</p>
<p begin="00:04:39.980" end="00:04:41.448">HE WAS ABUSIVE TOWARDS HIS STAFF.</p>
<p begin="00:04:41.448" end="00:04:45.485">SO FINALLY, WHEN HIS WORLD DID EXPLODE, THERE WAS NO ONE STANDING BESIDE HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:04:45.485" end="00:04:53.460">&gt;&gt; Jon:  IS IT-- ONE THING THAT YOU WERE ABLE TO AVOID IN SOME WAYS IS THE JUDGMENT, THIS </p>
<p begin="00:04:53.460" end="00:04:57.130">SENSE OF &quot;ASK HERE&apos;S WHY THIS IS SO FRUSTRATING A PLACE&quot; TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:57.130" end="00:05:02.035">WHEN YOU READ IT, YOU HAVE A GREAT EMPATHY FOR-- I CAN SEE WHY THEY&apos;RE IN THE WEEDS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:02.035" end="00:05:07.708">THEIR WORLD IS MICROMANAGING THE BYZANTINE INFRASTRUCTURE OF THE GOVERNMENT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:07.708" end="00:05:09.910">&gt;&gt; YEAH, AND IT&apos;S-- I MEAN,</p>
<p begin="00:05:09.910" end="00:05:13.947">IT&apos;S-- IT&apos;S A COURSE OF AMERICA SLICED UP 435 DIFFERENT WAYS,</p>
<p begin="00:05:13.947" end="00:05:20.420">AND YOU CAN KIND OF EMPATHIZE WITH A GUY LYCRAULE LAB DOR, A TEA PARTY FRESHMAN FROM IDAHO </p>
<p begin="00:05:20.420" end="00:05:22.456">WHO SAID I DEPARTMENT COME HERE TO BE PART OF A TEAM.</p>
<p begin="00:05:22.456" end="00:05:25.659">IN A WAY THAT DOES SOUND RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:25.659" end="00:05:31.732">THE WHOLE SHIRTS AND SKINS ZERO-SUM APPROACH TO GOVERNMENT I THINK HAS CREATED A PARALYSIS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:31.732" end="00:05:37.704">AT THE SAME TIME, YOU HAVE TO HAVE SOME ORGANIZING PRINCE PAN THAN 435 GUYS SCRAMBLING AROUND </p>
<p begin="00:05:37.704" end="00:05:39.940">TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHATEVER IS BEST.</p>
<p begin="00:05:39.940" end="00:05:42.609">&gt;&gt; Jon:  IT&apos;S INTERESTING TO SEE THE MOMENTS WHEN EITHER THE </p>
<p begin="00:05:42.609" end="00:05:50.684">BOEHNER FOR THE REPUBLICANS OR NANCY PELOSI FOR THE DEMOCRATS IS CONFRONTED BY A LITTLE BIT OF </p>
<p begin="00:05:50.684" end="00:05:52.853">NONCOM PLIANCE AND HOW THEY RESPOND TO THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:52.853" end="00:05:57.524">IT&apos;S VERY-- I WON&apos;T SAY CHILLING BUT COLD.</p>
<p begin="00:05:57.524" end="00:06:00.360">&gt;&gt; IN SPEAKER BOEHNER&apos;S CASE I THINK IT&apos;S MORE SORT OF SAD.</p>
<p begin="00:06:00.360" end="00:06:04.698"> <span tts:fontStyle="italic">(  LAUGHTER  )</span> I MEAN, THE GUY-- HE HAS VERY </p>
<p begin="00:06:04.698" end="00:06:06.266">LIMITED POWERS NOW AS A SPEAKER.</p>
<p begin="00:06:06.266" end="00:06:12.072">I MEAN, WHEN THE APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE SAID TO HIM, &quot;WHY ARE YOU LETTING THESE GUYS VOTE </p>
<p begin="00:06:12.072" end="00:06:13.640">AGAINST REPUBLICAN BILLS?</p>
<p begin="00:06:13.640" end="00:06:15.509">YOU SHOULD PUNISH THEM.</p>
<p begin="00:06:15.509" end="00:06:19.813">YOU SHOULD STRIP THEM AGAINST COMMITTEE ASSIGNMENTS.&quot; HE SAID WE CAN&apos;T DO THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:19.813" end="00:06:22.482">IT WILL ONLY MAKE MARTYRS OUT OF THEM.</p>
<p begin="00:06:22.482" end="00:06:26.753">THE KNUCKLE-BREAKING DAYS OF DELAY ARE OVER.</p>
<p begin="00:06:26.753" end="00:06:29.289">&gt;&gt; Jon:  THAT&apos;S WHY BOEHNER IS ALWAYS WEEPING.</p>
<p begin="00:06:29.289" end="00:06:34.328">I&apos;M TELLING YOU, MAN, WHAT WONDERFUL REPORTING AND ACCESS AND IT&apos;S A GREAT INSIGHT INTO </p>
<p begin="00:06:34.328" end="00:06:36.396">WHY THEY ARE AT 9% IN THE POLLS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:36.396" end="00:06:41.635"> <span tts:fontStyle="italic">(  LAUGHTER  )</span> &quot;DO NOT ASK WHAT GOOD WE DO&quot; IS </p>
<p begin="00:06:41.635" end="00:06:42.936">ON THE BOOKSHELVES NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:06:42.936" end="00:06:43.604">ROBERT DRAPER.</p>
<p begin="00:06:43.604" end="00:06:44.404"> <span tts:fontStyle="italic">( APPLAUSE )</span> </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
