<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:07.441" end="00:00:08.609">WELCOME TO MY GUEST TONIGHT,</p>
<p begin="00:00:08.609" end="00:00:10.310">THE FOUNDER OF CHANGE.ORG.</p>
<p begin="00:00:10.310" end="00:00:12.379">PLEASE WELCOME TO THE SHOW BEN RATTRAY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:12.379" end="00:00:16.450">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) NICE TO SEE YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:00:16.450" end="00:00:21.188">HOW ARE YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:00:21.188" end="00:00:23.557">NICE TO SEE YOU, DID I PRONOUNCE THAT CORRECTLY?</p>
<p begin="00:00:23.557" end="00:00:24.992">&gt;&gt; YOU DID.</p>
<p begin="00:00:24.992" end="00:00:26.360">&gt;&gt; Jon: THAT&apos;S THE END OF THE INTERVIEW.</p>
<p begin="00:00:26.360" end="00:00:27.394">&gt;&gt; THANK YOU SO MUCH.</p>
<p begin="00:00:27.394" end="00:00:36.303">&gt;&gt; Jon: I&apos;VE DONE IT TELL ME ABOUT, SO CHANGE.ORG, YOU ARE A GUY, YOU WERE GOING TO SANFORD.</p>
<p begin="00:00:36.303" end="00:00:36.670">&gt;&gt; YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:00:36.670" end="00:00:38.605">&gt;&gt; THANK YOU, ONE PERSON.</p>
<p begin="00:00:38.605" end="00:00:40.340">&gt;&gt; Jon: I KNOW.</p>
<p begin="00:00:40.340" end="00:00:45.179">SO [BLEEP] [BLEEP] HARD TO GET IN THERE YOU THINK THE WHOLE AUDIENCE IS GOING TO </p>
<p begin="00:00:45.179" end="00:00:47.214">BE LIKE THAT&apos;S WHERE WE ALL WENT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:47.214" end="00:00:49.249">YOU WERE IN FINANCE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:49.249" end="00:00:49.616">&gt;&gt; YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:00:49.616" end="00:00:52.986">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU WERE GOING TO MAKE MILLIONS AND MILLIONS OF DOLLARS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:52.986" end="00:00:54.688">&gt;&gt; AS MUCH AS YOU,</p>
<p begin="00:00:54.688" end="00:00:55.055">HOPEFULLY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:55.055" end="00:00:55.856">&gt;&gt; Jon: THANK YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:00:55.856" end="00:00:57.057">&gt;&gt; YOU&apos;RE WELCOME.</p>
<p begin="00:00:57.057" end="00:00:59.626">&gt;&gt; Jon: HE&apos;S RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:59.626" end="00:01:05.832">YOU DECIDE INSTEAD TO TRY AND HELP PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:05.832" end="00:01:11.705">&gt;&gt; CRAZY YZ IS THAT WHEN THEY THREW YOU OUT OF SANFORD.</p>
<p begin="00:01:11.705" end="00:01:14.741">&gt;&gt; THE STORY WAS I WAS GOK AN INVESTMENT BANKER, THAT WAS THE PLAN.</p>
<p begin="00:01:14.741" end="00:01:19.246">MY SENIOR YEAR I GO BACK HOME, TALK TO ONE OF MY YOUNGER BROTHERS, AND HE COMES OUT AS GAY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:19.246" end="00:01:23.483">WHAT HE SAYS IS THE MOST NOTABLE THING IS THE PAIN HE EXPERIENCED WASN&apos;T SOME OF </p>
<p begin="00:01:23.483" end="00:01:29.456">THAT PEOPLE WERE EXPLICITLY ANTI-GAY, THAT PEOPLE STOOD BY AND DIDN&apos;T DO ANYTHING ABOUT IT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:29.456" end="00:01:30.457">THE FIRST THING, YOU KNOW,</p>
<p begin="00:01:30.457" end="00:01:31.658">HI BEEN ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE,</p>
<p begin="00:01:31.658" end="00:01:37.331">I AM ASHAMED, TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT TO DO AND DECIDE I WILL DEDICATE MYSELF TO NEVER STAYING </p>
<p begin="00:01:37.331" end="00:01:43.136">SILENT AGAIN SO I START THE SITE CHANGE.ORG TO EMPOWER PEOPLE TO STAY WHAT THEY </p>
<p begin="00:01:43.136" end="00:01:45.439">WANT AROUND THE ISSUES THEY CARE ABOUT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:45.439" end="00:01:46.507">&gt;&gt; Jon: INCREDIBLE STORY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:46.507" end="00:01:51.211">PUTTING YOUR EFFORTS AND LIFE&apos;S WORK BEHIND A CHANGE THAT YOU WANTED TO MAKE, IN </p>
<p begin="00:01:51.211" end="00:01:53.347">YOUR OWN BEING.</p>
<p begin="00:01:53.347" end="00:01:57.417">HOW DOES IT FIRST COME TO SUCCESS OR LIGHT, YOU KNOW,</p>
<p begin="00:01:57.417" end="00:01:59.853">PEOPLE PUT THINGS UP ON THE INTERNET ALL THE TIME.</p>
<p begin="00:01:59.853" end="00:02:01.221">&gt;&gt; FIRST CAMED FAILURES.</p>
<p begin="00:02:01.221" end="00:02:02.589">SO WE STARTED FIVE YEARS AGO,</p>
<p begin="00:02:02.589" end="00:02:07.060">THIS IS A LONG JOURNEY AND IT HAS BEEN OVER THE PAST LIVING EVERY MONTH RIGHT NOW </p>
<p begin="00:02:07.060" end="00:02:10.764">WE ARE GROWING FASTER THAN WE DID IN THE FIRST FOUR YEARS COMBINNED, YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:02:10.764" end="00:02:13.867">AND SO WHAT IS HAPPENING NOW IS PEOPLE CAN START A COMPETITION VERY EASILY GO </p>
<p begin="00:02:13.867" end="00:02:18.639">ON THE SITE, SAY WHAT THEY CARE B IDENTIFY THE TARGET OF THE PETITION AND WHY </p>
<p begin="00:02:18.639" end="00:02:19.806">PEOPLE SHOULD JOIN THEM,</p>
<p begin="00:02:19.806" end="00:02:22.743">SPREAD THROUGH SOCIAL MEDIA AND A LOT GO VIRAL.</p>
<p begin="00:02:22.743" end="00:02:26.246">&gt;&gt; Jon: NOW PEOPLE DO THEY COME TO THE SITE LOOK OG FOR AN ISSUE, THEY SIGN IT AND </p>
<p begin="00:02:26.246" end="00:02:31.752">THAT IS HOW IT GOES VIRAL OR JUST BY THE SHEER NUMBER OF PEOPLE SIGNING IT, PEOPLE </p>
<p begin="00:02:31.752" end="00:02:32.686">BEGIN TO TAKE NOTICE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:32.686" end="00:02:34.087">HOW WOULD SOMETHING GO VIRAL.</p>
<p begin="00:02:34.087" end="00:02:36.089">&gt;&gt; WHAT USUALLY HAPPENS IS SOMEONE GOES TO THE SITE,</p>
<p begin="00:02:36.089" end="00:02:38.825">STARTS A PETITION ON AN ISSUE THEY TRULY CARE ABOUT,</p>
<p begin="00:02:38.825" end="00:02:42.563">PUSH IT TO THEIR FRIENDS BECAUSE IF I WERE ON FACEBOOK AND TWITTER, PEOPLE </p>
<p begin="00:02:42.563" end="00:02:45.399">FIND OUT ABOUT THE CAMPAIGN MOSTLY THROUGH SOCIAL MED YAMENT THEY DON&apos;T JUST COME </p>
<p begin="00:02:45.399" end="00:02:47.734">TO THE SITE, THEY SEE IT THROUGH OTHER CHANNELS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:47.734" end="00:02:49.837">&gt;&gt; Jon: SO PEOPLE ARE SENDING IT TO OTHER PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:49.837" end="00:02:53.874">AND THAT PUTS PRESSURE THEN ON IT SEEMS THE NEWS MEDIA.</p>
<p begin="00:02:53.874" end="00:02:56.343">AT WHAT POINT DOW GUYS GET INVOLVED AGAIN OR DON&apos;T YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:02:56.343" end="00:02:59.112">&gt;&gt; SO WE-- .</p>
<p begin="00:02:59.112" end="00:02:59.713">&gt;&gt; Jon: .</p>
<p begin="00:02:59.713" end="00:03:03.116">&gt;&gt; ABOUT 15,000 CAMPAIGNS GET STARTED EVERY MONTH ON THE SITE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:03.116" end="00:03:04.184">HUGE NUMBER OF CAMPAIGNS,</p>
<p begin="00:03:04.184" end="00:03:05.919">HUGE DIVERSITY OF CAMPAIGNS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:05.919" end="00:03:08.589">WHAT HAPPENS IS SOMETIMES PEOPLE SIGN BUT THEY TAKE OTHER ACTION AS WELL IT </p>
<p begin="00:03:08.589" end="00:03:13.126">THERE IS A LOT OF SKEPTICISM ABOUT THE POWER OF ON-LINE PETITIONS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:13.126" end="00:03:16.930">THE REASON YOU ARE POWERFUL IS YOU HAVE A MOVEMENT OF PEOPLE THAT CAN BE MOBILIZED </p>
<p begin="00:03:16.930" end="00:03:18.065">TO TAKE FURTHER ACTION.</p>
<p begin="00:03:18.065" end="00:03:19.600">CALL DECISION MAKERS,</p>
<p begin="00:03:19.600" end="00:03:22.503">MOBILIZE THE MEDIA OR GO TO OFFLINE EVENTS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:22.503" end="00:03:26.406">&gt;&gt; Jon: HOW DO YOU MAKE SURE THAT IT&apos;S NOT SPAM, THAT IT&apos;S NOT PEOPLE JUST </p>
<p begin="00:03:26.406" end="00:03:33.280">CLICKING AND OR A SPAMBOT OR A ROBOT, A REAL ROBOT?</p>
<p begin="00:03:33.280" end="00:03:35.415">&gt;&gt; WE HAVEN&apos;T YET DISCOVERED ANY REAL ROBOTS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:35.415" end="00:03:40.587">&gt;&gt; Jon: HOW DO YOU NOT KNOW IT IS A REAL ROBOT WITH LIKE LASERS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:40.587" end="00:03:43.156">BUT HOW DO YOU PATROL THE SITE IN ANY WAY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:43.156" end="00:03:47.127">&gt;&gt; SO WE HAVE A TEAM IN SILICON VALLEY, ENGINEERS THAT IDENTIFY IF THERE IS </p>
<p begin="00:03:47.127" end="00:03:48.362">ANY FRAUDULENT BEHAVIOR.</p>
<p begin="00:03:48.362" end="00:03:53.567">BUT OTHERWISE IT IS SORT OF LIKE YOUTUBE, PEOPLE CAN IDENTIFY POTENTIALLY FRAUDULENT CAMPAIGN </p>
<p begin="00:03:53.567" end="00:03:56.904">APPROXIMATES BUT OTHERWISE THE OVERWHELMING MAJORITY ARE AUTHENTIC LOCAL ISSUES.</p>
<p begin="00:03:56.904" end="00:03:59.706">&gt;&gt; Jon: DOW FIND THERE IS A REDUNDANCY?</p>
<p begin="00:03:59.706" end="00:04:04.745">IS THERE ANY WAY, DO YOU GET PEOPLE TO COALESCE AROUND AN ISSUE THAT HAS SET THINGS UP </p>
<p begin="00:04:04.745" end="00:04:05.779">AT DIFFERENT SPACES.</p>
<p begin="00:04:05.779" end="00:04:10.250">&gt;&gt; WE ALLOWED SORT OF THE DARWINNIAN PROCESS TO UNFOLD SO SOMETIMES THERE WILL BE </p>
<p begin="00:04:10.250" end="00:04:14.688">30, 40 PETITIONS AROUND A SINGLE ISSUE, THAT JUST GOES AND ONE OFF ENTIMES GOES </p>
<p begin="00:04:14.688" end="00:04:17.891">VIRAL AND THE MAJORITY OF PEOPLE WILL TAKE ACTION ON THAT CAMPAIGN.</p>
<p begin="00:04:17.891" end="00:04:24.565">&gt;&gt; DO YOU HAVE, IS THERE A SENSE OF JUDGEMENT, CAN ANYBODY, WILL YOU HAVE A </p>
<p begin="00:04:24.565" end="00:04:30.437">CONSERVATIVE ISSUE, A LIBERAL ISSUE OR OTHER THINGS THAT YOU KNOW GO TO DIFFERENT POLARITIES ON THE </p>
<p begin="00:04:30.437" end="00:04:31.071">SAME ISSUE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:31.071" end="00:04:34.808">&gt;&gt; YEAH, SO WHAT HAS BEEN REALLY IMPORTANT FOR SUS MAINTAINING AN OPEN PLATFORM </p>
<p begin="00:04:34.808" end="00:04:36.877">SO NOT A PARTISAN PERSPECTIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:36.877" end="00:04:41.982">ANYONE CAN SORT OF CAMPAIGN AND SAY WHAT ANYONE CAN POSE TO VIDEO ON YOUTUBE AND WE </p>
<p begin="00:04:41.982" end="00:04:45.786">DO HAVE CHEATING CAMPAIGNS SOMETIMES BUT USUALLY WHAT HAPPENS IS ONE ENDS UP </p>
<p begin="00:04:45.786" end="00:04:49.423">EXPLODING, THE MAJORITY OF AMERICANS AND GETS ALL THE MEDIA ATTENTION.</p>
<p begin="00:04:49.423" end="00:04:54.361">&gt;&gt; HOW MANY PEOPLE WANT POT LEGALIZED.</p>
<p begin="00:04:54.361" end="00:04:56.430">&gt;&gt; A NOINT SUBSTANTIAL NUMBER OF PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:56.430" end="00:04:59.833">&gt;&gt; IS THAT BECAUSE I REMEMBER, THE OBAMA CAMPAIGN STARTED THIS THING THAT IF </p>
<p begin="00:04:59.833" end="00:05:04.938">YOU SEND US A PETITION, I THINK IT WAS 5,000 NAMES, WE WILL GIVE IT ACTION AND THE </p>
<p begin="00:05:04.938" end="00:05:11.111">FIRST LIKE 100 PETITION THESE GOT WERE LIKE LEGALIZE POT, HEY, POT, HOW ABOUT LEGALIZING IT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:11.111" end="00:05:15.749">YOU KNOW, VARIOUS, AND THOSE TYPES OF NATIONAL PETITIONS ARE WHY I THINK PEOPLE ARE </p>
<p begin="00:05:15.749" end="00:05:17.784">SKEPTICAL OF THE POSSIBLE IMPACT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:17.784" end="00:05:21.655">HISTORICALLY PETITIONS HAVE BEEN LIKE STOP GLOBAL WARMING OR END POVERTY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:21.655" end="00:05:27.528">THINGS THAT DON&apos;T HAVE A REAL SERIOUS CHANGE, THE ABILITY TO MAKE IT A </p>
<p begin="00:05:27.528" end="00:05:31.265">DIFFERENCE WHAT IS DIFFERENT ON CHANGE.ORG PEOPLE START LOCAL PIRX THOUSANDS OF THEM </p>
<p begin="00:05:31.265" end="00:05:32.966">AND ARE WINNING EVERY DAY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:32.966" end="00:05:34.067">&gt;&gt; I SEE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:34.067" end="00:05:37.504">ONE THING THAT YOU WOULD SAY TO PEOPLE IF THEY WANTED TO GET INVOLVED IN THESE TYPES </p>
<p begin="00:05:37.504" end="00:05:40.874">OF THINGS OR SOMETHING THEY FELT IMPORTANT ABOUT IS THE WAY YOU CHANGED YOUR LIFE </p>
<p begin="00:05:40.874" end="00:05:41.542">WHAT WOULD YOU SAY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:41.542" end="00:05:44.645">&gt;&gt; I SAY OVERALL THE POWER PEOPLE HAVE TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE RIGHT NOW WITH </p>
<p begin="00:05:44.645" end="00:05:49.082">SOCIAL MEDIA IS FAR GREATER THAN EVER BEFORE, AS YOU IDENTIFY AN ISSUE, YOU CARE </p>
<p begin="00:05:49.082" end="00:05:51.785">PASSIONATELY B YOU IDENTIFY THE RIGHT PERSON WITHOUT CAN MAKE A DIFFERENCE, YOU HAVE </p>
<p begin="00:05:51.785" end="00:05:54.555">A GREATER CHANCE OF SUCCESS THAN YOU POSSIBLY COULD IMAGINE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:54.555" end="00:05:56.256">&gt;&gt; Jon: AND THIS IS THE WAY TO GO ABOUT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:56.256" end="00:05:58.992">&gt;&gt; ONE OF THE PRIMARY WAYS TO DO IT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:58.992" end="00:06:04.198">&gt;&gt; Jon: NICELY DONE, SIR,</p>
<p begin="00:06:04.198" end="00:06:04.932">BEN RATTRAY,</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
