<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:11.712" end="00:00:12.379"> <span tts:color="#ffff00">Captioning sponsored by</span> </p>
<p begin="00:00:12.379" end="00:00:15.315"> <span tts:color="#ffff00">COMEDY CENTRAL</span> </p>
<p begin="00:00:16.116" end="00:00:16.850">( <span tts:fontStyle="italic">THEME SONG PLAYING</span> ) </p>
<p begin="00:00:16.850" end="00:00:22.756">( <span tts:fontStyle="italic">CHEERS AND APPLAUSE</span> ) </p>
<p begin="00:00:23.123" end="00:00:24.091">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELCOME TO THE DAILY SHOW.</p>
<p begin="00:00:24.091" end="00:00:26.126">THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.</p>
<p begin="00:00:26.126" end="00:00:31.031">YES, OH, WE&apos;RE EXCITED TO WELCOME THIS GENTLEMAN BACK,</p>
<p begin="00:00:31.031" end="00:00:34.134">OUR GUEST TONIGHT ROB CORDDRY IS JOINING US.</p>
<p begin="00:00:34.134" end="00:00:35.169">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) </p>
<p begin="00:00:35.169" end="00:00:40.941">&gt;&gt; THAT MAN, AND I DON&apos;T MIND SAYING IT THIS, THAT MAN IS EASILY IN MY TOP TWO </p>
<p begin="00:00:40.941" end="00:00:44.344">FAVORITE CORDDRY&apos;S WHO HAS EVER WORKED HERE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:44.344" end="00:00:50.150">(LAUGHTER) HEY, YOU&apos;RE A REGULAR WATCHER OF THIS PROGRAM.</p>
<p begin="00:00:50.150" end="00:00:53.887">YOU MAY HAVE NOTICED ONE, I RECENTLY HAD A BREAST REDUCTION.</p>
<p begin="00:00:53.887" end="00:01:04.431">(LAUGHTER) (CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) THEY ARE REAL AND THEY ARE-- AND TWO, WE&apos;VE GOT A </p>
<p begin="00:01:04.431" end="00:01:06.133">PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION COMING UP.</p>
<p begin="00:01:06.133" end="00:01:09.903">AMERICA&apos;S DEMOGRAPHICS HAVE CHANGED DRAMATICALLY IN THE PAST TWO DECADE THERE ARE </p>
<p begin="00:01:09.903" end="00:01:13.674">TWO WAYS A POLITICAL PARTY CAN REACT TO THAT YOU CAN EITHER EXPAND YOUR APPEAL TO </p>
<p begin="00:01:13.674" end="00:01:17.911">A NEW FIELD OF VOTERS BY MAKING THEIR ISSUES YOUR ISSUES.</p>
<p begin="00:01:17.911" end="00:01:19.079">WELL, OR -- </p>
<p begin="00:01:19.079" end="00:01:23.817">&gt;&gt; CAN THEY PASS THE VOTER OHIO LAW, LOY LOY,</p>
<p begin="00:01:23.817" end="00:01:24.551">PENNSYLVANIA.</p>
<p begin="00:01:24.551" end="00:01:29.523">&gt;&gt; GORGE GRA, QUIND END RNLD KANSAS, ARE ALLOWED TO REQUIRE PHOTO I.D..</p>
<p begin="00:01:29.523" end="00:01:32.759">&gt;&gt; IT DISPROPORTIONATELY AFFECTS DEMOCRATIC VOTERS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:32.759" end="00:01:36.563">&gt;&gt; THESE LAWS DISPROPORTIONATELY AFFECT MINORITY, THE YOUNG, THE OLD,</p>
<p begin="00:01:36.563" end="00:01:36.930">THE POOR.</p>
<p begin="00:01:36.930" end="00:01:39.766">&gt;&gt; Stephen: THE YOUNG, THE OLD, THE POOR MINORITIES.</p>
<p begin="00:01:39.766" end="00:01:42.669">FOUR HORSEMEN OF THE DEMOCALYPSE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:42.669" end="00:01:48.909">WHICH IS WHY IT IS THE SUBJECT OF TONIGHT&apos;S DEMOCALYPSE 2012.</p>
<p begin="00:01:48.909" end="00:01:56.617">AS YOU KNOW-- AS YOU KNOW AND YOU WELL KNOW THIS, IN PERSON VOTER FRAUD IS AN </p>
<p begin="00:01:56.617" end="00:02:08.462">ENORMOUS ISSUE WITH MORE THAN EXACTLY 10 DOCUMENTED CASES OF IT IN THE ENTIRE COUNTRY ALONE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:08.462" end="00:02:11.932">JUST SINCE THE BEGINNING OF THE MILLENNIUM.</p>
<p begin="00:02:11.932" end="00:02:18.305">THAT&apos;S .000000284% OF ALL VOTES!</p>
<p begin="00:02:18.305" end="00:02:24.511">(LAUGHTER) SO YOU CAN SEE WHY PENNSYLVANIA WOULD WANT TO ENACT A VOTER I.D. LAW THAT </p>
<p begin="00:02:24.511" end="00:02:32.152">ONE CITY CLAIMS COULD-- OR AROUND 9% OF THE ENTIRE PENNSYLVANIA ELECTORATE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:32.152" end="00:02:36.089">BUT THAT&apos;S THE PRICE YOU PAY TO PREVENT SOMETHING THAT DOESN&apos;T HAPPEN.</p>
<p begin="00:02:36.089" end="00:02:44.231">(LAUGHTER) IT&apos;S LIKE HOW PEANUT PUT CERTIFICATE MADE WITH HUGE AMOUNTS OF HYDRO COLORIC </p>
<p begin="00:02:44.231" end="00:02:48.001">ACID TO-- DRAGON BONES THAT MAY HAVE GOTTEN INTO IT DURING THE MANUFACTURING PROCESS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:48.001" end="00:02:55.108">WILL YOU LOSE SOME PEOPLE WHO DIE BY EATING HYDRO COLORIC ACID, OF COURSE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:55.108" end="00:03:02.049">BUT ISN&apos;T IT WORTH KNOWING THAT YOUR PEANUT BUTTER IS DRAGON BONE FREE?</p>
<p begin="00:03:02.049" end="00:03:08.522">NOW PENNSYLVANIA HAS VOTED DEMOCRAT-- DEMOCRATIC IN THE LAST FIVE PRESIDENTIAL ELECTIONS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:08.522" end="00:03:10.224">LEANING TOWARD OS BAMA IN THIS ELECTION.</p>
<p begin="00:03:10.224" end="00:03:15.696">NOT ONLY THIS VOTER I.D. LAW IS BLATANTLY DESIGNED TO SKEW THAT RESULT, RIGHT?</p>
<p begin="00:03:15.696" end="00:03:18.565">THE HOUSE REPUBLICAN MAJORITY LEADER THAT DESIGNED IT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:18.565" end="00:03:25.639">&gt;&gt; VOTER I.D. WHICH IS GOING TO ALLOW GOVERNOR ROMNEY TO WIN THE STATE OF PENNSYLVANIA, DONE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:25.639" end="00:03:27.941">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:03:27.941" end="00:03:33.113">&gt;&gt; Jon: LORD KNOWS WE DIDN&apos;T WANT ROMNEY RUNNING ON HIS PERSONALITY AND POLICY, AM I </p>
<p begin="00:03:33.113" end="00:03:33.614">RIGHT PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:33.614" end="00:03:38.552">AND I&apos;M ASSUMING THAT THE JUDGE IN PENNSYLVANIA WHO HAS BEEN ASKED TO REVIEW IT </p>
<p begin="00:03:38.552" end="00:03:40.320">WILL SEE IT AS A PARTISAN ACT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:40.320" end="00:03:43.090">&gt;&gt; IT IS A STUNNING DECISION FROM THE PENNSYLVANIA COURT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:43.090" end="00:03:47.494">THE STATE&apos;S NEW TOUGH VOTER I.D. LAW WILL NOT BE STOPPED.</p>
<p begin="00:03:47.494" end="00:03:53.600">THE JUDGE BELIEVES IT WILL BE CARRIED OUT IN A NONPARTISAN EVENHANDED MANNER.</p>
<p begin="00:03:53.600" end="00:03:54.668">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:03:54.668" end="00:03:56.870">&gt;&gt; Jon: YES, OF COURSE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:56.870" end="00:04:04.811">THIS LAW CREATED FOR SPECIFICALLY PARTISAN PURPOSES WILL BE CARRIED OUT IN A NONPARTISAN EVENHANDED MANNER.</p>
<p begin="00:04:04.811" end="00:04:11.051">MUCH IN THE WAY THAT ROBO SAARUS WHILE CREATED SOLELY AS AN AUTOMOBILE EATING </p>
<p begin="00:04:11.051" end="00:04:16.456">MACHINE, WILL MOST LIKELY VALET PARK AT YOUR PARTY WITH NO FORESEEABLE PROBLEMS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:16.456" end="00:04:22.963">WHY WOULD IT-- MAYBE I&apos;M BEING TOO HARD ON IT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:22.963" end="00:04:27.534">AS LONG AS VOTERS ARE EDUCATED ABOUT THE LAW IN A NONPARTISAN WAY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:27.534" end="00:04:28.769">&gt;&gt; A CONTRACT?</p>
<p begin="00:04:28.769" end="00:04:34.208">FOR THE JOB OF EDUCATING PENNSYLVANIAIANS ON THE NEW VOTING RESTRICTIONS WAS GIVEN TO A MAN WHO HAS </p>
<p begin="00:04:34.208" end="00:04:37.678">HELPED RAISE $30,000 FOR THE MITT ROMNEY FOR PRESIDENT CAMPAIGN.</p>
<p begin="00:04:37.678" end="00:04:42.716">HE&apos;S ALSO THE FORMER EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR OF THE STATE REPUBLICAN PARTY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:42.716" end="00:04:46.086">&gt;&gt; Jon: ROBO SAARUS HUNGRY!</p>
<p begin="00:04:46.086" end="00:04:49.389">ROBOSAURUS SMASH!</p>
<p begin="00:04:49.389" end="00:04:53.627">WELL, I GUESS THAT DOES EXPLAIN THE NEW VOTER I.D.</p>
<p begin="00:04:53.627" end="00:04:54.361">AD I SAW.</p>
<p begin="00:04:54.361" end="00:04:55.729">&gt;&gt; WAS&apos;S UP, PENNSYLVANIA,</p>
<p begin="00:04:55.729" end="00:05:00.033">GUESS WHOSE&apos;S COME TOGETHER MONTGOMERIE COUNTY AMPITHEATRE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:00.033" end="00:05:05.172">IT&apos;S THE MOTOR CITY MAD MERN TED NUDGE ENT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:05.172" end="00:05:12.179">REASONS HEY, FELLOW REPUBLICANS, NOW THAT ALL THE DEMOCRATS ARE CHANGED THE CHANNELS HERE IS VOTING INFORMATION.</p>
<p begin="00:05:12.179" end="00:05:15.849">WHEN YOU GO TO VOTE FOR MITT ROMNEY BRING PHOTO IDENTIFICATION.</p>
<p begin="00:05:15.849" end="00:05:16.817">IT IS REQUIRED.</p>
<p begin="00:05:16.817" end="00:05:20.554">AND DON&apos;T TELL ANY BLACKS OR OLD PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:20.554" end="00:05:31.098">AD PAID FOR BY THOSE WHO WANT ROMNEY TO WIN.</p>
<p begin="00:05:31.098" end="00:05:36.069">&gt;&gt; Jon: I WONDER IF HE GOT THAT AT A SHELL TER.</p>
<p begin="00:05:36.069" end="00:05:40.274">BUT AS RIDICULOUS AS THIS VOTER I.D. BUSINESS IT IS NOT LIKE PENNSYLVANIA IS </p>
<p begin="00:05:40.274" end="00:05:47.147">DOING SOMETHING CRAZY LIKE GIVING REPUBLICAN COUNTIES MORE TIME TO VOTE THEN DEMOCRATIC COUNTIES.</p>
<p begin="00:05:47.147" end="00:05:47.814">THEY&apos;RE NOT CRAZY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:47.814" end="00:05:52.920">&gt;&gt; THE LATEST TWIST ON THIS HAS REPUBLICANS IN OHIO RESTRICTING EARLY VOTING </p>
<p begin="00:05:52.920" end="00:05:58.725">HOURS ON DEMOCRATIC COUNTIES BUT EXTENDING EARLY VOTING HOURS IN THE REPUBLICAN ONES.</p>
<p begin="00:05:58.725" end="00:06:03.463">&gt;&gt; Jon: ARE YOU-- [BLEEP]</p>
<p begin="00:06:03.463" end="00:06:05.532">KIDDING ME!</p>
<p begin="00:06:05.532" end="00:06:10.270">ALL AMERICANS WHO WANT EQUAL ACCESS TO THE VOTE TAKE TWO-STEPS FORWARD, NOT SO </p>
<p begin="00:06:10.270" end="00:06:14.908">FAST PEOPLE WHO LIVE ON MARTIN LUTHER KING BOULEVARD SOUTH.</p>
<p begin="00:06:14.908" end="00:06:20.214">NOW YOU MIGHT WONDER HOW IT WOULD EVEN BE POSSIBLE FOR OHIO TO DIVIDE UP VOTING </p>
<p begin="00:06:20.214" end="00:06:22.249">HOURS BY HOW DISTRICTS VOTE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:22.249" end="00:06:23.283">FUNNY STORY.</p>
<p begin="00:06:23.283" end="00:06:27.421">OHIO COUNTY ELECTION BOARD EACH HAVE TWO REPUBLICANS AN TWO DEMOCRATS AND THE GUY </p>
<p begin="00:06:27.421" end="00:06:33.894">WHO BREAKS THE TIE IN ESTABLISHING POWERS IS OHIO SECRETARY OF STATE JOHN HOUSTON.</p>
<p begin="00:06:33.894" end="00:06:34.294">REPUBLICAN.</p>
<p begin="00:06:34.294" end="00:06:37.664">GUESS WHO HE HAS BEEN SIDING WITH.</p>
<p begin="00:06:37.664" end="00:06:41.902">IT&apos;S AS FAIR AS WHEN YOUR DAD BREAKS THE TIE BETWEEN YOU AND YOUR MOM OVER </p>
<p begin="00:06:41.902" end="00:06:46.540">WHETHER YOU GET TO STAY OUT ALL NIGHT DRINKING.</p>
<p begin="00:06:46.540" end="00:06:51.078">EXCEPT INSTEAD OF STAYING OUT ALL NIGHT DRINKING, IT&apos;S VOTING.</p>
<p begin="00:06:51.078" end="00:06:53.080">MAYBE I&apos;M MISSING SOMETHING.</p>
<p begin="00:06:53.080" end="00:06:57.184">PLEASE EXPLAIN HOW FEWER PEOPLE VOTING SOMEHOW ENHANCES THE DEMOCRATIC PROCESS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:57.184" end="00:07:00.921">&gt;&gt; I DON&apos;T THINK THAT THE BAR IS TOO HIGH THERE FOR ANYBODY WHO REALLY CARES </p>
<p begin="00:07:00.921" end="00:07:04.791">ABOUT THE FUTURE OF OUR COUNTRY AND WANTS TO HAVE THEIR VOICE HEARD BY VOTING.</p>
<p begin="00:07:04.791" end="00:07:11.131">WE TRY TO MAKE IT EASY BUT WE CAN&apos;T, YOU KNOW, I SAY WE&apos;RE NOT 7-11.</p>
<p begin="00:07:11.131" end="00:07:18.105">WE CAN&apos;T STAY OPEN 24/7 AND LET ANYBODY VOTE BY ANY RULE THAT THEY WANT TO.</p>
<p begin="00:07:18.105" end="00:07:22.342">&gt;&gt; Jon: SURELY WE CAN&apos;T EXPECT OUR CONSTITUTIONALLY GUARANTEED VOTING RIGHTS TO </p>
<p begin="00:07:22.342" end="00:07:27.447">MEET THE SAME HIGH STANDARDS AS A COMBINATION GAS STATION CONVENIENCE STORE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:27.447" end="00:07:33.820">(LAUGHTER) NEED I REMIND YOU OF THE STRICT DRESS CODE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:33.820" end="00:07:41.061">NOT SURPRISINGLY, THIS SITUATION AND THE RULING PROVOKES A NATIONAL OUTCRY.</p>
<p begin="00:07:41.061" end="00:07:42.829">&gt;&gt; AFTER HEAVY CRITICISM,</p>
<p begin="00:07:42.829" end="00:07:49.069">OHIO SECRETARY OF STATE HAS JUST ORDERED THAT ALL 88 COUNTIES IN THAT STATE HAVE </p>
<p begin="00:07:49.069" end="00:07:51.972">TO ABIDE BY THE SAME EARLY VOTING RULES.</p>
<p begin="00:07:51.972" end="00:07:54.675">&gt;&gt; AND I WOULD HAVE GOTTEN AWAY WITH IT TOO.</p>
<p begin="00:07:54.675" end="00:07:55.676">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:07:55.676" end="00:07:59.413">&gt;&gt; Jon: IF IT WEREN&apos;T FOR THAT MEDDLING CONSTITUTION AND OF COURSE THOSE KIDS IN </p>
<p begin="00:07:59.413" end="00:08:00.113">THAT VAN.</p>
<p begin="00:08:00.113" end="00:08:18.131">THEY REALLY WERE THE ONES IT THAT REALLY--  (CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) </p>
<p begin="00:08:18.131" end="00:08:19.867">&gt;&gt;&gt; TWO THINGS, TWO STATES,</p>
<p begin="00:08:19.867" end="00:08:23.770">TWO COMPLETELY DIFFERENT MEANS OF SUPPRESSING DEMOCRATIC TURNOUT.</p>
<p begin="00:08:23.770" end="00:08:25.672">HERE IS THE ONE THING I HAVE IN COMMON.</p>
<p begin="00:08:25.672" end="00:08:30.944">THE MECHANISM OF THE VOTE ARE IN THE HANDS OF PARTISAN ELECTED OFFICIALS.</p>
<p begin="00:08:30.944" end="00:08:36.383">PERHAPS&apos;S IT&apos;S TIME THE WHEELS OF SOCIETY TOOK OUR CUES FROM OTHER HIGHLY </p>
<p begin="00:08:36.383" end="00:08:42.422">EVOLVED DEMOCRACIES AND ELECTION OVERSIGHT LIKE THEY DO IN MEXICO, CANADA, INDIA </p>
<p begin="00:08:42.422" end="00:08:46.193">AND OF COURSE RWANDA.</p>
<p begin="00:08:46.193" end="00:08:47.528">THAT&apos;S RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:08:47.528" end="00:08:54.334">A PLACE SO TERRIBLE DON CHEADLE MADE A MOVIE ABOUT A HOTEL THERE.</p>
<p begin="00:08:54.334" end="00:08:56.770">NO, THAT&apos;S THE OTHER-- YEAH.</p>
<p begin="00:08:56.770" end="00:09:01.141">(APPLAUSE) WE GOT TO GET OUR [BLEEP]</p>
<p begin="00:09:01.141" end="00:09:01.542">TOGETHER.</p>
<p begin="00:09:01.542" end="00:09:02.609">WE&apos;LL BE RIGHT BACK.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
