<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:03.303" end="00:00:05.005">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) </p>
<p begin="00:00:05.005" end="00:00:09.309">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELCOME BACK, MY GUEST TONIGHT, HE WAS A CAPTAIN IN THE UNITED STATES NAVY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:09.309" end="00:00:10.744">HE WAS AN ASTRONAUT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:10.744" end="00:00:16.049">HIS NEW BOOK WHICH HE COWROTE WITH HIS WIFE ARIZONA CONGRESSWOMAN GABRIELLE GIFFORDS </p>
<p begin="00:00:16.049" end="00:00:21.588">IS CALLED &quot;GABBY, A STORY OF COURAGE AND HOPE.&quot; PLEASE WELCOME TO THE PROGRAM MARK KELLY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:21.588" end="00:00:29.696">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) SO NICE TO SEE YOU, THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.</p>
<p begin="00:00:29.696" end="00:00:31.398">&gt;&gt; GREAT TO BE HERE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:31.398" end="00:00:35.235">&gt;&gt; Jon: THE BOOK IS CALLED &quot;GABBY, A STORY OF COURAGE AND HOPE.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:00:35.235" end="00:00:37.604">I HAVE TO TELL YOU, I&apos;M READING THE BOOK AND THE TEMPTATION IS,</p>
<p begin="00:00:37.604" end="00:00:40.440">YOU KNOW, YOU&apos;RE AN ASTRONAUT WHO MARRIES A CONGRESSWOMAN.</p>
<p begin="00:00:40.440" end="00:00:46.780">THE TEMPTATION IS TO SKIP THE ROUGH PARTS, THE TRAGEDY, AND READ IT AS A FAIRY TALE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:46.780" end="00:00:51.752">BECAUSE IT IS IN SOME RESPECTS A REMARKABLE LOVE STORY BETWEEN TWO EXTRAORDINARY PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:51.752" end="00:00:53.287">&gt;&gt; WELL, THANK YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:00:53.287" end="00:00:59.793">BUT WE TRIED TO INCLUDE ALL THE PARTS SO... YOU KNOW, I THINK GABBY&apos;S HAPPY WITH HOW IT CAME </p>
<p begin="00:00:59.793" end="00:01:03.197">OUT AND IT&apos;S... YOU KNOW, WE&apos;RE HAPPY WITH THE BOOK.</p>
<p begin="00:01:03.197" end="00:01:06.934">&gt;&gt; Jon: IS IT THERAPEUTIC TO WRITE THIS AFTER HAVING GONE THROUGH WHAT YOU GUYS WENT </p>
<p begin="00:01:06.934" end="00:01:07.835">THROUGH OVER THE PAST YEAR?</p>
<p begin="00:01:07.835" end="00:01:08.802">&gt;&gt; IT IS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:08.802" end="00:01:10.204">IT&apos;S SOMETIMES HARD, THOUGH.</p>
<p begin="00:01:10.204" end="00:01:14.842">YOU KNOW, WE... ESPECIALLY ON THE WEEKENDS WHEN I&apos;D SPEND A LOT OF TIME WITH HER GOING OVER </p>
<p begin="00:01:14.842" end="00:01:18.078">IT, IT&apos;S HARD TO RELIVE SOME OF THE STUFF, SOME OF THE PARTS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:18.078" end="00:01:20.414">WE&apos;D SOMETIMES HAVE TO TAKE A BREAK FROM IT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:20.414" end="00:01:24.885">BUT I THINK THE WHOLE EXPERIENCE FOR BOTH OF US WAS GENERALLY PRETTY POSITIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:24.885" end="00:01:29.323">&gt;&gt; Jon: I SAW SOME OF THE FOOTAGE, THE INTERVIEW WITH DIANE SAWYER, THE... YOU </p>
<p begin="00:01:29.323" end="00:01:35.262">RECORDED AN AWFUL LOT OF WHERE SHE&apos;S COME SINCE JANUARY UNTIL NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:01:35.262" end="00:01:37.998">IT&apos;S KIND OF... IT&apos;S AMAZING.</p>
<p begin="00:01:37.998" end="00:01:41.168">YOU FORGET THE TRAUMA WAS SO GREAT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:41.168" end="00:01:43.103">IT&apos;S REMARKABLE SHE&apos;S ALIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:43.103" end="00:01:46.006">&gt;&gt; I THINK WITHOUT THE VIDEO IN THE BEGINNING SOME PEOPLE </p>
<p begin="00:01:46.006" end="00:01:48.642">WOULDN&apos;T REALIZE WHAT THAT WHOLE JOURNEY WOULD BE LIKE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:48.642" end="00:01:50.210">WE TALK ABOUT IN THE THE BOOK.</p>
<p begin="00:01:50.210" end="00:01:51.445">BUT IT&apos;S SOMETHING TO SEE IT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:51.445" end="00:01:55.482">IT WASN&apos;T PLANNED I JUST THOUGHT, YOU KNOW, AT THE BEGINNING OF THIS THAT AT SOME </p>
<p begin="00:01:55.482" end="00:02:00.053">POINT SHE&apos;S GOING TO WANT TO SEE IT, NEVER THINKING WE MIGHT USE IT ON T.V.</p>
<p begin="00:02:00.053" end="00:02:03.524">&gt;&gt; Jon: THIS IS GOING TO SOUND LIKE A STRANGE OBSERVATION BUT IN READING IT, THERE WAS ONE </p>
<p begin="00:02:03.524" end="00:02:06.293">PART IN THERE THAT REALLY STRUCK ME AND IT&apos;S SUCH A SMALL THING.</p>
<p begin="00:02:06.293" end="00:02:09.663">YOU SAID THAT IN YOUR RELATIONSHIP SHE SPOKE 70% OF THE TIME.</p>
<p begin="00:02:09.663" end="00:02:10.230">&gt;&gt; AT LEAST.</p>
<p begin="00:02:10.230" end="00:02:11.965">I MEAN, SHE WAS A REAL TALKER.</p>
<p begin="00:02:11.965" end="00:02:14.935">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:02:14.935" end="00:02:19.673">&gt;&gt; Jon: SO ONCE THE ACCIDENT... YOU REALLY HAD TO DO-- ESPECIALLY IN THE </p>
<p begin="00:02:19.673" end="00:02:22.743">BEGINNING-- 100%, 95% OF THE TALKING.</p>
<p begin="00:02:22.743" end="00:02:24.144">I DON&apos;T KNOW IF PEOPLE REALIZE,</p>
<p begin="00:02:24.144" end="00:02:26.647">LIKE EVEN THAT, WHAT A DRASTIC CHANGE IN YOUR RELATIONSHIP.</p>
<p begin="00:02:26.647" end="00:02:27.281">&gt;&gt; BIG CHANGE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:27.281" end="00:02:29.316">IN THE BEGINNING IT WAS 100%,</p>
<p begin="00:02:29.316" end="00:02:36.256">FOR A LONG PERIOD OF TIME AND EVERYBODY AROUND HER AND SHE WAS SUCH A TALKATIVE PERSON AND </p>
<p begin="00:02:36.256" end="00:02:37.357">INQUISITIVE, AND SHE STILL IS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:37.357" end="00:02:38.725">THE DIFFERENCE IS NOW I&apos;M...</p>
<p begin="00:02:38.725" end="00:02:41.395">EVEN TODAY I&apos;M CARRYING MOST OF THE CONVERSATION.</p>
<p begin="00:02:41.395" end="00:02:43.397">IT&apos;S CHANGING ON A WEEKLY BASIS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:43.397" end="00:02:44.665">SHE&apos;S GETTING BET WE ARE THAT,</p>
<p begin="00:02:44.665" end="00:02:46.533">BUT IT WAS A BIG CHANGE FOR US.</p>
<p begin="00:02:46.533" end="00:02:50.103">&gt;&gt; Jon: HOW DID... I&apos;M READING THE THIS STORY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:50.103" end="00:02:54.875">YOU&apos;RE A KID FROM NEW JERSEY-- SUCH AS MYSELF-- THE SAME SIZE...</p>
<p begin="00:02:54.875" end="00:02:57.110">(LAUGHTER).</p>
<p begin="00:02:57.110" end="00:03:01.715">AND YET YOU END UP IN SPACE MARRIED TO A CONGRESSWOMAN.</p>
<p begin="00:03:01.715" end="00:03:03.050">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:03:03.050" end="00:03:06.053">&gt;&gt; A JEWISH CONGRESSWOMAN.</p>
<p begin="00:03:06.053" end="00:03:12.059">&gt;&gt; Jon: AND I&apos;M MARRIED TO A CATHOLIC WOMAN AND I&apos;VE NEVER LEFT THE TRISTATE AREA.</p>
<p begin="00:03:12.059" end="00:03:15.562">(APPLAUSE) SO REALLY SHOULDN&apos;T WE BE MORE... WE&apos;RE COMPADRES.</p>
<p begin="00:03:15.562" end="00:03:19.399">I WOULD SAY TWIN SONS BUT OFF TWIN BROTHER WHO HAS ALSO BEEN THE TO SPACE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:19.399" end="00:03:21.869">&gt;&gt; I THINK YOU COULD PROBABLY DO MY JOB BUT I DON&apos;T THINK I&apos;D </p>
<p begin="00:03:21.869" end="00:03:24.771">HAVE IT... I WOULDN&apos;T BE ABLE TO SIT THERE AND DO WHAT YOU DO.</p>
<p begin="00:03:24.771" end="00:03:27.374">&gt;&gt; Jon: MARK, THERE IS NO WAY I CAN DO YOUR JOB.</p>
<p begin="00:03:27.374" end="00:03:29.109">(LAUGHTER) THERE IS GOOD STUFF IN HERE,</p>
<p begin="00:03:29.109" end="00:03:35.115">TOO, ABOUT THE PRESSURES... YOU KNOW, YOU FLEW YOUR FINAL MISSION AND THE FINAL SHUTTLE </p>
<p begin="00:03:35.115" end="00:03:40.654">MISSION WHILE YOU WERE ALSO FEELING VERY RESPONSIBLE FOR A LOT OF GABBY&apos;S RECOVERY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:40.654" end="00:03:42.322">HOW DIFFICULT WAS THAT DECISION TO MAKE?</p>
<p begin="00:03:42.322" end="00:03:43.590">&gt;&gt; IT WAS REALLY HARD.</p>
<p begin="00:03:43.590" end="00:03:48.428">I WANTED HER TO BE MORE OF A PART OF THE DECISION WHEN WE MADE IT BUT SHE WASN&apos;T REALLY </p>
<p begin="00:03:48.428" end="00:03:53.200">ABLE TO EXPRESS HERSELF THAT WELL THEN SO I JUST KIND OF TOOK A LEAP OF FAITH.</p>
<p begin="00:03:53.200" end="00:03:58.005">NOW, I DO KNOW HER REALLY WELL AND I KNEW ONE THING I WASN&apos;T GOING TO DO IS HEAR FOR THE REST </p>
<p begin="00:03:58.005" end="00:04:02.042">OF MY LIFE &quot;HOW DID YOU GIVE THAT UP BECAUSE OF WHAT HAPPENED TO ME?&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:04:02.042" end="00:04:06.513">AND SO SHE&apos;S VERY... VERY HAPPY WITH THE DECISION.</p>
<p begin="00:04:06.513" end="00:04:09.449">IT&apos;S REMARKABLE HOW THE TWO OF YOU PUSH EACH OTHER VERY WELL,</p>
<p begin="00:04:09.449" end="00:04:11.919">URGE EACH OTHER ON, MOTIVATE EACH OTHER.</p>
<p begin="00:04:11.919" end="00:04:18.725">BACK IN THE DAY SHE&apos;S TRYING TO MOTIVATE YOU TO MOVE ON FROM MAYBE JOINING... BECOMING AN </p>
<p begin="00:04:18.725" end="00:04:21.195">ADMIRAL AND GOING TO THE JOINT CHIEFS AND NOW WITH HER RECOVERY </p>
<p begin="00:04:21.195" end="00:04:27.534">YOU&apos;RE ALWAYS SAYING TO HER &quot;NOT GOOD ENOUGH, FORM A WORD, WHAT WORD IS THAT?</p>
<p begin="00:04:27.534" end="00:04:32.973">KEEP GOING, GABBY.&quot; THE TWO OF YOU... DID YOU ALWAYS HAVE A RELATIONSHIP THAT WAS...</p>
<p begin="00:04:32.973" end="00:04:34.608">YOU COULD MOTIVATE EACH OTHER VERY WELL?</p>
<p begin="00:04:34.608" end="00:04:35.876">&gt;&gt; I THINK SO.</p>
<p begin="00:04:35.876" end="00:04:37.878">WE ALWAYS COMPLEMENTED EACH OTHER PRETTY WELL.</p>
<p begin="00:04:37.878" end="00:04:42.082">SHE WAS ALWAYS A BIG FAN OF MY MILITARY SERVICE AND MY CAREER AND ALWAYS TRIED TO PUSH ME </p>
<p begin="00:04:42.082" end="00:04:47.754">ALONG WITH THAT AND NOW... TODAY IN THE SITUATION WE&apos;RE IN I&apos;M DOING A LOT MORE OF THE </p>
<p begin="00:04:47.754" end="00:04:51.959">ENCOURAGING BUT I KNOW THAT&apos;S GOING TO GET PROBABLY BACK TO MORE OF A BALANCE EVENTUALLY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:51.959" end="00:04:53.327">LOOKING FORWARD TO THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:53.327" end="00:04:59.099">&gt;&gt; Jon: DO YOU THINK IN HER MIND, ARE HER THOUGHTS MORE SOPHISTICATED TAN HER ABILITY TO COMMUNICATE?</p>
<p begin="00:04:59.099" end="00:05:01.168">IS THAT SOMETHING THAT YOU&apos;RE ABLE TO DISERN?</p>
<p begin="00:05:01.168" end="00:05:03.070">&gt;&gt; ABSOLUTELY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:03.070" end="00:05:09.076">HER COGNITION AND HER ABILITY TO UNDERSTAND EVERYTHING AND UNDERSTAND WHAT PEOPLE SAY </p>
<p begin="00:05:09.076" end="00:05:12.679">AND... A COUPLE PEOPLE ASKED ME THIS WEEK BEING UP HERE WOULD SHE RECOGNIZE ME.</p>
<p begin="00:05:12.679" end="00:05:13.146">WELL, OF COURSE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:13.146" end="00:05:14.848">I MEAN, IF SHE KNEW YOU BEFORE,</p>
<p begin="00:05:14.848" end="00:05:17.551">SHE&apos;S GOING TO KNOW YOU NOW JUST THE SAME AS ALWAYS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:17.551" end="00:05:19.253">SO THOSE THINGS HAVEN&apos;T CHANGED.</p>
<p begin="00:05:19.253" end="00:05:21.889">IT&apos;S JUST THE COMMUNICATION SHE STRUGGLES WITH.</p>
<p begin="00:05:21.889" end="00:05:24.658">BUT IT&apos;S... YOU KNOW, LEAPS AND BOUNDS EVERY WEEK.</p>
<p begin="00:05:24.658" end="00:05:27.594">&gt;&gt; Jon: AND HOW ARE HER DOCTORS FEELING ABOUT ALL THAT?</p>
<p begin="00:05:27.594" end="00:05:30.330">SHE&apos;S NOW MUCH MORE AN OUTPATIENT BUT STILL DOING THERAPY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:30.330" end="00:05:34.468">SHE PASSED UP... SHE WAS GOING TO HAVE A MEETING WITH PRESIDENT OBAMA, HAD TO FLY BACK FOR REHAB.</p>
<p begin="00:05:34.468" end="00:05:35.936">SHE STILL STICKS TO THAT SCHEDULE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:35.936" end="00:05:39.373">&gt;&gt; SHE DOESN&apos;T MISS MANY DAYS OF THERAPY NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:05:39.373" end="00:05:44.912">WITH THE SHOW ON TONIGHT SHE MAY HAVE TO TAKE A DAY OFF TOMORROW SO SHE CAN WATCH YOUR SHOW.</p>
<p begin="00:05:44.912" end="00:05:45.312">(LAUGHTER).</p>
<p begin="00:05:45.312" end="00:05:47.814">&gt;&gt; Jon: I THINK IT&apos;S IMPORTANT TO WATCH THE SHOW AND MISS REHAB.</p>
<p begin="00:05:47.814" end="00:05:49.449">&gt;&gt; THE HIGHLIGHT OF HER DAY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:49.449" end="00:05:51.084">&gt;&gt; Jon: TO WATCH YOU ON THIS SHOW?</p>
<p begin="00:05:51.084" end="00:05:55.389">&gt;&gt; NO, TO WATCH YOU, WATCH &quot;THE DAILY SHOW.&quot; SHE WATCHES VERY... ON THE </p>
<p begin="00:05:55.389" end="00:05:59.626">WEEKENDS SHE WATCHES THE NEWS PROGRAMS BUT DURING THE WEEK AFTER DINNER SHE WATCHES &quot;THE </p>
<p begin="00:05:59.626" end="00:06:02.095">DAILY SHOW&quot; FROM THE NIGHT BEFORE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:02.095" end="00:06:03.230">(AUDIENCE REACTS) SNEUL REAPLY.</p>
<p begin="00:06:03.230" end="00:06:03.864">&gt;&gt; THAT&apos;S RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:03.864" end="00:06:07.334">&gt;&gt; Jon: I&apos;M GOING TO HAVE DO A BETTER JOB!</p>
<p begin="00:06:07.334" end="00:06:11.805">(LAUGHS) NOW THAT I KNOW IMPORTANT PEOPLE ARE WATCHING I HAVE TO TRY A LITTLE HARDER.</p>
<p begin="00:06:11.805" end="00:06:13.173">NOW WHAT ABOUT YOU?</p>
<p begin="00:06:13.173" end="00:06:14.041">YOU&apos;RE A GUY.</p>
<p begin="00:06:14.041" end="00:06:16.109">YOU&apos;VE ALWAYS BEEN RUNNING AROUND.</p>
<p begin="00:06:16.109" end="00:06:17.644">HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT WHAT YOU WANT TO DO NEXT?</p>
<p begin="00:06:17.644" end="00:06:22.449">&gt;&gt; WELL, THE BIGGEST THING I WANT TO DO IS MAKE SURE THAT SHE HAS EVERYTHING SHE NEEDS TO GET BETTER.</p>
<p begin="00:06:22.449" end="00:06:28.856">SHE WANTS TO GET BACK TO SOUTHERN ARIZONA, SERVE HER CON ONSTITUENTS, GET BACK TOC CONGRESS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:28.856" end="00:06:33.527">SHE&apos;S GOING TO MAKE THIS DECISION ON HER OWN TERMS WHEN SHE&apos;S READY TO MAKE THE DECISION </p>
<p begin="00:06:33.527" end="00:06:34.595">AND WE&apos;LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:34.595" end="00:06:37.297">BUT I THEME TO SUPPORT HER FOR NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:06:37.297" end="00:06:38.065">&gt;&gt; Jon: WOW.</p>
<p begin="00:06:38.065" end="00:06:43.604">IT&apos;S AN INCREDIBLY MOVING AND WONDERFUL STORY AND I WISH THE TWO OF YOU THE GREATEST SUCCESS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:43.604" end="00:06:45.072">SO NICE TO SEE YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:06:45.072" end="00:06:46.874">AND PLEASE WISH HER WELL FOR ME.</p>
<p begin="00:06:46.874" end="00:06:50.577">OH, I&apos;LL JUST SAY IT MYSELF SINCE I KNOW SHE&apos;S WATCHING.</p>
<p begin="00:06:50.577" end="00:06:52.613">DOES SHE FAST FORWARD THROUGH THE COMMERCIALS?</p>
<p begin="00:06:52.613" end="00:06:57.885">&gt;&gt; Jon: I WAS DOING THAT SO SHE&apos;S PROBABLY GOING TO DO IT TONIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:57.885" end="00:07:01.922">&gt;&gt; Jon: ON THE BOOKSHELVES NOW, MARK KELLY.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
