<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:02.302" end="00:00:02.903">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE).</p>
<p begin="00:00:02.903" end="00:00:05.439">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELCOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:05.439" end="00:00:09.309">LAST WEEK WE WERE TALKING... THE SUPREME COURT OF THE UNITED STATES HEARD ARGUMENTS IN THE </p>
<p begin="00:00:09.309" end="00:00:12.079">LANDMARK CASE OF OBAMACARE V.</p>
<p begin="00:00:12.079" end="00:00:13.180">FREEDOM AND...</p>
<p begin="00:00:13.180" end="00:00:13.580">(LAUGHTER).</p>
<p begin="00:00:13.580" end="00:00:16.817">FROM NOW UNTIL THE COURT&apos;S JUNE DECISION ALL WE CAN DO IS WAIT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:16.817" end="00:00:20.187">UNLESS SOMEONE WANTS TO MAKE SOME KIND OF POST-CLOSING ARGUMENT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:20.187" end="00:00:26.560">&gt;&gt; ULTIMATELY I&apos;M CONFIDENT THAT THE SUPREME COURT WILL NOT TAKE </p>
<p begin="00:00:26.560" end="00:00:35.402">WHAT WOULD BE AN UNPRECEDENTED EXTRAORDINARY STEP OF OVERTURNING A LAW THAT WAS </p>
<p begin="00:00:35.402" end="00:00:44.411">PASSED BY A STRONG MAJORITY OF A DEMOCRATICALLY ELECTED CONGRESS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:44.411" end="00:00:47.381">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELL, THAT WAS VAGUELY AND HALTINGLY THREATENING.</p>
<p begin="00:00:47.381" end="00:00:50.684">(LAUGHTER) YEAH, I&apos;M SURE THE COURT WILL CONSIDER THE PRECEDENT SET FORTH </p>
<p begin="00:00:50.684" end="00:00:54.755">IN THE CASE OF &quot;THAT&apos;S A LOVELY FAMILY YOU GOT THERE&quot; V. &quot;IT </p>
<p begin="00:00:54.755" end="00:00:59.826">WOULD BE A SHAME OF ANYTHING HAPPENED TO THEM.&quot; (LAUGHTER) CONSERVATIVES POINTED OUT </p>
<p begin="00:00:59.826" end="00:01:01.528">LIBERALS DON&apos;T UNDERSTAND JUDICIAL REVIEW.</p>
<p begin="00:01:01.528" end="00:01:08.235">&gt;&gt; THAT WAS ESTABLISHED BY MARBURY V. MADISON BACK IN THE EARLY 1800s AND EVER SINCE </p>
<p begin="00:01:08.235" end="00:01:13.740">THEN NO SERIOUS LEGAL SCHOLAR IN 175 YEARS HAS QUESTIONED WHETHER OR NOT THE SUPREME COURT CAN </p>
<p begin="00:01:13.740" end="00:01:16.710">THROW OUT A LAW THAT IS UNCONSTITUTIONAL.</p>
<p begin="00:01:16.710" end="00:01:22.216">&gt;&gt; Jon: YEAH, WE ALL HAVE WIKIPEDIA.</p>
<p begin="00:01:22.216" end="00:01:25.085">(LAUGHTER) THAT&apos;S JUST WHAT CONSERVATIVES BELIEVE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:25.085" end="00:01:29.456">THE JUDICIAL BRANCH&apos;S JOB IS TO DETERMINE WHAT LAW IS UNCONSTITUTIONAL AND THROW THEM OUT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:29.456" end="00:01:31.124">THAT&apos;S WHAT CONSERVATIVES BELIEVE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:31.124" end="00:01:31.458">WELL...</p>
<p begin="00:01:31.458" end="00:01:35.495">&gt;&gt; CALIFORNIA ALONG WITH SO MANY OTHER STATES DEFINING TRADITIONALLY WHAT MARRIAGE IS </p>
<p begin="00:01:35.495" end="00:01:44.738">AND TO SEE THAT THIRD BRANCH OF GOVERNMENT UNDERDOING THE WILL OF THE PEOPLE IT&apos;S FRUSTRATING.</p>
<p begin="00:01:44.738" end="00:01:47.140">&gt;&gt; Jon: THAT&apos;S DIFFERENT THAT WAS A LAW BANNING GAY MARRIAGE </p>
<p begin="00:01:47.140" end="00:01:49.943">BECAUSE THEY DIDN&apos;T WANT JUDGES TO INTERVEER.</p>
<p begin="00:01:49.943" end="00:01:53.413">LIBERALS ARE CONSISTENT THAT THEY DON&apos;T WANT JUDGES TO INTERFERE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:53.413" end="00:01:54.214">&gt;&gt; IT&apos;S BEEN A TRUE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:54.214" end="00:01:56.483">THEY COURTS HAVE THE AUTHORITY TO SAY WHAT THE LAW IS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:56.483" end="00:02:00.954">EVEN TO INVALIDATE STATUTES ENACTED BY THE ELECTED BRANCHES OF GOVERNMENT WHEN THEY CONFLICT </p>
<p begin="00:02:00.954" end="00:02:02.689">WITH THE CONSTITUTION.</p>
<p begin="00:02:02.689" end="00:02:07.561">&gt;&gt; Jon: RIGHT, BUT UNLESS THE LAW IS WITH REGARD TO HEALTH CARE WHICH LIBERALS DON&apos;T </p>
<p begin="00:02:07.561" end="00:02:11.265">WANT... THINGS CONSERVATIVES WOULD LIKE TO OVERTURN BECAUSE UNELECTED JUDGES SHOULD HAVE </p>
<p begin="00:02:11.265" end="00:02:12.065">THAT POWER TO DO THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:12.065" end="00:02:15.669">&gt;&gt; WE CONSERVATIVES STAND FOR CAUSES THAT ARE TOO IMPORTANT TO </p>
<p begin="00:02:15.669" end="00:02:20.073">ALLOW UNELECTED JUDGES TO FORCE THEIR OWN BIASES ON AN UNWILLING NATION.</p>
<p begin="00:02:20.073" end="00:02:20.474">&gt;&gt; Jon: RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:20.474" end="00:02:22.409">BUT THAT WAS... YOU SAID THAT THREE YEARS AGO.</p>
<p begin="00:02:22.409" end="00:02:23.977">LORD KNOWS WHAT YOU THINK NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:02:23.977" end="00:02:30.851">(LAUGHTER) MEANWHILE CONSERVATIVES AND LIBERALS, WHILE THEY&apos;RE BUSY </p>
<p begin="00:02:30.851" end="00:02:34.221">EXCHANGING PLACES WITH EACH OTHER&apos;S MOST DEEPLY HELD CONVICTIONS EVERYONE SHOULD LOOK </p>
<p begin="00:02:34.221" end="00:02:37.157">OVER HERE BECAUSE I THINK THOSE JUSTICES MIGHT BE UP TO SOMETHING.</p>
<p begin="00:02:37.157" end="00:02:41.361">&gt;&gt; THE SUPREME COURT HAS RULED POLICE NOW HAVE THE RIGHT TO STRIP SEARCH ANYONE BOOKED INTO </p>
<p begin="00:02:41.361" end="00:02:48.001">JAIL, EVEN PEOPLE WHO COMMIT MINOR OFFENSES LIKE FAILING TO WEAR A SEAT BELT, MAKING AN </p>
<p begin="00:02:48.001" end="00:02:50.370">ILLEGAL U-TURN OR EATING ON THE SUBWAY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:50.370" end="00:02:51.705">GET IT?</p>
<p begin="00:02:51.705" end="00:02:57.244">WHILE EVERYONE&apos;S CIRCLE JERKING HEALTH CARE THE COURT JUST COD PAID TO STRIP SEARCHES FOR ANYTHING.</p>
<p begin="00:02:57.244" end="00:02:57.544">EVER.</p>
<p begin="00:02:57.544" end="00:03:01.048">TRAFFIC TICKETS, JAYWALKING.</p>
<p begin="00:03:01.048" end="00:03:01.381">PROTESTING.</p>
<p begin="00:03:01.381" end="00:03:06.286">IF THAT DOESN&apos;T SEND A CHILL UP YOUR NOW-UNCOVERED SPINE HOW ABOUT THIS?</p>
<p begin="00:03:06.286" end="00:03:11.058">WHAT IF SOMEDAY MATT LAUER MAKES AN ILLEGAL U-TURN?</p>
<p begin="00:03:11.058" end="00:03:11.358">YEAH!</p>
<p begin="00:03:11.358" end="00:03:13.894">THAT&apos;S RIGHT!</p>
<p begin="00:03:13.894" end="00:03:18.932">THE RULING THAT ANYONE WHO&apos;S ARRESTED EVEN ACCIDENTALLY CAN BE STRIP SEARCHED WAS DECIDED </p>
<p begin="00:03:18.932" end="00:03:24.872">5-4 WITH THE VOTES FOR THE SEARCHES COMING FROM THE FIVE CONSERVATIVES, YOU KNOW, THE </p>
<p begin="00:03:24.872" end="00:03:27.708">DEFENDING PERSONAL LIBERTY GUYS WHICH IS WEIRD BECAUSE I&apos;M NOT A </p>
<p begin="00:03:27.708" end="00:03:30.677">CONSTITUTIONAL SCHOLAR BUT I&apos;M WILLING TO GET BIG GOVERNMENTS </p>
<p begin="00:03:30.677" end="00:03:35.148">ITS BIGGEST WHEN IT&apos;S INSIDE YOUR ANUS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:35.148" end="00:03:39.286">(LAUGHTER) A SWING VOTE GUY, KENNEDY, YOU WROTE IN THIS GEM.</p>
<p begin="00:03:39.286" end="00:03:39.820">EXPLAIN YOURSELF.</p>
<p begin="00:03:39.820" end="00:03:43.857">&gt;&gt; JUSTICE ANTHONY KENNEDY SAID PEOPLE PICKED UP FOR THE MOST MINOR OFFENSES CAN TURN OUT TO </p>
<p begin="00:03:43.857" end="00:03:48.629">BE DANGEROUS CRIMINALS NOTING THAT OKLAHOMA CITY BOMBER TIMOTHY McVEIGH WAS ORIGINALLY </p>
<p begin="00:03:48.629" end="00:03:51.498">ARRESTED FOR DRIVING WITHOUT A LICENSE PLATE ON HIS CAR.</p>
<p begin="00:03:51.498" end="00:03:56.303">&gt;&gt; OH, RIGHT AND BECAUSE WE DIDN&apos;T STRIP SEARCH HIM YOU NEVER FOUND THE EXPLOSIVE-PACKED </p>
<p begin="00:03:56.303" end="00:04:00.841">VAN HE WAS HIDING IN HIS ASS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:00.841" end="00:04:04.311">(LAUGHTER) I GUESS THE JUDICIAL PRINCIPAL IS SINCE ANYONE COULD BE A </p>
<p begin="00:04:04.311" end="00:04:09.316">CRIMINAL LET&apos;S TREAT EVERYONE LIKE THEY&apos;RE CRIMINALS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:09.316" end="00:04:12.085">WHICH AT LEAST TAKES US A STEP CLOSER TO HEALTH CARE REFORM.</p>
<p begin="00:04:12.085" end="00:04:18.825">IF WE COULD TRAIN POLICE TO DIAGNOSE PROSTATE TUMORS WE&apos;RE JUST ONE BURRITO AWAY FROM A SCREENING!</p>
<p begin="00:04:18.825" end="00:04:19.560">WE&apos;LL BE RIGHT </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
