<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:03.737" end="00:00:05.472">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) </p>
<p begin="00:00:05.472" end="00:00:07.474">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELCOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:07.474" end="00:00:12.346">THE PULITZER PRIZE WINNING AUTHOR, HIS NEW BOOK IS CALLED &quot;CONFIDENCE MEN: WALL STREET,</p>
<p begin="00:00:12.346" end="00:00:18.118">WASHINGTON, AND THE EDUCATION OF A PRESIDENT.&quot; PLEASE WELCOME BACK TO THE SHOW RON SUSKIND.</p>
<p begin="00:00:18.118" end="00:00:26.460">(APPLAUSE) NICE TO SEE YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:00:26.460" end="00:00:28.896">&quot;CONFIDENCE MEN: WALL STREET,</p>
<p begin="00:00:28.896" end="00:00:32.933">WASHINGTON&quot; AND, OF COURSE, THE EDUCATION OF A PRESIDENT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:32.933" end="00:00:39.873">I&apos;VE ALWAYS FOUND THE EDUCATION OF A PRESIDENT TO BE SOMETHING THAT YOU WOULD LIKE TO HAPPEN </p>
<p begin="00:00:39.873" end="00:00:43.877">PREVIOUS TO THEIR PRESIDENTING.</p>
<p begin="00:00:43.877" end="00:00:52.653">THIS REPRESENTS A VERY CREDIBLE CASE THAT HE WAS A FRESHMAN AND RECEIVED WHAT MAY BE PERCEIVED </p>
<p begin="00:00:52.653" end="00:00:56.056">AS AN ECONOMIC TEAM WEDGIE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:56.056" end="00:01:00.427">(LAUGHTER) YOUR THOUGHTS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:00.427" end="00:01:02.229">&gt;&gt; WHATEVER YOU SAID, I THINK THAT SOUNDS RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:02.229" end="00:01:06.300">HE ARRIVES HERE AS AN UNTESTED LEADER IN A LOT OF WAYS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:06.300" end="00:01:07.935">I CALL HIM AN AMATEUR PRESIDENT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:07.935" end="00:01:14.641">HE IS BRILLIANT, HE IS SOMEONE PEOPLE PAINT YEARNINGS ON, HE RISES AT A MOMENT OF CRISIS AND </p>
<p begin="00:01:14.641" end="00:01:21.715">HE SURROUNDS HIMSELF WHEN HE HAS A KIND OF COLD SWEAT MOMENT WITH OLD SEASONED HANDS-- MANY OF </p>
<p begin="00:01:21.715" end="00:01:25.853">THEM FROM BILL CLINTON-- AND WHAT YOU&apos;VE GOT IS, WELL, WHAT WE&apos;VE GOT RIGHT NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:01:25.853" end="00:01:27.120">IT WAS VERY DIFFICULT FOR HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:01:27.120" end="00:01:32.159">PEOPLE WILL FEEL SOME SYMPATHY FOR HIM, ACTUALLY MAYBE A LOT OF SYMPATHY FOR WHAT BARACK OBAMA </p>
<p begin="00:01:32.159" end="00:01:35.729">FACED AT THIS MOMENT BASED ON WHAT HE BROUGHT TO THE TABLE,</p>
<p begin="00:01:35.729" end="00:01:36.196">UNDERSTANDABLY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:36.196" end="00:01:38.465">AND IT&apos;S QUITE A BATTLE THROUGH THE TWO YEARS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:38.465" end="00:01:42.603">NOW OBAMA SAYS IN THE FINAL INTERVIEW &quot;I&apos;VE GROWN.</p>
<p begin="00:01:42.603" end="00:01:45.506">YES, WHAT&apos;S IN THE BOOK IS TRUE BUT I&apos;VE LEARNED HARD LESSONS </p>
<p begin="00:01:45.506" end="00:01:48.475">FROM THIS AND I&apos;VE BECOME THE PRESIDENT PEOPLE WANT AND DESERVE.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:01:48.475" end="00:01:50.444">BUT THAT WILL BE SOMETHING PEOPLE JUDGE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:50.444" end="00:01:52.980">&gt;&gt; Jon: WHY DO PEOPLE TALK TO YOU?</p>
<p begin="00:01:52.980" end="00:02:07.494">(LAUGHTER) BECAUSE A LOT OF PEOPLE TALK TO YOU IN THIS BOOK.</p>
<p begin="00:02:07.494" end="00:02:08.295">&gt;&gt; EVERYBODY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:08.295" end="00:02:09.796">&gt;&gt; Jon: EVERYBODY GOES ON RECORD.</p>
<p begin="00:02:09.796" end="00:02:14.801">DO THEY THINK IN THIS... ARE YOU THEIR CHANCE?</p>
<p begin="00:02:14.801" end="00:02:17.638">ARE YOU A LIFE PRESERVER TO THEIR REPUTATION?</p>
<p begin="00:02:17.638" end="00:02:22.976">DOES THE PRESIDENT... IS THE THOUGHT THAT WE WANT TO CHRONICLE THIS FOR HISTORICAL </p>
<p begin="00:02:22.976" end="00:02:28.081">PURPOSES OVERWHELM MAYBE A PRUDENT STEP BACK?</p>
<p begin="00:02:28.081" end="00:02:29.816">WHY DO YOU THINK IT IS?</p>
<p begin="00:02:29.816" end="00:02:34.288">&gt;&gt; PEOPLE COME TO SOMEONE LIKE ME AND HAVE FOR NOW... THIS IS THE FIFTH BOOK.</p>
<p begin="00:02:34.288" end="00:02:40.227">FOR ALL KINDS OF REASONS, BUT I THINK IT&apos;S CLEAR THAT A LOT OF THEM FEEL THAT THEY WERE FRONT </p>
<p begin="00:02:40.227" end="00:02:44.231">SEATS IN BIG MOMENTS OF HISTORY AND THEY SAY &quot;I NEED TO TELL YOU WHAT I SAW.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:02:44.231" end="00:02:47.467">NOW THE ADVISORS ARE INTERESTING AND THE BOOK IS FULL OF THEM BUT </p>
<p begin="00:02:47.467" end="00:02:51.738">THE REASON YOU&apos;RE INTERESTED IN THEM IS BECAUSE THEY GIVE YOU A GLIMPSE OF THE MAN, THE </p>
<p begin="00:02:51.738" end="00:02:56.577">PRESIDENT, THE DECIDER, SO TO SPEAK, INTO THE MAN OF THIS MOMENT AND THIS PERIOD.</p>
<p begin="00:02:56.577" end="00:02:57.511">&gt;&gt; Jon: RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:57.511" end="00:03:03.183">&gt;&gt; NOW INTERESTINGLY WHAT YOU FIND HERE IS OBAMA&apos;S WRESTLING WITH HIS ADVISORS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:03.183" end="00:03:05.586">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELL, THERE&apos;S A...</p>
<p begin="00:03:05.586" end="00:03:11.291">PROBABLY THE MOST DIFFICULT THING IN THE BOOK FOR OBAMA IS THE SENSE THAT HE SITS BACK AND </p>
<p begin="00:03:11.291" end="00:03:18.732">ALLOWS WHAT WOULD BE HIS NATURAL INSTINCTS... YOU KNOW, YOU SAY HE PROMOTED THE SWEDISH MODEL </p>
<p begin="00:03:18.732" end="00:03:21.969">AND THEY WENT &quot;NO&quot; AND HE WENT &quot;ALL RIGHT.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:03:21.969" end="00:03:26.173">&gt;&gt; IT DOES NOT PAINT A STRONG LEADERSHIP POSITION FOR IT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:26.173" end="00:03:30.077">IT&apos;S INTERESTING, THE FIRST FEW MONTHS OF THIS PRESIDENCY IS CLEARLY THE CRUCIAL TIME.</p>
<p begin="00:03:30.077" end="00:03:32.613">HE&apos;S GOT A 75% APPROVAL RATING,</p>
<p begin="00:03:32.613" end="00:03:37.284">TWO MILLION PEOPLE WERE WEEPING ON THE MALL IN JANUARY AND YOU CAN FEEL AND THINK I CAN DO THIS </p>
<p begin="00:03:37.284" end="00:03:41.622">I CAN BE THIS LARGER-THAN-LIFE PRESIDENT AND YOU SEE HIM KIND OF GETTING THE WIND KNOCKED OUT </p>
<p begin="00:03:41.622" end="00:03:47.294">OF HIM BY MARCH AND IT&apos;S HARD TO READ BECAUSE YOU CAN SEE HIM REACHING FOR BIG IDEAS,</p>
<p begin="00:03:47.294" end="00:03:52.299">ESPECIALLY RESTRUCTURING, TAKING DOWN SOME OF THE BIG BANGS, THAT DOESN&apos;T HAPPEN.</p>
<p begin="00:03:52.299" end="00:03:55.636">AND AFTER THAT YOU HAVE MORE INCIDENTS LIKE THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:55.636" end="00:03:58.372">ALL THE WAY THROUGH TO 2010, THE BEGINNING OF 2010 WHEN HE GETS A </p>
<p begin="00:03:58.372" end="00:04:02.442">MEMO, THERE&apos;S LOTS OF MEMOS IN THERE FROM PETE ROUSE, THE TOP </p>
<p begin="00:04:02.442" end="00:04:06.046">ADVISOR SAYING &quot;LOOK, YOU NEED TO TAKE CONTROL OF THIS BUILDING YOU ARE THE PRESIDENT.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:04:06.046" end="00:04:11.518">AND THIS MEMO WAS KIND OF A BLUEPRINT FOR MOSTLY ALL THE STAFF, THE FIRST STAFF LEAVING </p>
<p begin="00:04:11.518" end="00:04:15.856">AND OBAMA AFTER THE MIDTERMS HE SAYS TO ME I FEEL LIKE NOW I&apos;M </p>
<p begin="00:04:15.856" end="00:04:18.592">KIND OF GETTING MY RHYTHM, I&apos;M HERE NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:04:18.592" end="00:04:23.096">WITH A NEW STAFF THAT CAN DO WHAT I NEED BUT THAT&apos;S FOR FOLKS TO JUDGE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:23.096" end="00:04:28.202">&gt;&gt; WELL, THE DIFFICULTTY HERE IS THE FEELING OF OPPORTUNITY SQUANDERED.</p>
<p begin="00:04:28.202" end="00:04:35.342">THE HARDEST THING TO READ IN IT IS THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN OBAMA AS A CAMPAIGNER AND HOW HE... HE </p>
<p begin="00:04:35.342" end="00:04:37.678">REALLY DID REPUDIATE HIS OWN CAMPAIGN.</p>
<p begin="00:04:37.678" end="00:04:42.649">HE RAN AS A GUY WHO SAID THE DEFINITION OF INSANITY IS HAVE THE SAME PEOPLE AND EXPECT </p>
<p begin="00:04:42.649" end="00:04:43.183">DIFFERENT RESULTS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:43.183" end="00:04:46.386">AS SOON AS THE FINANCIAL CRISIS HIT-- AND IT DOESN&apos;T HIT WHILE </p>
<p begin="00:04:46.386" end="00:04:50.123">HE&apos;S IN OFFICE, IT&apos;S BEFORE-- HE HIRES LARRY SUMMERS WHO, BY THE </p>
<p begin="00:04:50.123" end="00:04:55.829">WAY, I THINK BY UNANIMOUS CONSENT IS AN AS (BLEEP).</p>
<p begin="00:04:55.829" end="00:04:59.399">(LAUGHTER) LIKE I&apos;VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING...</p>
<p begin="00:04:59.399" end="00:05:01.602">(APPLAUSE) LIKE NORMFULLY THESE BOOKS...</p>
<p begin="00:05:01.602" end="00:05:05.672">AND, BY THE WAY, IT DOESN&apos;T FEEL LIKE A PREJUDICE THING, LIKE </p>
<p begin="00:05:05.672" end="00:05:07.641">YOU&apos;RE LOOKING FOR A NARRATIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:07.641" end="00:05:09.610">IT DOES FEEL FAIR-MINDED BUT,</p>
<p begin="00:05:09.610" end="00:05:14.948">MAN, WHEN YOU INTERVIEWED, I THINK, HIS FAMILY AND THEY...</p>
<p begin="00:05:14.948" end="00:05:16.750">NO, THAT&apos;S NOT IN THERE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:16.750" end="00:05:17.084">BUT...</p>
<p begin="00:05:17.084" end="00:05:19.887">&gt;&gt; WELL, HE SPEAKS SO HIGHLY OF YOU, JON.</p>
<p begin="00:05:19.887" end="00:05:21.088">&gt;&gt; Jon: REALLY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:21.088" end="00:05:21.755">HE DOES?</p>
<p begin="00:05:21.755" end="00:05:25.726">BUT IT&apos;S ASTONISHING TO SEE SUCH A CLEAR PORTRAYAL OF ONE INDIVIDUAL.</p>
<p begin="00:05:25.726" end="00:05:28.695">&gt;&gt; THERE ARE LOTS OF THEM IN THIS MIX BUT, LARRY, LOOK, HE&apos;S </p>
<p begin="00:05:28.695" end="00:05:32.733">OFTEN BEEN HIS OWN WORST ENEMY THROUGH A LONG PERIOD ON THE PUBLIC STAGE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:32.733" end="00:05:37.104">HERE HE SAYS, OF COURSE, ONE OF THE SIGNATURE QUOTES OF THIS PERIOD WHICH IS THE FAMOUS NOW </p>
<p begin="00:05:37.104" end="00:05:38.305">&quot;HOME ALONE&quot; QUOTE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:38.305" end="00:05:42.509">WE&apos;RE HOME ALONE, THERE&apos;S NO ADULT IN CHARGE AND CLINTON WOULD NEVER MAKE THESE MISTAKES.</p>
<p begin="00:05:42.509" end="00:05:46.680">HE SAYS THIS A LOT LEAVING MEETINGS IN THE OVAL OFFICE WITH THE PRESIDENT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:46.680" end="00:05:51.585">LOTS OF PEOPLE HEAR THIS AND THEY&apos;RE TROUBLED BY IT, THEY SAY IS LARRY RIGHT ABOUT THIS OR NOT?</p>
<p begin="00:05:51.585" end="00:05:53.720">AND THEY WRESTLE WITH IT THROUGH THE PERIOD OF THIS PRESIDENCY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:53.720" end="00:05:57.257">&gt;&gt; BUT YOU SAY EVERYBODY HATES SUMMERS BUT OBAMA.</p>
<p begin="00:05:57.257" end="00:06:01.261">THE ONE THING YOU KEEP COMING BACK TO IS HIS JUDGMENT NECESSARILY ON THE PEOPLE THAT </p>
<p begin="00:06:01.261" end="00:06:04.164">HE HAS AROUND HIM AS ADVISORS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:04.164" end="00:06:12.339">THIS ISN&apos;T NECESSARILY THE IRAQ WAR, HE&apos;S GOT A SITUATION HE HAS INHERITED BUT HE IS </p>
<p begin="00:06:12.339" end="00:06:20.547">RESPONSIBLE... YOU CAN&apos;T SIT BACK AND SAY HE&apos;S NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR BAD ADVISE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:20.547" end="00:06:22.449">&gt;&gt; WITH LARRY THERE&apos;S A SEDUCTION.</p>
<p begin="00:06:22.449" end="00:06:28.922">OBAMA LOVES THESE HIGH I.Q. GUYS LARRY IS THE TOP OF THE HEAT THERE AND HE SORT OF ENDS UP IN </p>
<p begin="00:06:28.922" end="00:06:31.792">WHAT I CALL THE LARRY SUMMERS DEBATE SOCIETY.</p>
<p begin="00:06:31.792" end="00:06:37.064">I THINK OBAMA FELT HE&apos;D SIT ABOVE IT AND JUDGE WHO&apos;S THE WINNER.</p>
<p begin="00:06:37.064" end="00:06:38.866">HE&apos;S JUST ANOTHER GUY AT THE TABLE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:38.866" end="00:06:41.168">LARRY SAYING I&apos;LL GO FIRST, YOU GO AFTER ME.</p>
<p begin="00:06:41.168" end="00:06:44.438">IT TROUBLES PEOPLE WHO ARE SITTING THERE SAYING WAIT A SECOND, IS THAT BEING </p>
<p begin="00:06:44.438" end="00:06:47.341">DISRESPECTFUL TO THE PRESIDENT?</p>
<p begin="00:06:47.341" end="00:06:52.379">EVENTUALLY YOU SEE THE PRESIDENT&apos;S CONFIDENCE SORT OF BRUISED AND, FRANKLY, THAT&apos;S WHY </p>
<p begin="00:06:52.379" end="00:06:53.747">CONFIDENCE MEN IS THE TITLE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:53.747" end="00:06:54.815">IT&apos;S ALL ABOUT CONFIDENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:54.815" end="00:06:56.950">THE COIN OF THE REALM.</p>
<p begin="00:06:56.950" end="00:06:59.520">&gt;&gt; Jon: I SEE WHAT YOU DID THERE!</p>
<p begin="00:06:59.520" end="00:07:06.126">YOU TURNED IT AROUND YOU&apos;RE VERY GOOD.</p>
<p begin="00:07:06.126" end="00:07:11.031">(LAUGHTER) I WANT TO ASK YOU A COUPLE MORE THINGS, THIS WILL BE ON THE WEB.</p>
<p begin="00:07:11.031" end="00:07:13.200">&quot;CONFIDENCE MEN&quot; IS THE NAME OF THE BOOK, RON SUSKIND.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
