<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:06.340" end="00:00:06.940">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE).</p>
<p begin="00:00:06.940" end="00:00:07.508">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELCOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:07.508" end="00:00:13.780">SO WAY BACK IN 2003 ON THIS PROGRAM WE INTRODUCED A SEGMENT DEVOUTED TO ROUNDING UP VARIOUS </p>
<p begin="00:00:13.780" end="00:00:18.886">NEWS ITEMS ABOUT THE HOMOSEXUAL AGENDA WHICH WE CALLED &quot;GAY WATCH.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:00:18.886" end="00:00:19.486">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE).</p>
<p begin="00:00:19.486" end="00:00:24.291">&gt;&gt; Jon: THE TITLE...</p>
<p begin="00:00:24.291" end="00:00:31.765">(LAUGHTER) FORGOT I STARTED THIS SHOW 43 YEARS AGO.</p>
<p begin="00:00:31.765" end="00:00:35.435">(LAUGHTER) ANYWAY, THE TITLE, OF COURSE, A PLAY ON &quot;BY A WATCH&quot; AND THE </p>
<p begin="00:00:35.435" end="00:00:39.039">TITLE WORKED ON A LOT OF LEVELS BUT THAT SHOW&apos;S BEEN OFF THE AIR </p>
<p begin="00:00:39.039" end="00:00:44.311">FOR LIKE 20 YEARS NOW SO WE NEED A MORE CONTEMPORARY CULTURAL REFERENCE FOR THE SEGMENT SO...</p>
<p begin="00:00:44.311" end="00:00:45.078">NO.</p>
<p begin="00:00:45.078" end="00:00:45.345">NO.</p>
<p begin="00:00:45.345" end="00:00:48.215">I THINK... ACTUALLY, THAT&apos;S BEEN OFF THE AIR FOR FIVE YEARS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:48.215" end="00:00:51.351">MAYBE SOMETHING A BIT MORE HIP.</p>
<p begin="00:00:51.351" end="00:00:52.753">(LAUGHTER) MEH.</p>
<p begin="00:00:52.753" end="00:00:56.423">I NEED SOMETHING NEWSY THAT CAN CAN... HMM.</p>
<p begin="00:00:56.423" end="00:00:56.723">OKAY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:56.723" end="00:00:59.826">(LAUGHTER) OKAY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:59.826" end="00:01:01.728">CLOSER.</p>
<p begin="00:01:01.728" end="00:01:02.863">NO.</p>
<p begin="00:01:02.863" end="00:01:03.163">NO.</p>
<p begin="00:01:03.163" end="00:01:05.132">I DON&apos;T EVEN KNOW WHAT THAT IS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:05.132" end="00:01:08.101">(LAUGHTER) THAT&apos;S...</p>
<p begin="00:01:08.101" end="00:01:18.412">(LAUGHTER) (CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) ALL RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:18.412" end="00:01:22.149">LET&apos;S JUST GO WITH THE ONE WE AGREED ON EARLIER.</p>
<p begin="00:01:22.149" end="00:01:24.084">THANK YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:01:24.084" end="00:01:25.452">(LAUGHTER) THAT&apos;S IN THE SWEET SPOT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:25.452" end="00:01:29.523">IN ANY CASE, OUR TITLE ISN&apos;T THE ONLY THING THAT&apos;S CHANGED SINCE 2003.</p>
<p begin="00:01:29.523" end="00:01:31.792">THE RIGHTS OF GAY PEOPLE HAVE PROGRESSED SIGNIFICANTLY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:31.792" end="00:01:37.497">THEY&apos;VE MADE GAINS IN OBTAINING ACCESS TO MARRIAGE, MILITARY SERVICE AND (BLEEP)ING BETWEEN </p>
<p begin="00:01:37.497" end="00:01:38.465">ANGST MELODRAMAS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:38.465" end="00:01:42.102">EVERYTHING SEEMS TO BE MOVING IN THE DIRECTION OF MORE EQUALITY FOR GAY PEOPLE BUT SOME PEOPLE </p>
<p begin="00:01:42.102" end="00:01:45.772">ARE TRYING TO HOLD BACK THE FLOOD, STEM THE TIDE, TO PUT A FINGER IN...</p>
<p begin="00:01:45.772" end="00:01:47.941">(LAUGHTER).</p>
<p begin="00:01:47.941" end="00:01:51.378">UM... TO STEM THE TIDE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:51.378" end="00:01:57.284">(LAUGHTER) CASE IN POINT: LAST YEAR CALIFORNIA&apos;S PROP 8 BANNING SAME-SEX MARRIAGE WAS RULED </p>
<p begin="00:01:57.284" end="00:01:59.419">UNCONSTITUTIONAL BY FEDERAL JUDGE VAUGHN WALKER.</p>
<p begin="00:01:59.419" end="00:02:03.223">SOME OPPONENTS OF GAY MARRIAGE THINK THEY&apos;VE FOUND A LOOPHOLE TO UNDO THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:03.223" end="00:02:11.465">&gt;&gt; PEOPLE ALWAYS SORT OF SPECULATED ABOUT HIS SEXUALITY AND IN APRIL HE CAME OUT AND HE </p>
<p begin="00:02:11.465" end="00:02:16.069">SAID &quot;YES, I AM GAY AND I HAVE HAD THIS LONG TERM SAME-SEX RELATIONSHIP.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:02:16.069" end="00:02:22.209">NOW SUPPORTERS OF PROPOSITION 8 ARE TRYING TO OVERTURN HIS DECISION.</p>
<p begin="00:02:22.209" end="00:02:25.646">&gt;&gt; Jon: HE CAN&apos;T BE GAY AND IMPARTIAL.</p>
<p begin="00:02:25.646" end="00:02:28.882">(WHISPERING) YOU KNOW HOW DRAMATIC THOSE PEOPLE ARE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:28.882" end="00:02:32.786">(LAUGHTER) WALKER RULING ON PROP 8 WOULD BE LIKE THURGOOD MARSHALL RULING A </p>
<p begin="00:02:32.786" end="00:02:38.125">CASE ABOUT RACE OR SANDRA DAY O&apos;CONNOR RULING A CASE INVOLVING REPRODUCTIVE RIGHTS OR JUDGE </p>
<p begin="00:02:38.125" end="00:02:41.995">JUDY TRYING TO BE IMPARTIAL IN A CASE INVOLVING SASS AND MOXIE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:41.995" end="00:02:50.637">(LAUGHTER) OR A DOG JUDGE RULING ON A CASE CONCERNING PUBLIC BALL-LICKING.</p>
<p begin="00:02:50.637" end="00:02:54.107">(LAUGHTER) IDEA FOR A SHOW.</p>
<p begin="00:02:54.107" end="00:02:57.644">(LAUGHTER) DOG JUDGE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:57.644" end="00:03:03.483">WE&apos;LL CALL IT &quot;JUSTICE OF THE PAW.&quot; (LAUGHTER) I&apos;LL WORK ON THE TITLE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:03.483" end="00:03:08.121">MEANWHILE AIR, CROSS THE COUNTRY IN TENNESSEE, GAY RIGHTS OPPONENTS ARE TAKING A DIFFERENT TACT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:08.121" end="00:03:11.892">&gt;&gt; NOW TO TENNESSEE WHERE A PROPOSED BILL WOULD PREVENT ELEMENTARY AND MIDDLE SCHOOL </p>
<p begin="00:03:11.892" end="00:03:15.629">TEACHERS FROM TALKING ABOUT HOMOSEXUALITY TO KIDS IN THE CLASSROOM.</p>
<p begin="00:03:15.629" end="00:03:21.235">NO PUBLIC ELEMENTARY OR MIDDLE SCHOOL SHALL PROVIDE ANY INSTRUCTION OR MATERIAL THAT </p>
<p begin="00:03:21.235" end="00:03:25.873">DISCUSSES SEXUAL ORIENTATION OTHER THAN HETEROSEXUALITY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:25.873" end="00:03:29.910">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU KNOW, KEEPING PEOPLE FROM SAYING THE WORD &quot;GAY&quot; IS NOT REALLY GOING TO </p>
<p begin="00:03:29.910" end="00:03:32.112">KEEP PEOPLE FROM BEING GAY, YOU KNOW.</p>
<p begin="00:03:32.112" end="00:03:34.114">(LAUGHTER) BEING GAY ISN&apos;T LIKE BEETLEJUICE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:34.114" end="00:03:39.520">IF YOU SAY IT OUTLOUD SO MANY TIMES, YOU&apos;RE GAY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:39.520" end="00:03:44.191">(LAUGHTER) THE BILL WAS INTRODUCED BY STATE SENATOR STACEY CAMPFIELD WHO </p>
<p begin="00:03:44.191" end="00:03:46.994">MAINTAINS HIS &quot;DON&apos;T SAY GAY BILL&quot; ISN&apos;T ANTIGAY AT ALL.</p>
<p begin="00:03:46.994" end="00:03:50.631">&gt;&gt; IS THERE ANY DAMAGE DONE IN TERMS OF HEARING THE WORD </p>
<p begin="00:03:50.631" end="00:03:53.967">&quot;HOMOSEXUALITY&quot; TO CHILDREN IN A CONTROLLED SETTING LIKE A CLASSROOM?</p>
<p begin="00:03:53.967" end="00:03:56.336">&gt;&gt; WELL ACTUALLY, MY BILL IS NEUTRAL.</p>
<p begin="00:03:56.336" end="00:03:58.338">IT DOESN&apos;T SAY ANYBODY CAN SPEAK FOR IT OR AGAINST IT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:58.338" end="00:04:01.642">&gt;&gt; Jon: HERE&apos;S A FUN FACT: AT THE SAME TIME THIS GUY&apos;S BILL IS </p>
<p begin="00:04:01.642" end="00:04:05.846">MAKING ITS WAY THROUGH TENNESSEE SENATE, A BILL IS ALSO MAKING ITS WAY THROUGH THE TENNESSEE </p>
<p begin="00:04:05.846" end="00:04:10.317">STATEHOUSE THAT MANDATES SCIENCE TEACHERS HAVE THE FREEDOM TO TEACH ALTERNATIVE THEORIES TO EVOLUTION.</p>
<p begin="00:04:10.317" end="00:04:16.056">SO IN TENNESSEE THE DEFINITION OF NEUTRALITY IS GAY PEOPLE ARE NOT ALLOWED TO BE BROUGHT UP BUT </p>
<p begin="00:04:16.056" end="00:04:21.161">WHETHER ADAM AND EVE HAD PET DINOSAURS WHEN THE EARTH WAS CREATED 6,000 YEARS AGO WE </p>
<p begin="00:04:21.161" end="00:04:23.063">SHOULD REALLY TEACH THAT CONTROVERSY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:23.063" end="00:04:27.167">(LAUGHTER) NOW, WHILE SOME PEOPLE ARE TRYING TO HOLD GAY PEOPLE BACK,</p>
<p begin="00:04:27.167" end="00:04:29.102">THEY DO HAVE SOME DEFENDERS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:29.102" end="00:04:34.741">FORTUNATELY, ONE OF THEM IS ATTORNEY GLORIA ALLRED WHO SUED ATLANTA BRAVES PITCHING COACH </p>
<p begin="00:04:34.741" end="00:04:39.780">ROGER McDOWEL FOR MAKING HOMOPHOBIC COMMENTS TRAUMATIZE AGO FAN TBHOFS THE STANDS WITH </p>
<p begin="00:04:39.780" end="00:04:41.114">HIS TWO YOUNG DAUGHTERS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:41.114" end="00:04:48.388">&gt;&gt; MR. QUINN HEARD COACH McDOWEL SAY TO THESE MEN &quot;ARE YOU GUYS A HOMO COUPLE OR A </p>
<p begin="00:04:48.388" end="00:04:51.892">THREESOME?&quot; THEN THE COACH ALLEGEDLY GRABBED A BASEBALL BAT AND STARTED </p>
<p begin="00:04:51.892" end="00:04:58.699">SHOVING THE SMALL END THROUGH A CIRCLE FORMED BY HIS FINGER AND THUMB SIMULATING SEX.</p>
<p begin="00:04:58.699" end="00:05:04.404">THE COACH THEN ALLEGEDLY SAID &quot;ARE YOU THREE GIVING IT TO EACH </p>
<p begin="00:05:04.404" end="00:05:10.777">OTHER UP THE...&quot; AND USED THE WORD FOR... CRUDE WORD FOR REAR END.</p>
<p begin="00:05:10.777" end="00:05:13.680">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:05:13.680" end="00:05:17.251">&gt;&gt; Jon: THE KIDS ARE STILL IN THE ROOM!</p>
<p begin="00:05:17.251" end="00:05:21.421">(LAUGHTER) THEY&apos;RE SITTING IN THE PINK SWEATERS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:21.421" end="00:05:25.659">(LAUGHTER) YES, I CAN&apos;T BELIEVE THERE WAS CHILDREN THAT HAD TO HEAR THAT </p>
<p begin="00:05:25.659" end="00:05:28.929">VULGAR LANGUAGE AT THE BALLPARK.</p>
<p begin="00:05:28.929" end="00:05:34.067">(LAUGHTER) CLEARLY IT&apos;S SUITABLE TALK ONLY FOR LAW OFFICE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:34.067" end="00:05:40.274">AT LEAST THE KID DON&apos;T HAVE TO WATCH THOSE OBSCENE GESTURES AGAIN BECAUSE... REALLY?</p>
<p begin="00:05:40.274" end="00:05:58.492">(LAUGHTER) (AUDIENCE REACTS) (LAUGHTER) GIRLS, YOU YOU GETTING THIS?</p>
<p begin="00:05:58.492" end="00:05:59.660">ARE YOU SEEING THIS?</p>
<p begin="00:05:59.660" end="00:06:10.237">BECAUSE I, GLORIA ALLRED, WANT WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT THE YOUNGER GIRLS BROUGHT HERE TODAY WANT TO </p>
<p begin="00:06:10.237" end="00:06:13.140">SEE ME (BLEEP)ING DADDY&apos;S HAND WITH A BASEBALL BAT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:13.140" end="00:06:16.577">IF THERE WERE ANY TENNESSEE SEX ED TEACHERS THAT WANT TO GET </p>
<p begin="00:06:16.577" end="00:06:19.446">AROUND THE WHOLE &quot;DON&apos;T SAY GAY&quot; THING.</p>
<p begin="00:06:19.446" end="00:06:23.817">YOU CAN GET AROUND IT NICELY BY SAYING &quot;SOMETIMES WHEN TWO MEN LOVE EACH OTHER VERY MUCH </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
