<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:02.336" end="00:00:07.107">[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]</p>
<p begin="00:00:07.107" end="00:00:08.175">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELCOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:08.175" end="00:00:11.278">MY GUEST TONIGHT IS CNN&apos;S SENIOR MEDICAL CORRESPONDENT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:11.278" end="00:00:16.984">HIS NEW SPECIAL IS CALLED DR. SANJAY GUPTA REPORTS: TERROR IN THE DUST.</p>
<p begin="00:00:16.984" end="00:00:23.423">&gt;&gt; WE HAVE FIRE, PLASTICS, OTHER PARTS OF THE PERIODIC TABLE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:23.423" end="00:00:31.565">&gt;&gt; GOLD AND MERCURY FROM TENS OF THOUSANDS OF FLORESCENT LIGHTBULBS, BAD -- LEAD FROM </p>
<p begin="00:00:31.565" end="00:00:34.601">THOUSANDS OF COMPUTER MONITOR,</p>
<p begin="00:00:34.601" end="00:00:40.307">TITANIUM FROM PAINT ON THE TRADE CENTER WALLS, ASBESTOS THAT COATED LOWER BEAMS OF THE TRADE </p>
<p begin="00:00:40.307" end="00:00:41.542">CENTER BUILDINGS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:41.542" end="00:00:46.547">THERE WAS CEMENT, GLASS, CARPET FIBERS, CEILING TILES, EVEN HUMAN HAIR.</p>
<p begin="00:00:46.547" end="00:00:50.050">IN ALL 1.5 MILLION TONS OF THE STUFF.</p>
<p begin="00:00:50.050" end="00:01:02.362">&gt;&gt; Jon: PLEASE WELCOME BACK TO THE SHOW DR. SANJAY GROUP TA. -- GROUP -- GUPTA.</p>
<p begin="00:01:03.197" end="00:01:05.399">[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]</p>
<p begin="00:01:05.399" end="00:01:13.440">SO IN THE SWIRL OF OBVIOUSLY ALL THESE REMEMBRANCES AND THE TEN-YEAR, THIS REALLY IS AN </p>
<p begin="00:01:13.440" end="00:01:18.679">ONGOING ISSUE, WHICH IS THE HEALTH OF THE PEOPLE THAT WENT DOWN TO THE POD, AND THAT&apos;S WHAT </p>
<p begin="00:01:18.679" end="00:01:19.546">THIS SPECIAL IS EXPLORING.</p>
<p begin="00:01:19.546" end="00:01:20.781">&gt;&gt; NO QUESTION ABOUT IT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:20.781" end="00:01:23.283">I MEAN, IT&apos;S BEEN A HUGELY,</p>
<p begin="00:01:23.283" end="00:01:24.518">SURPRISINGLY CONTENTIOUS ISSUE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:24.518" end="00:01:29.323">PEOPLE HAVE SUSPECTED FOR SOME TIME THAT THERE IS A LINK BETWEEN THIS DUST AND THE CANCER </p>
<p begin="00:01:29.323" end="00:01:30.824">THAT PEOPLE ARE SEEING.</p>
<p begin="00:01:30.824" end="00:01:32.559">HIGHER RATES OF CANCER.</p>
<p begin="00:01:32.559" end="00:01:34.094">PEOPLE NOTICE THIS PRETTY QUICKLY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:34.094" end="00:01:38.232">THE QUESTION HAS BEEN, PEOPLE HAVE SAID, IS THIS EMOTION OR IS THIS SCIENCE?</p>
<p begin="00:01:38.232" end="00:01:44.204">AND NOW AT THE TEN-YEAR MARK WE&apos;RE STARTING TO SEE SCIENTIFIC PAPERS COME OUT AND ADDRESS THIS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:44.204" end="00:01:51.278">&gt;&gt; Jon: WHY DO YOU THINK WE COULDN&apos;T HAVE GIVEN THEM THE BENEFIT OF THE DOUBT AND ERRED </p>
<p begin="00:01:51.278" end="00:01:58.919">ON THE SIDE OF MAYBE SPENDING A YEAR ON A SMOLDERING PILE MIGHT NOT BE GOOD FOR YOU?</p>
<p begin="00:01:58.919" end="00:02:02.556">&gt;&gt; I MEAN, YOU MAY KNOW THE ANSWER TO THAT BETTER THAN I.</p>
<p begin="00:02:02.556" end="00:02:04.191">YOU&apos;VE TALKED A LOT TO PEOPLE ABOUT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:04.191" end="00:02:05.292">THIS I DON&apos;T KNOW, JON.</p>
<p begin="00:02:05.292" end="00:02:07.528">I THINK PART OF THAT IS JUST PERSONALITY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:07.528" end="00:02:09.663">PART OF THAT IS OUR ATTITUDE TOWARDS OTHER PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:09.663" end="00:02:15.235">PART OF IT IS ARE WE GOING TO BE COMPASSIONATE PEOPLE WHO AIR ON THE SIDE OF, OKAY, SO WE TOOK </p>
<p begin="00:02:15.235" end="00:02:19.373">CARE OF AN EXTRA GUY WHO GOT CANCER THAT WASN&apos;T RELATED TO 9/11 BUT TOOK CARE OF HUNDREDS </p>
<p begin="00:02:19.373" end="00:02:22.309">OF PEOPLE WHO DID, OR ARE WE GOING TO DO NOTHING AT ALL?</p>
<p begin="00:02:22.309" end="00:02:27.681">I THINK THAT&apos;S JUST... THE AMAZING THING IS YOU TALK TO THESE FIRST RESPONDERS, AND THEY </p>
<p begin="00:02:27.681" end="00:02:31.185">REAFFIRM MY FAITH BECAUSE OF ALL THAT MAKES ME... IT SORT OF CHALLENGES YOU FAITH.</p>
<p begin="00:02:31.185" end="00:02:35.989">THEN YOU TALK TO THESE GUYS AND THEY&apos;RE LITERALLY ON OXYGEN.</p>
<p begin="00:02:35.989" end="00:02:37.591">THEY&apos;RE ON THEIR DEATH BEDS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:37.591" end="00:02:38.959">THAT&apos;S NOT AN EXAGGERATION.</p>
<p begin="00:02:38.959" end="00:02:42.296">THEY SAY, YOU KNOW WHAT, IF THERE WAS AN ATTACK TOMORROW,</p>
<p begin="00:02:42.296" end="00:02:43.297">I&apos;D BE OUT THERE AGAIN.</p>
<p begin="00:02:43.297" end="00:02:45.532">AND THERE&apos;S NOTHING FALSE ABOUT WHAT THEY&apos;RE SAYING.</p>
<p begin="00:02:45.532" end="00:02:47.000">&gt;&gt; Jon: IT&apos;S IN THEIR D.N.A.</p>
<p begin="00:02:47.000" end="00:02:48.635">I TRULY BELIEVE IT&apos;S IN THEIR D.N.A.</p>
<p begin="00:02:48.635" end="00:02:52.105">THE QUESTION BECOMES: LET&apos;S NOT BE INSANE HERE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:52.105" end="00:02:59.146">A SMOLDERING PILE OF ANYTHING, A SMOLDERING PILE OF BROCCOLI...</p>
<p begin="00:02:59.146" end="00:03:00.547">&gt;&gt; CAN&apos;T BE GOOD FOR YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:03:00.547" end="00:03:03.150">&gt;&gt; Jon: NOTHING SMOLDERING IS GOOD FOR YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:03:03.150" end="00:03:08.856">AND THESE GUYS WERE DOWN THERE DAY IN AND DAY OUT WITH THE TYPE OF PAPER MASKS A JAPANESE </p>
<p begin="00:03:08.856" end="00:03:11.358">BUSINESSMAN WITH A HEAD COLD WEARS WHEN HE&apos;S GOING DOWN THE </p>
<p begin="00:03:11.358" end="00:03:14.428">STREET INCH GOD&apos;S NAME NEW YORK WHAT WORLD WOULD THAT NOT CAUSE </p>
<p begin="00:03:14.428" end="00:03:17.798">THESE BRAVE INDIVIDUALS DISEASE?</p>
<p begin="00:03:17.798" end="00:03:19.533">&gt;&gt; I COMPLETELY AGREE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:19.533" end="00:03:23.937">IT&apos;S AMAZING BECAUSE WE KNOW AS YOU SAW, ALL THE COMPONENTS OF THIS DUST NOW, THAT&apos;S BEEN STUDIED.</p>
<p begin="00:03:23.937" end="00:03:27.708">WE KNOW THAT SO MANY OF THOSE THINGS, THEY CAUSE CANCER,</p>
<p begin="00:03:27.708" end="00:03:28.842">THEY&apos;RE CARCINOGENIC.</p>
<p begin="00:03:28.842" end="00:03:34.414">WHAT WAS AMAZING IS YOU GOT THIS WHOLLY UNIQUE SITUATION WHERE ALL THESE CHEMICALS WERE THRUST </p>
<p begin="00:03:34.414" end="00:03:38.986">TOGETHER AT THE TIME OF THESE ATTACKS, SO BENZENE WITH VARIOUS OTHER COMPOUNDS, TITANIUM.</p>
<p begin="00:03:38.986" end="00:03:43.457">WE KNOW THOSE THINGS INDIVIDUALLY CAN CAUSE CANCER AND IN COMBINATION COULD BE EVEN WORSE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:43.457" end="00:03:48.362">WHAT I THINK SOME PEOPLE WILL SAY IS, LOOK, CANCER CAN TAKE A LONG TIME TO DEVELOP.</p>
<p begin="00:03:48.362" end="00:03:51.198">IT CAN TAKE 15, 20, 30 YEARS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:51.198" end="00:03:53.834">SO WE&apos;RE IN THE SEEING THE BIG CANCER RATES THAT WE THOUGHT YET.</p>
<p begin="00:03:53.834" end="00:03:55.102">WE THINK IT&apos;S GOING TO HAPPEN,</p>
<p begin="00:03:55.102" end="00:03:59.773">BUT WE&apos;RE NOT SEEING IT AS OF YET.</p>
<p begin="00:03:59.773" end="00:04:03.343">&gt;&gt; Jon: THEY&apos;RE COVERING THINGS LIKE SCIATIC AND, YOU KNOW...</p>
<p begin="00:04:03.343" end="00:04:04.945">&gt;&gt; CARPEL TUNNEL SYNDROME.</p>
<p begin="00:04:04.945" end="00:04:06.547">&gt;&gt; BUT NOT CANCER.</p>
<p begin="00:04:06.547" end="00:04:10.517">THEY SAY THE SCIENCE IS NOT THERE, BUT THE SCIENCE OF CANCER, WE STILL DON&apos;T KNOW WHAT </p>
<p begin="00:04:10.517" end="00:04:11.518">CAUSES MOST CANCERS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:11.518" end="00:04:12.753">&gt;&gt; ABSOLUTELY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:12.753" end="00:04:20.827">&gt;&gt; Jon: IF THEIR LEVEL OF PROOF, THE BAR OF PROOF IS THEY HAVE TO FIND A PERFECT </p>
<p begin="00:04:20.827" end="00:04:25.499">CAUSALITY, NOT EVEN A CORRELATION, WILL THESE GUYS EVER GET THE SATISFACTION AND </p>
<p begin="00:04:25.499" end="00:04:26.099">COVERAGE THEY NEED?</p>
<p begin="00:04:26.099" end="00:04:29.102">&gt;&gt; IT IS AN ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE BAR TO MEET.</p>
<p begin="00:04:29.102" end="00:04:30.437">I THINK THAT&apos;S WHAT YOU&apos;RE SAYING.</p>
<p begin="00:04:30.437" end="00:04:38.245">IT TOOK A LONG TIME TO DRAW A CORRELATION BETWEEN SMOKING AND LUNG CANCER.</p>
<p begin="00:04:38.245" end="00:04:40.814">THERE WAS A SHOW ON YOUR PIECE ON ASBESTOS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:40.814" end="00:04:45.152">THAT TOOK 25 YEARS THE DRAW THE LINK BETWEEN ASBESTOS AND MESOTHELIOMA.</p>
<p begin="00:04:45.152" end="00:04:48.088">PEOPLE DIED WHO MAY HAVE OTHERWISE BEEN SCREENED AND TREATED AND SAVED.</p>
<p begin="00:04:48.088" end="00:04:51.091">IF YOU WAIT FOR THE SCIENCE TO CATCH UP, WHICH IT MAY NEVER, AS </p>
<p begin="00:04:51.091" end="00:04:53.594">YOU&apos;RE SAYING, YOU&apos;VE WAITED TOO LONG.</p>
<p begin="00:04:53.594" end="00:04:57.831">&gt;&gt; Jon: HAVE YOU BEEN SURPRISED BY THE... THIS HAS BEEN ONE OF THE MORE STUNNING </p>
<p begin="00:04:57.831" end="00:05:03.036">EXAMPLES OF PUSHBACK THAT I HAVE EVER SEEN FROM A COMMUNITY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:03.036" end="00:05:08.041">IT DOESN&apos;T FEEL LIKE THE SCIENCE COMMUNITY, BUT THE GOVERNMENT PUSHING BACK ON THESE GUYS TO </p>
<p begin="00:05:08.041" end="00:05:13.247">KEEP MAKING IT MORE AND MORE DIFFICULT FOR THEM TO GET HELP AND TREATMENT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:13.247" end="00:05:15.349">&gt;&gt; I DON&apos;T UNDERSTAND THIS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:15.349" end="00:05:21.455">I MEAN, AND YOU KNOW, YOU SEE ADS AND FOR CAMPAIGNS, WHENEVER SOMEONE IS RUNNING FOR OFFICE,</p>
<p begin="00:05:21.455" end="00:05:24.925">THEY INVOKE THE FIRST RESPONDERS, YOU HAVE PICTURES OF THEM.</p>
<p begin="00:05:24.925" end="00:05:29.396">I DON&apos;T UNDERSTAND HOW AGAIN YOU WOULDN&apos;T ERR ON THE SIDE OF TAKING CARE OF THESE FOLKS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:29.396" end="00:05:30.063">&gt;&gt; Jon: RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:30.063" end="00:05:34.935">&gt;&gt; THE THING IS IT&apos;S NOT JUST TAKING CARE OF PEOPLE WHO ARE SICK RIGHT NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:05:34.935" end="00:05:39.139">IF THEY ALLOW THIS SCIENCE TOE MERGE AND PEOPLE START TO UNDERSTAND, THERE ARE PEOPLE WHO </p>
<p begin="00:05:39.139" end="00:05:39.606">COULD BE SAVED.</p>
<p begin="00:05:39.606" end="00:05:44.912">THERE ARE PEOPLE WHO WILL GET SCREENED KNOWING THAT WHAT THEY WERE BREATHING IN COULD BE PROBLEMATIC.</p>
<p begin="00:05:44.912" end="00:05:48.582">&gt;&gt; Jon: THE SPECIAL YOU&apos;RE DOING IS BASED ON SCIENCE, NOT EMOTION.</p>
<p begin="00:05:48.582" end="00:05:52.653">THE GENTLEMAN YOU HAVE IN THE SHOW...</p>
<p begin="00:05:52.653" end="00:05:54.721">&gt;&gt; THE CHIEF MEDICAL OFFICER FOR THE FIRE DEPARTMENT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:54.721" end="00:05:56.590">IT WAS INTERESTING BECAUSE HE SAID THAT EXACT THING.</p>
<p begin="00:05:56.590" end="00:06:00.093">HE SAID, PEOPLE HAVE SAID DON&apos;T LET EMOTIONS CLOUD SCIENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:00.093" end="00:06:01.328">THEY SAID, HERE&apos;S THE SCIENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:01.328" end="00:06:02.596">I GOT IT FOR YOU NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:06:02.596" end="00:06:04.464">&gt;&gt; Jon: SO THIS GUY HAS THE SCIENCE NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:06:04.464" end="00:06:12.339">WILL THEY REVISIT THE RULING THAT THEY WON&apos;T COVER CANCER?</p>
<p begin="00:06:12.339" end="00:06:15.209">&gt;&gt; THEY SAID THEY KNOW ABOUT THE STUDY.</p>
<p begin="00:06:15.209" end="00:06:18.145">TECHNICALLY THEY DON&apos;T HAVE TO HAVE VISIT THIS UNTIL JULY OF 2012.</p>
<p begin="00:06:18.145" end="00:06:22.850">THERE WAS A PETITION SIGNED TODAY BY PEOPLE WHO INTRODUCED THE ZADROGA BILL IN THE FIRST </p>
<p begin="00:06:22.850" end="00:06:24.785">PLACE WHO SAID THIS SCIENCE IS COMPELLING.</p>
<p begin="00:06:24.785" end="00:06:27.087">THERE ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE WHO HAVE BEEN WAITING FOR THIS,</p>
<p begin="00:06:27.087" end="00:06:28.121">TRYING TO DO SOMETHING.</p>
<p begin="00:06:28.121" end="00:06:32.759">&gt;&gt; Jon: SO THERE ARE INDIVIDUALS THAT COULD POSSIBLY HAVE TO WAIT A YEAR BEFORE, AND </p>
<p begin="00:06:32.759" end="00:06:35.162">SICK INDIVIDUALS?</p>
<p begin="00:06:35.162" end="00:06:36.496">&gt;&gt; THEY&apos;RE IN THIS DOCUMENTARY.</p>
<p begin="00:06:36.496" end="00:06:40.467">THIS GUY MARTY FULHAM, WHO MAYBE IS WATCHING RIGHT NOW, BUT HE&apos;S </p>
<p begin="00:06:40.467" end="00:06:44.071">LITERALLY... HE&apos;S BEEN WAITING FOR THIS FOR A LONG TIME.</p>
<p begin="00:06:44.071" end="00:06:50.978">AND, YOU KNOW, I HATE SAYING THIS, BUT IT MAY NOT COME IN TIME FOR HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:06:50.978" end="00:06:54.448">BECAUSE OF ALL THE THINGS YOU MENTIONED, MATE NOW HAPPEN FAST ENOUGH.</p>
<p begin="00:06:54.448" end="00:06:55.816">IT SHOULD FOR PEOPLE LIKE HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:06:55.816" end="00:07:00.120">&gt;&gt; Jon: DO YOU HAVE A FEAR THIS GETS BURIED IN ANOTHER BUREAUCRATIC JUMBLE OR IT&apos;S A </p>
<p begin="00:07:00.120" end="00:07:03.924">HOT BUTTON ENOUGH ISSUE AROUND THE TENTH ANNIVERSARY THAT PEOPLE WILL TAKE UP THE MANTLE?</p>
<p begin="00:07:03.924" end="00:07:05.926">&gt;&gt; I THINK PEOPLE WILL TAKE UP THE MANTLE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:05.926" end="00:07:06.560">I BELIEVE THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:06.560" end="00:07:09.296">I THINK THAT THIS IS A TIME WHERE PEOPLE DO REFLECT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:09.296" end="00:07:16.069">THEY LOOK AT THE PEOPLE WHO WERE THE HEROES ON THAT DAY, NOT A TERM IN ANY WAY USED LYINGLY BUT </p>
<p begin="00:07:16.069" end="00:07:17.604">GENUINELY, AND I HOPE THEY DO.</p>
<p begin="00:07:17.604" end="00:07:19.840">&gt;&gt; Jon: RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:19.840" end="00:07:25.479">IT&apos;S FREAKY THAT THESE ANNIVERSARIES ARE ARBITRARY AND LORD KNOWS WE&apos;RE EXCESSIVE IN </p>
<p begin="00:07:25.479" end="00:07:28.615">OUR COVERAGE AND REMEMBRANCE OF IT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:28.615" end="00:07:34.521">IT&apos;S SO SHOCKING THAT IN ACTUALITY THE HELP YOU NEED STILL DOESN&apos;T COME.</p>
<p begin="00:07:34.521" end="00:07:37.791">&gt;&gt; I HAVE TO SAY, JON, YOU&apos;VE DONE A LOT ON THIS ISSUE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:37.791" end="00:07:39.526">WE&apos;VE BEEN WORKING ON THIS FOR A YEAR.</p>
<p begin="00:07:39.526" end="00:07:42.529">YOUR NAME WAS BROUGHT UP SO MANY TIMES BY THESE FIRST RESPONDERS.</p>
<p begin="00:07:42.529" end="00:07:48.902">&gt;&gt; Jon: LISTEN, IF THAT&apos;S WHAT GOES ON THE GRAVESTONE AS IN YOUR TIME HERE YOU HELPED </p>
<p begin="00:07:48.902" end="00:07:52.072">INCREMELY THESE PEOPLE...</p>
<p begin="00:07:52.072" end="00:07:53.073">&gt;&gt; YOU&apos;LL TAKE IT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:53.073" end="00:07:54.241">&gt;&gt; Jon: I&apos;LL TAKE IT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:54.241" end="00:07:55.943">THAT WILL BE FINE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:55.943" end="00:08:00.414">&quot;TERROR IN THE DUST.&quot; IT&apos;S ACTUALLY ON RIGHT NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:08:00.414" end="00:08:02.783">TRUTH OF THE MATTER, THIS WHOLE TIME, NOBODY&apos;S BEEN WATCHING.</p>
<p begin="00:08:02.783" end="00:08:05.652">IT&apos;S A GREAT SPECIAL AND REALLY WONDERFUL WORK.</p>
<p begin="00:08:05.652" end="00:08:06.753">NICE JOB.</p>
<p begin="00:08:06.753" end="00:08:10.324">&quot;TERROR IN THE DUST.&quot; REPLAYS ON SATURDAY SEPTEMBER 10th.</p>
<p begin="00:08:10.324" end="00:08:11.425">9:00 P.M.</p>
<p begin="00:08:11.425" end="00:08:12.826">DR. SANJAY GROUP TAMP NICE JOB.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
