<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:03.971" end="00:00:05.839">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) </p>
<p begin="00:00:05.839" end="00:00:07.007">&gt;&gt; Jon: WE&apos;RE BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:07.007" end="00:00:12.579">MY GUEST TONIGHT IS THE CHAIRMAN OF THE JOINT CHIEFS, PLEASE WELCOME BACK TO THE PROGRAMMED A </p>
<p begin="00:00:12.579" end="00:00:13.580">MIRL MIKE MULLEN.</p>
<p begin="00:00:13.580" end="00:00:24.024">(APPLAUSE) HOW ARE YOU?</p>
<p begin="00:00:24.024" end="00:00:26.059">&gt;&gt; TERRIFIC.</p>
<p begin="00:00:26.059" end="00:00:27.160">&gt;&gt; Jon: NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.</p>
<p begin="00:00:27.160" end="00:00:28.362">&gt;&gt; IT&apos;S GREAT TO BE BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:28.362" end="00:00:34.301">&gt;&gt; Jon: I THINK STARTING THIS SHOW WITH JUSTIN BIEBER AND ENDING WITH THE CHAIRMAN OF THE </p>
<p begin="00:00:34.301" end="00:00:37.971">JOINT CHIEFS OF STAFF MAKES THIS THE WEIRDEST &quot;THE DAILY SHOW&quot; ANYONE HAS EVER SEEN.</p>
<p begin="00:00:37.971" end="00:00:40.774">&gt;&gt; THERE&apos;S WONDERFUL EXCITEMENT TONIGHT AND IT WAS TERRIFIC TO </p>
<p begin="00:00:40.774" end="00:00:42.309">SEE HIM AND BE B BACK WITH YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:00:42.309" end="00:00:44.611">&gt;&gt; Jon: HE&apos;S A NICE KID.</p>
<p begin="00:00:44.611" end="00:00:45.646">&gt;&gt; HE IS, HE IS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:45.646" end="00:00:48.615">&gt;&gt; Jon: AND SURROUNDED BY PEOPLE WHO ARE REALLY LOOKING OUT FOR HIS BEST INTERESTS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:48.615" end="00:00:50.884">&gt;&gt; THEY ARE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:50.884" end="00:00:51.985">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:00:51.985" end="00:00:53.020">&gt;&gt; Jon: HOW ARE YOU DOING?</p>
<p begin="00:00:53.020" end="00:00:57.291">I KNOW THAT THE UNITED STATES MILITARY PRIDES ITSELF ON READINESS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:57.291" end="00:01:03.931">YOU GAME FOR ALL SORTS OF SITUATIONS, NORTH AFRICA AND WHAT&apos;S HAPPENED IN TUNISIA AND EGYPT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:03.931" end="00:01:05.365">DID THIS TAKE US BY SURPRISE?</p>
<p begin="00:01:05.365" end="00:01:10.270">I KNOW IT&apos;S BEEN AN AREA OF CONCERN BUT HAS THIS TAKEN US BY SURPRISE TO SOME EXTENT?</p>
<p begin="00:01:10.270" end="00:01:17.311">&gt;&gt; WELL, I THINK ACTUALLY IT HAS TAKEN NOT JUST US BUT MANY PEOPLE BY SURPRISE AND CERTAINLY </p>
<p begin="00:01:17.311" end="00:01:20.848">WE&apos;RE LOOKING AT... WE&apos;VE GOT A 30-YEAR RELATIONSHIP WITH THE </p>
<p begin="00:01:20.848" end="00:01:27.688">PEOPLE OF EGYPT AND CERTAINLY A VERY STRONG RELATIONSHIP FROM OUR MILITARY TO THEIRS THAT HAS </p>
<p begin="00:01:27.688" end="00:01:29.323">PROVEN TO BE VERY STRONG.</p>
<p begin="00:01:29.323" end="00:01:32.125">ALSO IN THIS CRISIS THAT THEY&apos;RE IN.</p>
<p begin="00:01:32.125" end="00:01:37.564">BUT TO A GREAT DEGREE I THINK THE TIMING OF IT CERTAINLY CAUGHT US AS IT MOVED FROM </p>
<p begin="00:01:37.564" end="00:01:45.873">TUNISIA AND SORT OF ACROSS TO THE REALLY DIFFICULT CHALLENGE THAT SITS THERE RIGHT NOW IN EGYPT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:45.873" end="00:01:48.108">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU SAY WE HAVE A RELATIONSHIP WITH THE MILITARY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:48.108" end="00:01:49.443">WE HAVE TRAINED THEIR OFFICERS,</p>
<p begin="00:01:49.443" end="00:01:51.011">HAVE WE NOT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:51.011" end="00:01:53.881">THEY&apos;VE COMED HERE AND TRAINED.</p>
<p begin="00:01:53.881" end="00:01:57.885">&gt;&gt; WE HAVE, ACTUALLY BY THE HUNDREDS IF NOT THOUSANDS OVER THE COURSE OF THAT 30 YEARS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:57.885" end="00:01:59.820">SO WE&apos;VE GOT A LOT OF CONTACTS,</p>
<p begin="00:01:59.820" end="00:02:03.891">WE&apos;VE GOT RELATIONSHIPS, THEY&apos;VE LIVED WITH US, THEIR FAMILIES HAVE LIVED WITH US.</p>
<p begin="00:02:03.891" end="00:02:08.996">SO ONE OF MY CHIEF GOALS RIGHT NOW IS TO MAKE SURE WE KEEP THE LINES OF COMMUNICATION OPEN.</p>
<p begin="00:02:08.996" end="00:02:15.669">I&apos;VE TALKED TO MY COUNTERPARTS A COUPLE OF TIMES.</p>
<p begin="00:02:15.669" end="00:02:20.407">AND ALSO THAT WE&apos;VE GOT OUR MILITARY READY SHOULD ANY KIND OF SUPPORT BE REQUIRED AND THAT </p>
<p begin="00:02:20.407" end="00:02:21.608">ISN&apos;T THE CASE RIGHT NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:02:21.608" end="00:02:23.310">I&apos;M VERY FOCUSED ON THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:23.310" end="00:02:27.614">&gt;&gt; Jon: THIS IS A STRANGE QUESTION AND MAY BE IN A DIFFERENT AREA BUT IS IT ODD FOR </p>
<p begin="00:02:27.614" end="00:02:31.852">THE UNITED STATES... WHEN WE GO INTO IRAQ OR AFGHANISTAN WE&apos;RE TALKING ABOUT PROMOTING </p>
<p begin="00:02:31.852" end="00:02:34.955">DEMOCRACY, WE&apos;RE BRINGING A SYSTEM OF GOVERNMENT AND WE&apos;VE </p>
<p begin="00:02:34.955" end="00:02:43.096">DONE IT THROUGH AN INVASION AND RELATIVELY EXTREME MEASURES YET IN EGYPT AS WE SEE A DEMOCRATIC </p>
<p begin="00:02:43.096" end="00:02:48.268">MOVEMENT COMING FROM THE GROUND UP WE GO, LIKE, HEY, WHAT&apos;S THAT?</p>
<p begin="00:02:48.268" end="00:02:56.510">IT ALMOST SEEMS LIKE ISN&apos;T THAT THE FRUIT OF THAT LABOR AND IS IT THAT AS A COUNTRY WE HAVE TO </p>
<p begin="00:02:56.510" end="00:03:03.317">BALANCE THIS IDEA OF STABILITY AND OUR INTERESTS WITH THIS DEMOCRACY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:03.317" end="00:03:04.818">CAN WE HAVE IT BOTH WAYS LIKE THIS?</p>
<p begin="00:03:04.818" end="00:03:08.088">&gt;&gt; I THINK WE DO HAVE TO BALANCE THAT AND PROBABLY BALANCE RIGHT </p>
<p begin="00:03:08.088" end="00:03:10.123">NOW IS A TERRIFIC WAY TO LOOK AT THIS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:10.123" end="00:03:13.026">IT&apos;S A VERY VOLATILE SITUATION.</p>
<p begin="00:03:13.026" end="00:03:13.961">IT&apos;S EVOLVING.</p>
<p begin="00:03:13.961" end="00:03:15.295">THERE&apos;S A LOT WE DON&apos;T KNOW.</p>
<p begin="00:03:15.295" end="00:03:21.969">WE HAVEN&apos;T KNOWN SINCE IT STARTED AND IN MANY CRISES LIKE THAT THERE&apos;S AN AWFUL LOT OF </p>
<p begin="00:03:21.969" end="00:03:26.473">UNKNOWNS SO CERTAINTY WITH OUTCOMES AND CERTAINTY WITH WHAT&apos;S GOING TO HAPPEN TOMORROW </p>
<p begin="00:03:26.473" end="00:03:27.307">IT&apos;S JUST NOT THERE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:27.307" end="00:03:28.742">BUT IN THAT UNCERTAINTY,</p>
<p begin="00:03:28.742" end="00:03:35.549">CERTAINLY, I HAVE AN EXPECTATION AND A RELATIONSHIP WITH THE EGYPTIAN MILITARY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:35.549" end="00:03:37.651">THEY&apos;VE REAFFIRMED THE SUPPORT OF THEIR PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:37.651" end="00:03:40.721">THEY&apos;VE REAFFIRMED THEIR SUPPORT OF THE INSTITUTIONS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:40.721" end="00:03:48.195">AND CERTAINLY WE&apos;RE ALL HOPEFUL THIS CAN EVOLVE PEACEFULLY WITH NO MORE VIOLENCE AND IN A WAY </p>
<p begin="00:03:48.195" end="00:03:52.799">WHERE IT REALLY IS REPRESENTATIVE OF THE EGYPTIAN PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:52.799" end="00:03:58.338">&gt;&gt; Jon: WHAT IS THE IDEA THAT IF THERE WAS... IF THEIR ARMY-- WHICH I GUESS IS NOW TRYING TO </p>
<p begin="00:03:58.338" end="00:04:06.647">GAIN A LITTLE BIT OF CONTROL-- IF THEY WERE TO MOVE IN THAT DIRECTION AGAINST THEIR OWN </p>
<p begin="00:04:06.647" end="00:04:12.719">PEOPLE, DO WE HAVE AN OPTION THERE OR I GUESS WHAT I&apos;M SAYING IS COULD WE EVER GO IN TO </p>
<p begin="00:04:12.719" end="00:04:15.989">PROTECT THE EGYPTIAN PEOPLE FROM THEIR OWN MILITARY?</p>
<p begin="00:04:15.989" end="00:04:24.431">&gt;&gt; I THINK THAT THE OUTCOME IS UP TO THE EGYPTIAN PEOPLE AND ALSO THEIR LEADERSHIP INCLUDING </p>
<p begin="00:04:24.431" end="00:04:24.998">THE ARMY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:24.998" end="00:04:28.836">I MEAN, IN DISCUSSIONS I&apos;VE HAD WITH THEIR MILITARY LEADERSHIP,</p>
<p begin="00:04:28.836" end="00:04:33.674">THEY HAVE REASSURED ME THAT THEY HAVE NO INTENT TO FIRE ON THEIR OWN PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:33.674" end="00:04:38.278">THEY HAVE TAKEN STEPS TO TRY TO QUELL THE VIOLENCE FROM YESTERDAY, THE TRAGIC VIOLENCE </p>
<p begin="00:04:38.278" end="00:04:44.251">THAT OCCURRED, THE PRIME MINISTER CAME OUT AND APOLOGIZED FOR IT THAT HE&apos;S GOING TO DO AN INVESTIGATION.</p>
<p begin="00:04:44.251" end="00:04:49.489">SO THERE&apos;S A LOT OF WORK GOING ON TO TRY TO MAKE SURE THAT THAT DOESN&apos;T RECUR.</p>
<p begin="00:04:49.489" end="00:04:55.629">BUT IT&apos;S AN EVOLVING SITUATION THAT WE HOPE CAN JUST CONTINUE TO EVOLVE PEACEFULLY SO THE </p>
<p begin="00:04:55.629" end="00:04:59.700">EGYPTIAN PEOPLE CAN END UP WITH THE GOVERNMENT THAT THEY WANT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:59.700" end="00:05:01.969">&gt;&gt; Jon: NOW, AS YOU LOOK ACROSS THE REGION NOW THAT YOU&apos;RE </p>
<p begin="00:05:01.969" end="00:05:07.574">SEEING IT WITH A PAIR OF FRESH EYES, SEEING IT COULD HAPPEN IN EGYPT, DO YOU LOOK AND THINK </p>
<p begin="00:05:07.574" end="00:05:11.778">&quot;SYRIA, THEY&apos;VE GOT ABOUT A WEEK.&quot; (LAUGHTER) &quot;THESE GUYS ARE GOING DOWN.</p>
<p begin="00:05:11.778" end="00:05:17.718">LEBANON, GEE.&quot; DO YOU SEE THIS ENTIRE REGION NOW GOING THROUGH OR IS IT </p>
<p begin="00:05:17.718" end="00:05:24.491">BECAUSE WE ARE SO... BECAUSE THESE ARE NOT NECESSARILY UNUSUAL RIPPLES IN THIS PART OF THE WORLD.</p>
<p begin="00:05:24.491" end="00:05:32.099">IT&apos;S JUST THAT THEIR GOVERNMENTS HAVE GENERALLY BEEN ABLE TO QUASH THEM BEHIND A VEIL NOW </p>
<p begin="00:05:32.099" end="00:05:34.134">THAT THE SOCIAL MEDIA IS THE WAY IT IS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:34.134" end="00:05:34.968">PEOPLE SEE IT MORE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:34.968" end="00:05:40.007">ARE WE SEEING SOMETHING NEW OR IS THIS A REPRISE OF A CYCLE?</p>
<p begin="00:05:40.007" end="00:05:43.877">&gt;&gt; WELL, OVERALL I WOULD THINK IT IS NEW AND CERTAINLY THERE ARE GOVERNMENTS THROUGHOUT THE </p>
<p begin="00:05:43.877" end="00:05:48.382">MIDDLE EAST AND LEADERS WHO ARE CONCERNED ABOUT THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:48.382" end="00:05:52.452">YOU&apos;VE SEEN THE PRESIDENT OF YEMEN SPEAK PUBLICLY THAT HE ISN&apos;T GOING TO STAND FOR </p>
<p begin="00:05:52.452" end="00:05:56.056">ELECTION IN A COUPLE YEARS, NOR WILL HE TURN IT OVER TO HIS FAMILY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:56.056" end="00:06:00.627">YOU&apos;VE... I&apos;VE ENGAGED LEADERS FROM OTHER COUNTRIES IN THE </p>
<p begin="00:06:00.627" end="00:06:03.564">REGION TO... AGAIN, THAT WE HAVE RELATIONSHIPS WITH.</p>
<p begin="00:06:03.564" end="00:06:08.869">WE&apos;VE WORKED HARD IN THE UNITED STATES AND THE MILITARY TO HAVE </p>
<p begin="00:06:08.869" end="00:06:11.205">RELATIONSHIPS WITH THE MILITARY FOR MANY OF THESE COUNTRIES.</p>
<p begin="00:06:11.205" end="00:06:15.342">THEY HAVE GONE TO OUR SCHOOL SO IT&apos;S AN EASY CALL TO MAKE EVEN IN A VERY DIFFICULT SITUATION </p>
<p begin="00:06:15.342" end="00:06:22.516">AND THEY ARE CONCERNED ABOUT WHERE THIS GOES AND HOW CONTAGIOUS IT IS AND WHAT IT </p>
<p begin="00:06:22.516" end="00:06:25.819">MEANS IN EACH COUNTRY, SOMETHING WE&apos;RE ALL LOOKING AT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:25.819" end="00:06:31.258">&gt;&gt; Jon: AND FOR YOU PERSONALLY IS IT THE TYPE OF THING... ARE </p>
<p begin="00:06:31.258" end="00:06:33.360">THEIR MILITARIES CONTROLLED IN A SIMILAR MATTER?</p>
<p begin="00:06:33.360" end="00:06:35.062">IT&apos;S NOT CIVILIAN LEADERSHIP.</p>
<p begin="00:06:35.062" end="00:06:37.598">I THINK THAT&apos;S THE THING THAT CONFUSES ME ABOUT EGYPT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:37.598" end="00:06:39.900">IS THE MILITARY AN ARMY OF MUBARAK?</p>
<p begin="00:06:39.900" end="00:06:42.302">THE MILITARY IN EGYPT IS VERY WELL RESPECTED.</p>
<p begin="00:06:42.302" end="00:06:44.838">IT&apos;S SEEN AS AN INSTITUTION OF GREAT INTEGRITY.</p>
<p begin="00:06:44.838" end="00:06:49.977">NOT SO MUCH THE POLICE FORCES AND WHOEVER IT IS THOSE GUYS ON CAM METS WITH WHIPS ARE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:49.977" end="00:06:50.611">NOBODY KNOWS WHO THEY ARE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:50.611" end="00:06:52.846">(LAUGHTER) BUT THE MILITARY DOES NOT HAVE THAT REPUTATION.</p>
<p begin="00:06:52.846" end="00:06:59.286">&gt;&gt; NO, THEIR REPRESENTATION IS EXCEPTIONALLY HIGH WITH THE </p>
<p begin="00:06:59.286" end="00:07:00.754">PEOPLE AND I THINK THEY&apos;D SAY...</p>
<p begin="00:07:00.754" end="00:07:04.057">THE MILITARY WOULD SAY THAT THAT&apos;S WHO THEY ARE SUPPORTING.</p>
<p begin="00:07:04.057" end="00:07:05.559">THE PEOPLE OF EGYPT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:05.559" end="00:07:12.099">AND THAT&apos;S WHY THE REPRESENTATION IS AS GOOD AS IT IS WITH THE POPULATION THERE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:12.099" end="00:07:15.802">&gt;&gt; Jon: ALWAYS GOOD TO... DO YOU MIND, CAN YOU STICK AROUND FOR FIVE MINUTES?</p>
<p begin="00:07:15.802" end="00:07:17.237">CAN WE TALK A LITTLE BIT?</p>
<p begin="00:07:17.237" end="00:07:17.604">&gt;&gt; SURE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:17.604" end="00:07:19.773">&gt;&gt; Jon: ADMIRAL MIKE MULLEN,</p>
<p begin="00:07:19.773" end="00:07:20.974">WE&apos;LL BE RIGHT BACK AFTER THIS.</p>
<p begin="00:07:20.974" end="00:07:21.441">(APP|||| </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
