<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:07.574" end="00:00:07.875">SHOW.</p>
<p begin="00:00:07.875" end="00:00:08.442">[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]</p>
<p begin="00:00:08.442" end="00:00:14.982">AS THE RECENT TRAGIC EVENTS IN ARIZONA SHOW US, A SCOURGE OF VIOLENCE IS STILL VERY MUCH WITH </p>
<p begin="00:00:14.982" end="00:00:15.516">THIS COUNTRY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:15.516" end="00:00:21.221">IT&apos;S CLEAR THAT THERE ARE GOING TO BE NO QUICK FIXES UNLESS THERE ARE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:21.221" end="00:00:27.427">&gt;&gt; AT LEAST FIVE MEMBERS OF CONGRESS ARE NOW PLANNING TO INTRODUCE NEW GUN LEGISLATION.</p>
<p begin="00:00:27.427" end="00:00:31.965">AMONG THEM NEW YORK REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN PETER KING WHO SAID TODAY HE WILL INTRODUCE A BILL </p>
<p begin="00:00:31.965" end="00:00:39.106">THAT WOULD MAKE IT ILLEGAL TO BRING A GUN WITHIN 1,000 FEET OF A GOVERNMENT OFFICIAL.</p>
<p begin="00:00:39.106" end="00:00:45.679">[LAUGHTER]</p>
<p begin="00:00:45.679" end="00:00:55.522">&gt;&gt; Jon: TWO QUESTIONS:  A, CAN YOU REST OF US GET US ONE OF THOSE 1,000 FEET GUN PERIMETERS </p>
<p begin="00:00:55.522" end="00:00:57.758">AND HOW IS THAT SUPPOSED TO WORK EXACTLY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:57.758" end="00:01:04.898">HOW WOULD LAW ABIDING GUN OWNERS KNOW HOW FAR THEY ARE FROM GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS UNLESS THE </p>
<p begin="00:01:04.898" end="00:01:14.541">STATUTE ALSO REQUIRES GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS TO WEAR COW BELLS AND GUN OWNERS TO CARRY NFL YARDAGE CHAINS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:14.541" end="00:01:19.947">THE QUESTION IS THIS THOUGH:  SHOULD WE REALLY BE WRITING LAWS THAT MAY BUMP UP AGAINST THE </p>
<p begin="00:01:19.947" end="00:01:26.119">SECOND AMENDMENT WITHOUT AT LEAST FIRST CONSIDERING LAWS THAT COULD BUMP UP AGAINST THE </p>
<p begin="00:01:26.119" end="00:01:27.020">FIRST AMENDMENT?</p>
<p begin="00:01:27.020" end="00:01:33.193">&gt;&gt; THE FIRST REAL INTRODUCTION OF LEGISLATION HAS BEEN BROUGHT BY REPRESENTATIVE BRADY OF PENNSYLVANIA.</p>
<p begin="00:01:33.193" end="00:01:38.799">HE&apos;S GOING CONTINUE TO TROA DEUCE LEGISLATION SAYING IT MAKES IT A FEDERAL CRIME TO USE </p>
<p begin="00:01:38.799" end="00:01:46.340">LANGUAGE OR SIGNALS USED AS INCITING VIOLENCE AGAINST A THREATENING FIGURE OR A MEMBER OF CONGRESS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:46.340" end="00:01:51.478">&gt;&gt; Jon: ISN&apos;T THREATENING A FEDERAL OFFICIAL OR MEMBER OF CONGRESS ALREADY AGAINST THE LAW?</p>
<p begin="00:01:51.478" end="00:01:52.479">[LAUGHTER]</p>
<p begin="00:01:52.479" end="00:01:54.081">HOW IS THIS DIFFERENT?</p>
<p begin="00:01:54.081" end="00:01:56.917">&gt;&gt; WE&apos;RE ADDING SYMBOLS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:56.917" end="00:02:07.895">YOU CAN&apos;T PUT A ACROSSHAIR -- A CROSSHAIR OR A BULL&apos;S EYE ON A MEMBER OF CONGRESS OR A DISTRICT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:07.895" end="00:02:12.065">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU CAN&apos;T PUT CROSSHAIRS ON A DISTRICT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:12.065" end="00:02:18.605">YOU ARE WRITING A NEW FEDERAL LAW JUST TO SAY (bleep) YOU TO SARAH PALIN.</p>
<p begin="00:02:18.605" end="00:02:20.340">[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]</p>
<p begin="00:02:20.340" end="00:02:29.249">OR IS PERHAPS SAYING (bleep) YOU TO SARAH PALIN ALSO NOW ILLEGAL AGAINST THE STATUTE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:29.249" end="00:02:35.689">WE&apos;RE UP AGAINST THE AGE-OLD DILEMMA A FREE PEOPLE MUST FACE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:35.689" end="00:02:43.297">MOST OF US DO NOT NEED CLARIFICATION ON THE WHOLE THOU SHALL NOT KILL THING AND FOR </p>
<p begin="00:02:43.297" end="00:02:49.469">THOSE WHO DO CLARIFICATION NEVER SEEMS SPECIFIC ENOUGH.</p>
<p begin="00:02:49.469" end="00:02:51.205">ONE SHALL NOT KILL.</p>
<p begin="00:02:51.205" end="00:02:54.441">WHAT ABOUT ABOUT KNIVES?</p>
<p begin="00:02:54.441" end="00:02:57.411">YOU CAN&apos;T KILL PEOPLE WITH KNIVES.</p>
<p begin="00:02:57.411" end="00:02:58.812">I SEE, I SEE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:58.812" end="00:03:02.382">ARE MINORITIES MINORITIES ARE INCLUDED?</p>
<p begin="00:03:02.382" end="00:03:04.685">WHAT IF I GET SOMEBODY ELSE TO DO IT?</p>
<p begin="00:03:04.685" end="00:03:08.922">CAN I GO UP TO SOMEBODY AND SAY I WANT TO YOU?</p>
<p begin="00:03:08.922" end="00:03:09.690">CAN I DO THAT?</p>
<p begin="00:03:09.690" end="00:03:14.328">WE ENFORCE ENFORCING LAW AND FORCING EVERYONE TO LIVE BY RULES THAT ONLY ATTEMPT TO </p>
<p begin="00:03:14.328" end="00:03:19.566">PREVENT THE LAST THING THAT WAS DONE BY THE LEAST CONTROLLABLE AMONGST US.</p>
<p begin="00:03:19.566" end="00:03:21.001">IT DOESN&apos;T HAVE TO BE THIS WAY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:21.001" end="00:03:28.442">WE MUST NOT GIVE IN TO FEAR SM WE MUST EMPOWER OUR BETTER JUDGEMENT TO CREATE A SOCIETY </p>
<p begin="00:03:28.442" end="00:03:37.618">WHERE VIOLENT RHETORIC AND IMAGERY IS FROWNED UPON NOT BECAUSE IT DRIVES THE UNSTABLE </p>
<p begin="00:03:37.618" end="00:03:40.754">TO ACTION BUT IT&apos;S BECAUSE IT&apos;S WRONG ITSELF.</p>
<p begin="00:03:40.754" end="00:03:43.490">I BELIEVE THAT&apos;S HOW THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ARE REACT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:43.490" end="00:03:48.829">&gt;&gt; MONDAY AFTER THE SHOOTING HANDGUNS SALES JUMPED 60% IN ARIZONA COMPARED TO THE SAME DAY </p>
<p begin="00:03:48.829" end="00:03:50.297">A YEAR AGO.</p>
<p begin="00:03:50.297" end="00:03:56.170">ONE GUN SHOP OWNER TOLD BLOOMBERG NEWS HIS GLOCK SALES DOUBLED THIS WEEK.</p>
<p begin="00:03:56.170" end="00:04:00.340">&gt;&gt; Jon: OR WE COULD GO THE OTHER WAY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:00.340" end="00:04:00.941">WE&apos;LL BE RI </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
