<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:04.738" end="00:00:05.806">&gt;&gt; WELCOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:05.806" end="00:00:09.343">MY GUEST TONIGHT, A PHYSICS PROFESSOR AT HARVARD UNIVERSITY,</p>
<p begin="00:00:09.343" end="00:00:11.078">ALSO A BESTSELLING AUTHOR.</p>
<p begin="00:00:11.078" end="00:00:16.650">HER NEW BOOK IS CALLED &quot;KNOCKING ON HEAVEN&apos;S DOOR: HOW PHYSICS AND SCIENTIFIC THINKING </p>
<p begin="00:00:16.650" end="00:00:21.855">ILLUMINATE THE UNIVERSE AND THE MODERN WORLD.&quot; PLEASE WELCOME LISA RANDALL.</p>
<p begin="00:00:21.855" end="00:00:23.657">HELLO.</p>
<p begin="00:00:23.657" end="00:00:28.662">[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]</p>
<p begin="00:00:28.662" end="00:00:29.530">THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:29.530" end="00:00:31.765">&gt;&gt; THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME HERE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:31.765" end="00:00:35.736">&gt;&gt; Jon: IT&apos;S CALLED &quot;KNOCKING ON HEAVEN&apos;S DOOR: HOW PHYSIC AND </p>
<p begin="00:00:35.736" end="00:00:40.941">SCIENTIFIC THINKING ILLUMINATE THE UNIVERSE AND THE MODERN WORLD.</p>
<p begin="00:00:40.941" end="00:00:44.144">PHYSICS AND SCIENCE ILLUMINATE THE UNIVERSE AND THE MODERN WORLD.</p>
<p begin="00:00:44.144" end="00:00:48.682">WHY DO WE FIGHT SO HARD NOT TO BE ILLUMINATED BY IT?</p>
<p begin="00:00:48.682" end="00:00:51.018">&gt;&gt; THAT IS A REALLY GOOD YES,</p>
<p begin="00:00:51.018" end="00:00:52.019">AND I DON&apos;T KNOW THE ANSWER.</p>
<p begin="00:00:52.019" end="00:00:56.957">I FIND IT SO FASCINATING AND EXCITING, BUT I GUESS PART OF THE REASON MIGHT BE THAT SOME OF </p>
<p begin="00:00:56.957" end="00:01:00.160">THE IDEAS ARE REMOVED FROM WHAT WE SEE IN OUR DAILY LIVES.</p>
<p begin="00:01:00.160" end="00:01:02.296">THEY&apos;RE NOT NECESSARILY THE MOST INTUITIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:02.296" end="00:01:07.668">SO WE HAVE TO GET OUTSIDE THE FRAME OF HUMAN SCALES OR HUMAN SIZES AND THINK ABOUT WHAT&apos;S </p>
<p begin="00:01:07.668" end="00:01:11.672">REALLY GOING ON AT PLACES WHERE YOU ACTUALLY NEED TECHNOLOGY TO MAKE MEASUREMENTS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:11.672" end="00:01:16.743">BUT MY HOPE IS THAT IF PEOPLE LEARN MORE ABOUT IT OR ARE AWARE OF IT THEN THEY WON&apos;T BE SO </p>
<p begin="00:01:16.743" end="00:01:19.079">AFRAID AND THEY WILL BE MORE INTERESTED.</p>
<p begin="00:01:19.079" end="00:01:22.382">&gt;&gt; Jon: I THOUGHT IT WAS INTERESTING TO WATCH IN THE FIRST PART, THERE&apos;S A SENSE THAT </p>
<p begin="00:01:22.382" end="00:01:27.254">THIS IS VERY COMPLICATED, AND IT SOUNDS MADE UP.</p>
<p begin="00:01:27.254" end="00:01:27.621">[LAUGHTER]</p>
<p begin="00:01:27.621" end="00:01:31.558">SO YOU MUST BE MAKING IT UP AND THEN IT&apos;S A VERY EASY THING TO SAY, AND THE REASON YOU&apos;RE </p>
<p begin="00:01:31.558" end="00:01:35.596">MAKING IT UP IS BECAUSE YOU&apos;RE WORKING FOR THE DEMOCRATS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:35.596" end="00:01:36.897">[LAUGHTER]</p>
<p begin="00:01:36.897" end="00:01:40.467">YOU KNOW, SOMEHOW... I DON&apos;T UNDERSTAND HOW IT BECOMES A POLITICAL ISSUE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:40.467" end="00:01:44.271">IT&apos;S A VERY STRANGE LITTLE TURN THAT HAPPENS THERE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:44.271" end="00:01:47.241">&gt;&gt; AND PART OF THE PROBLEM I THINK IS THAT WE ACTUALLY DON&apos;T </p>
<p begin="00:01:47.241" end="00:01:48.942">ALWAYS TALK ABOUT THE SCIENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:48.942" end="00:01:51.211">WE&apos;RE A LITTLE BIT AFRAID TO TALK ABOUT THE SCIENCE ITSELF.</p>
<p begin="00:01:51.211" end="00:01:52.679">WE TALK ABOUT PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:52.679" end="00:01:56.016">WHEN WE REPORT, THIS PERSON SAID THIS, THIS PERSON SAID THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:56.016" end="00:01:59.486">AND THAT&apos;S NOT THE SAME AS REALLY UNDERSTANDING WHAT IS AT THE ROOT OF IT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:59.486" end="00:02:04.958">AND IT&apos;S ALSO TRUE THAT SCIENCE ISN&apos;T ALWAYS ENTIRELY PREDICTIVE AT 100% LEVEL.</p>
<p begin="00:02:04.958" end="00:02:06.326">THAT&apos;S PART OF THE NATURE OF SCIENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:06.326" end="00:02:07.728">THAT&apos;S WHY WE STILL HAVE RESEARCH.</p>
<p begin="00:02:07.728" end="00:02:08.962">AND THAT&apos;S NOT A BAD THING.</p>
<p begin="00:02:08.962" end="00:02:13.200">AND BECAUSE WE SO MUCH WANT SCIENCE TO JUST SAY, THIS IS THE WAY IT WORKS, WE SOMETIMES LOSE </p>
<p begin="00:02:13.200" end="00:02:17.137">THAT AND WE LOSE THE FACT THAT THIS UNCERTAINTY IS ACTUALLY INTERESTING.</p>
<p begin="00:02:17.137" end="00:02:20.507">IT&apos;S PLACE PEOPLE CAN THINK AND YOU WANT TO UNDERSTAND THE ASSUMPTION, UNDERSTAND THE </p>
<p begin="00:02:20.507" end="00:02:23.510">QUESTIONS PEOPLE ARE ASKING, SO YOU CAN MOVE FORWARD.</p>
<p begin="00:02:23.510" end="00:02:29.383">&gt;&gt; Jon: I ALWAYS FELT THAT THE MORE YOU LEARN FROM SCIENTIFIC RESEARCH, THE MORE MYSTERIOUS </p>
<p begin="00:02:29.383" end="00:02:32.085">AND INCREDIBLE THE UNIVERSE BECOMES.</p>
<p begin="00:02:32.085" end="00:02:39.493">YOU KNOW, EVEN IF YOU LEARN EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED AT THE BIG BANG, WHAT A PARTICLE IS OR </p>
<p begin="00:02:39.493" end="00:02:45.098">WHATEVER OTHER THINGS YOU CLEARLY ARE MAKING UP, THAT DOESN&apos;T DISCOUNT, THAT DOESN&apos;T </p>
<p begin="00:02:45.098" end="00:02:48.268">EVER GET... I DON&apos;T THINK WE&apos;LL EVER GET TO THE POINT WHERE WE </p>
<p begin="00:02:48.268" end="00:02:52.105">KNOW EVERYTHING AND THEREFORE THERE&apos;S NO ROOM FOR GOD OR FAITH OR ANYTHING.</p>
<p begin="00:02:52.105" end="00:02:54.942">IS THAT... WHY ARE THEY INCOMPATIBLE?</p>
<p begin="00:02:54.942" end="00:02:55.843">&gt;&gt; WELL, OKAY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:55.843" end="00:02:59.346">FIRST OF ALL, I ANOTHER SAY THE FACT THERE ARE ALL THESE QUESTIONS IS FANTASTIC.</p>
<p begin="00:02:59.346" end="00:03:04.218">FIRST OF ALL, IT WOULD BE WEIRD IF WE LIVED AT THE ONE TIME WHERE WE SUDDENLY KNEW ALL THE ANSWERS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:04.218" end="00:03:06.620">THAT&apos;S WHAT GIVES US ROOM TO DO STUFF.</p>
<p begin="00:03:06.620" end="00:03:08.622">BUT IN TERMS OF ROOM FOR GOD,</p>
<p begin="00:03:08.622" end="00:03:11.658">PEOPLE CAN THINK WHATEVER THEY WANT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:11.658" end="00:03:15.896">THERE&apos;S ROOM FOR SOCIAL IMPLICATIONS OR PSYCHOLOGICAL,</p>
<p begin="00:03:15.896" end="00:03:19.399">BUT SCIENCE ACTUALLY TELLS US A VERY DEFINITE WAY OF MOVING FORWARD.</p>
<p begin="00:03:19.399" end="00:03:21.134">IT DOESN&apos;T SAY WE KNOW THE ANSWER TO EVERYTHING.</p>
<p begin="00:03:21.134" end="00:03:22.536">IT SAYS THIS IS WHAT WE KNOW.</p>
<p begin="00:03:22.536" end="00:03:27.374">THIS IS THE DEGREE OF PRECISION WITH WHICH WE KNOW IT, AND THIS IS HOW WE CAN MOVE FORWARD, AN </p>
<p begin="00:03:27.374" end="00:03:30.077">WE CAN MOVE FORWARD BY STUDYING THINGS THAT WE CAN TEST.</p>
<p begin="00:03:30.077" end="00:03:31.078">WE CAN HAVE IDEAS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:31.078" end="00:03:32.613">WE DON&apos;T YET KNOW THE ANSWER.</p>
<p begin="00:03:32.613" end="00:03:34.515">THAT WAS THE TITLE OF MY BOOK,</p>
<p begin="00:03:34.515" end="00:03:38.118">&quot;KNOCKING ON HEAVEN&apos;S DOOR&quot; WAS SUPPOSED TO CONVEY THE IDEA THAT </p>
<p begin="00:03:38.118" end="00:03:42.589">WE DO KNOW A LOT, BUT THERE IS AN EDGE BEYOND IT THAT WE&apos;RE STILL TRYING TO PRY OPEN.</p>
<p begin="00:03:42.589" end="00:03:44.324">AND SO THIS IS WHAT SIGNS DOES.</p>
<p begin="00:03:44.324" end="00:03:45.792">AND THERE&apos;S NOTHING WRONG WITH THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:45.792" end="00:03:50.831">&gt;&gt; DO YOU THINK THE CONFLUENCE OF SCIENCE AND THE INDIVIDUAL...</p>
<p begin="00:03:50.831" end="00:03:55.102">HAS SCIENCE GOTTEN SO COMPLEX AND OUR KNOWLEDGE GOTTEN SO GREAT THAT WE STILL HAVE ROOM </p>
<p begin="00:03:55.102" end="00:04:02.376">FOR THINGS LIKE, YOU KNOW, WE HAD WALTER ISAACSON STEVE JOBS,</p>
<p begin="00:04:02.376" end="00:04:07.047">THIS GUY IN HIS GARAGE TOOK WHAT WAS THE FOREFRONT OF SEMICONDUCTOR SCIENCE AND COULD </p>
<p begin="00:04:07.047" end="00:04:12.886">STILL IN HIS GARAGE FASHION NEW AND INCREDIBLE THINGS THAT WOULD HELP YOU PLAY PONG.</p>
<p begin="00:04:12.886" end="00:04:14.521">[LAUGHTER]</p>
<p begin="00:04:14.521" end="00:04:20.827">ARE WE AT A POINT WHERE THAT STILL WILL BE ABLE TO... IS THERE A VANGUARD OF THAT CAN </p>
<p begin="00:04:20.827" end="00:04:22.196">STILL OCCUR WITH THE INDIVIDUAL?</p>
<p begin="00:04:22.196" end="00:04:31.238">&gt;&gt; LOOK, YOU KNOW, WHEN PEOPLE WERE WORKING OUT IN THE EARLY 1300s HOW IT IS THIS AT TOM </p>
<p begin="00:04:31.238" end="00:04:35.475">COULD MAKE SENSE WITH NUCLEUS AND ELECTRONS, THEY WEREN&apos;T THINKING ABOUT PONG.</p>
<p begin="00:04:35.475" end="00:04:39.413">MANY YEARS LATER PEOPLE FOUND THAT, WOW, THIS HAS IMPLICATIONS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:39.413" end="00:04:41.081">THERE&apos;S SEMICONDUCTOR INDUSTRY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:41.081" end="00:04:42.616">WE CAN DO ELECTRONICS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:42.616" end="00:04:43.717">AND IT CHANGES THE WORLD.</p>
<p begin="00:04:43.717" end="00:04:46.954">I DON&apos;T THINK WE ALWAYS KNOW WHAT THOSE THINGS ARE AT THE TIME WE&apos;RE DOING IT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:46.954" end="00:04:51.558">BUT SOMEHOW IT SEEMS THAT THESE ADVANCES COME MAYBE NOT EXACTLY IN TANDEM BUT CERTAINLY WHEN WE </p>
<p begin="00:04:51.558" end="00:04:54.461">HAVE MORE KNOWLEDGE TO THINK THROUGH THEM.</p>
<p begin="00:04:54.461" end="00:04:57.197">&gt;&gt; Jon: IS THERE ANY... WHY DO YOU THINK THE FURTHER WE GET </p>
<p begin="00:04:57.197" end="00:05:03.604">INTO IT, WE&apos;RE STILL STUCK IN THAT FOSSIL FUEL, YOU KNOW,</p>
<p begin="00:05:03.604" end="00:05:08.675">ENGINE, AND WE HAVEN&apos;T BEEN ABLE FOR 100-SOME YEARS WITH ALL THE ADVANCES WE MADE IN SO MANY </p>
<p begin="00:05:08.675" end="00:05:15.182">AREAS, WHY ENERGY IS STILL SOMEWHAT IN ITS 1880s, 180 R 90s FORM STILL.</p>
<p begin="00:05:15.182" end="00:05:16.917">&gt;&gt; THIS IS PART OF THE PROBLEM.</p>
<p begin="00:05:16.917" end="00:05:19.419">BECAUSE I&apos;M THE SCIENTIST DOESN&apos;T MEAN I KNOW THE ANSWER TO THAT QUESTION.</p>
<p begin="00:05:19.419" end="00:05:20.787">&gt;&gt; HERE&apos;S THE THING.</p>
<p begin="00:05:20.787" end="00:05:21.688">HERE&apos;S PART OF THE ANSWER.</p>
<p begin="00:05:21.688" end="00:05:25.826">YOU CAN SAY ANYTHING AND I WOULD HAVE NO IDEA WHAT THE HELL YOU&apos;RE TALKING ABOUT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:25.826" end="00:05:28.896">&gt;&gt; BECAUSE I DON&apos;T THINK THE ANSWER IS ENTIRELY SCIENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:28.896" end="00:05:30.397">I THINK PART OF IT IS SCIENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:30.397" end="00:05:32.866">THERE ISN&apos;T A MAGIC BULLET YET.</p>
<p begin="00:05:32.866" end="00:05:36.103">THEY HAVEN&apos;T DEVELOPED THE NEW BATTERY THAT&apos;S GOING TO REPLACE EVERYTHING AT THIS POINT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:36.103" end="00:05:37.471">AND THAT&apos;S A DIFFICULT SCIENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:37.471" end="00:05:42.442">AND IT DOESN&apos;T HAPPEN THE WAY THE WEB HAPPENS OR THINGS EXPO INNOCENT ESTIMATE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:42.442" end="00:05:44.745">YOU HAVE TO DO SOME HARD RESEARCH TO COME UP WITH SOMETHING.</p>
<p begin="00:05:44.745" end="00:05:47.848">I THINK OBVIOUSLY THERE&apos;S A LOT OF ENTRENCHED BUSINESS INTERESTS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:47.848" end="00:05:50.717">THERE&apos;S A LOT OF OTHER THINGS INVOLVED THAT HAVE NOTHING TO DO WITH SCIENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:50.717" end="00:05:52.953">AND I THINK THAT GETS CONFUSED,</p>
<p begin="00:05:52.953" end="00:05:54.555">HOW SCIENCE INTERFACES WITH THE WORLD.</p>
<p begin="00:05:54.555" end="00:05:58.959">THAT&apos;S WHY IT&apos;S IMPORTANT TO KNOW A SCIENTIFIC THING AND HOW IT&apos;S BEING USED.</p>
<p begin="00:05:58.959" end="00:06:02.296">&gt;&gt; IT&apos;S SO NICE TO FINALLY HAVE SOMEONE COME ON AND TELL US TO </p>
<p begin="00:06:02.296" end="00:06:04.064">OUR FACES IT&apos;S ALL A BIG SCAM.</p>
<p begin="00:06:04.064" end="00:06:06.533">AND I REALLY APPRECIATE IT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:06.533" end="00:06:08.302">THANK YOU VERY MUCH.</p>
<p begin="00:06:08.302" end="00:06:10.604">KNOCKING ON HEAVEN&apos;S DOOR.</p>
<p begin="00:06:10.604" end="00:06:12.573">YOU GOT TO GET THIS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:12.573" end="00:06:15.075">LISA RANDALL.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
