<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:05.672" end="00:00:06.139">&gt;&gt; WELCOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:06.139" end="00:00:13.780">MY GUEST TONIGHT, THE FORMER DIRECTOR OF EDUCATION AT JAMES MADISON&apos;S MONOPEELIER AND A </p>
<p begin="00:00:13.780" end="00:00:17.784">FELLOW FOR THE HUMANITY, HER NEW BOOK IS CALLED &quot;A SLAVE IN THE </p>
<p begin="00:00:17.784" end="00:00:28.295">WHITE HOUSE: PAUL JENSEN AND THE MADISONS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:28.295" end="00:00:29.796">PLEASE WELCOME ELIZABETH DOWLING TAYLOR.</p>
<p begin="00:00:29.796" end="00:00:31.431">THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR BEING HERE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:31.431" end="00:00:37.571">IT&apos;S CALLED &quot;A SLAVE IN THE WHITE HOUSE.&quot; YOU KNOW, IT IS SO INTERESTING </p>
<p begin="00:00:37.571" end="00:00:39.173">TO SEE A BOOK LIKE THIS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:39.173" end="00:00:46.647">IN OUR CURRENT SORT OF FOUNDING FATHERS FETISH THAT WE ENJOY,</p>
<p begin="00:00:46.647" end="00:00:51.118">THEIR INFALLIBILITY, THEIR ULTIMATE WISDOM THAT WE ALWAYS LOOK BACK TO THEM, WE FORGET </p>
<p begin="00:00:51.118" end="00:00:56.957">THAT THE INDIVIDUAL CREDITED WITH REALLY THE FATHER OF OUR CONSTITUTION HAD 100 SLAVES.</p>
<p begin="00:00:56.957" end="00:01:01.428">&gt;&gt; WELL, YOU KNOW, THERE WERE EIGHT EARLY PRESIDENTS WHO OWNED SLAVES DURING THEIR TENURE IN </p>
<p begin="00:01:01.428" end="00:01:03.964">THE WHITE HOUSE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:03.964" end="00:01:08.535">&gt;&gt; Jon: WHY DO YOU KEEP APOLOGIZING FOR AMERICA?</p>
<p begin="00:01:08.535" end="00:01:16.777">IT&apos;S SHOCKING TO ME BECAUSE THE IMAGE WE HAVE... BOY DOES DOLLY MADISON NOT COME OFF WELL IN </p>
<p begin="00:01:16.777" end="00:01:17.511">THIS BOOK.</p>
<p begin="00:01:17.511" end="00:01:21.114">MY IMAGE OF HER WAS ALWAYS THE COURAGEOUS SAVIOR OF THE WHITE HOUSE IN 1812.</p>
<p begin="00:01:21.114" end="00:01:24.084">THEN SHE WENT ON TO MAKE THOSE DELICIOUS CAKES.</p>
<p begin="00:01:24.084" end="00:01:26.887">[LAUGHTER]</p>
<p begin="00:01:26.887" end="00:01:34.094">SHE WAS PROUD OF HERSELF FOR RESCINDING THE OFFER OF FREEDOM TO PAUL JENNING.</p>
<p begin="00:01:34.094" end="00:01:39.666">&gt;&gt; WELL, SHE ACCOMPLISHED MUCH AS FIRST LADY, BUT SHE WAS A SLAVE OWNER.</p>
<p begin="00:01:39.666" end="00:01:43.937">HER HUSBAND BEQUEATHED THE 100 SLAVES TO DOLLY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:43.937" end="00:01:46.940">JENNINGS HAD EXPECTED THAT HE WOULD BE FREED BY MADISON&apos;S WILL.</p>
<p begin="00:01:46.940" end="00:01:52.946">WHEN THAT DIDN&apos;T HAPPEN, DOLLY HAD A TERM IN HER WILL THAT SHE </p>
<p begin="00:01:52.946" end="00:01:58.919">WOULD FREE PAUL, BUT INSTEAD SHE SOLD HIM, AND THIS IS AFTER MADISON DIED AND WHILE DALI WAS </p>
<p begin="00:01:58.919" end="00:02:02.489">BACK IN WASHINGTON, BUT PAUL&apos;S FAMILY, HIS WIFE AND CHILDREN,</p>
<p begin="00:02:02.489" end="00:02:08.629">WERE OWNED BY ANOTHER MASTER, SO HE WAS SEPARATED FROM THEM AND HE DETERMINED THAT HE NEEDED TO </p>
<p begin="00:02:08.629" end="00:02:11.198">RAISE HIS OWN PURCHASE PRICE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:11.198" end="00:02:17.404">SHE SET IT AT $200, AND THAT&apos;S WHEN HE WENT TO SENATOR DANIEL WEBSTER, WHO LOANED HIM THE MONEY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:17.404" end="00:02:21.341">AND THEN JENNINGS WORKED FOR WEBSTER TO PAY IT BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:02:21.341" end="00:02:25.279">&gt;&gt; Jon: THAT&apos;S WHY I&apos;M SAYING WE HAVE TO GET BACK THE OUR </p>
<p begin="00:02:25.279" end="00:02:27.147">CONSTITUTIONAL PRINCIPLES.</p>
<p begin="00:02:27.147" end="00:02:27.614">[LAUGHTER]</p>
<p begin="00:02:27.614" end="00:02:28.382">BACK TO THE FOUNDING FATHERS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:28.382" end="00:02:35.322">CAN YOU IMAGINE... I JUST... AS YOU READ THESE STORIES, YOU JUST IMAGINE NOW IN THE CURRENT MEDIA </p>
<p begin="00:02:35.322" end="00:02:40.093">ENVIRONMENT, YOU KNOW, MADISON GOING ON ONE OF THESE NEWS SHOWS AND THEM READING THEM LIKE </p>
<p begin="00:02:40.093" end="00:02:45.265">YOU&apos;VE WRITTEN HERE, YOU KNOW,</p>
<p begin="00:02:45.265" end="00:02:52.172">THE SADDEST SLAVERY OF ALL IS BEING VICIOUS FREE BLACKS WHO KEEP THE MINDS OF OWN CENTERS A </p>
<p begin="00:02:52.172" end="00:02:56.143">STATE OF PERPETUAL SUSPICION,</p>
<p begin="00:02:56.143" end="00:02:59.646">FEAR AND ANGER AND YET YOU ALSO WROTE THE CONSTITUTION IS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:59.646" end="00:03:00.547">THAT A FLIP-FLOP?</p>
<p begin="00:03:00.547" end="00:03:02.416">&gt;&gt; THAT&apos;S AN ABSOLUTE FLIP-FLOP.</p>
<p begin="00:03:02.416" end="00:03:09.423">HE WAS A COMPLICATED MAN, AND HE KNEW HIMSELF THAT SLAVERY WAS A BLOT ON OUR REPUBLICAN CHARACTER.</p>
<p begin="00:03:09.423" end="00:03:13.060">&gt;&gt; Jon: WAS HE... YOU KNOW,</p>
<p begin="00:03:13.060" end="00:03:16.496">ISN&apos;T &quot;THEY WERE COMPLICATED MEN&quot; AN EXCUSE FOR IN THAT AREA </p>
<p begin="00:03:16.496" end="00:03:19.533">OF THEIR LIVES, THEY WERE MORALLY COWARDLY?</p>
<p begin="00:03:19.533" end="00:03:25.572">&gt;&gt; WELL, YOU KNOW, WHEN I APPROACH A BOOK LIKE THIS, MY PARTICULAR OBJECTIVE IS NEITHER </p>
<p begin="00:03:25.572" end="00:03:27.441">TO DEFEND NOR TO DENOUNCE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:27.441" end="00:03:31.445">I REALLY WANT TO TELL PAUL JENNING&apos;S STORY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:31.445" end="00:03:36.083">&gt;&gt; Jon: YEAH, THAT&apos;S NOT GOING TO FLY IN THIS ENVIRONMENT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:36.083" end="00:03:38.785">UNFORTUNATELY I&apos;M AFRAID YOU&apos;RE GOING TO HAVE TO BE A LITTLE </p>
<p begin="00:03:38.785" end="00:03:41.488">MORE PARTISAN AND PERNICIOUS IN YOUR WRITING.</p>
<p begin="00:03:41.488" end="00:03:46.827">THE AMAZING THING IS THE STORY JENNINGS HAD TO THEN GO WORK.</p>
<p begin="00:03:46.827" end="00:03:53.934">ONCE HE WAS ULTIMATELY FREED AND THEN WEBSTER DIED AND FORGAVE HIS DEBT, HE THEN HAD TO WORK TO </p>
<p begin="00:03:53.934" end="00:04:00.641">FREE HIS CHILDREN FROM... AND HE APPARENTLY HAD GREAT AFFECTION FOR THE MADISONS, BUT FREE HIS </p>
<p begin="00:04:00.641" end="00:04:04.077">CHILDREN FROM THE FAMILY THAT THE MADISONS HAD SOLD HIS CHILDREN TO.</p>
<p begin="00:04:04.077" end="00:04:10.551">&gt;&gt; YOU KNOW, HIS LIFE WAS A COURAGEOUS AND DELIBERATE AND SUCCESSFUL PURSUIT OF THE RIGHT </p>
<p begin="00:04:10.551" end="00:04:11.185">TO RISE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:11.185" end="00:04:17.457">SO, YES, WHAT HE WANTED IS A REASONABLE FACSIMILE OF WHAT WE CALL THE AMERICAN DREAM.</p>
<p begin="00:04:17.457" end="00:04:24.131">HE BOUGHT A PIECE OF LAND, HAD A MODEST HOUSE, MANAGED TO GET HIS CHILDREN FROM SLAVERY IN </p>
<p begin="00:04:24.131" end="00:04:26.066">VIRGINIA, AND THEY JOINED HIM IN WASHINGTON.</p>
<p begin="00:04:26.066" end="00:04:31.538">AND HE HAD A LOW-LEVEL JOB WORKING FOR THE DEPARTMENT OF INTERIOR, BUT IT TOOK EVERY BIT </p>
<p begin="00:04:31.538" end="00:04:39.947">OF EFFORT IN THE FACE OF GALLING PATERNALISM AND CONSTANT DISCRIMINATION TO PULL THIS OFF.</p>
<p begin="00:04:39.947" end="00:04:41.081">&gt;&gt; Jon: IT&apos;S REMARKABLE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:41.081" end="00:04:42.916">THE THING THAT NOBODY REALIZES,</p>
<p begin="00:04:42.916" end="00:04:44.418">HE WROTE NOT NECESSARILY A BOOK,</p>
<p begin="00:04:44.418" end="00:04:48.188">BUT HE WROTE OF HIS TIME WITH THE MADISONS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:48.188" end="00:04:51.792">&gt;&gt; HE&apos;S THE AUTHOR OF THE FIRST WHITE HOUSE MEMOIR, AND, AS YOU </p>
<p begin="00:04:51.792" end="00:04:56.129">KNOW, IT&apos;S DERIGGER THESE DAYS FOR ANYONE WITH WHITE HOUSE EXPERIENCE TO PUBLISH A MEMOIR.</p>
<p begin="00:04:56.129" end="00:04:56.997">&gt;&gt; Jon: RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:56.997" end="00:05:00.534">AND HE PUBLISHED, BUT YET WHY HAVE WE NEVER HEARD OF IT?</p>
<p begin="00:05:00.534" end="00:05:04.304">&gt;&gt; THERE WERE LIMITED NUMBER OF COPIES PRODUCED.</p>
<p begin="00:05:04.304" end="00:05:06.273">IT&apos;S BEEN OBSCURE ALL THIS TIME.</p>
<p begin="00:05:06.273" end="00:05:14.648">MOREOVER, THE TITLE IS &quot;A COLASHED MAN&apos;S REMINISCES OF JAMES MADISON.</p>
<p begin="00:05:14.648" end="00:05:16.216">SO IT&apos;S MORE ABOUT THE GREAT MAN.</p>
<p begin="00:05:16.216" end="00:05:18.285">MY STARTING QUESTION WAS WHAT ABOUT PAUL JENNINGS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:18.285" end="00:05:23.724">&gt;&gt; Jon: SURE, SURE, WHEN WE MAKE HIS MANUSCRIPT INTO A MOVIE, THAT WILL BE CHANGED.</p>
<p begin="00:05:23.724" end="00:05:33.600">SOMETHING LIKE &quot;THE HELP.&quot; I DON&apos;T KNOW.</p>
<p begin="00:05:33.600" end="00:05:42.276">THE STORY OF JENNINGS, YOU SPOKE WITH HIS ACTUAL RELATIVES AND WERE STUNNED AT THEIR </p>
<p begin="00:05:42.276" end="00:05:43.143">RECOLLECTIONS OF IT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:43.143" end="00:05:46.813">IT REALLY WAS PASSED DOWN TO THE FAMILY, THE STORY OF THIS MAN.</p>
<p begin="00:05:46.813" end="00:05:51.652">&gt;&gt; IT WAS SO SATISFYING TO TRACK DOWN AND INTERVIEW HIS GREAT GRANDDAUGHTER.</p>
<p begin="00:05:51.652" end="00:05:54.421">YOU KNOW, HE WAS BORN AT THE END OF THE 18th CENTURY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:54.421" end="00:05:57.491">SO IN 2008, GREAT GRANDDAUGHTER,</p>
<p begin="00:05:57.491" end="00:06:02.462">THAT&apos;S NOT MANY GENERATIONS THERE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:02.462" end="00:06:09.903">SHE WAS ABLE TO SHARE WITH ME THE FAMILY TRADITIONS THAT GO RIGHT BACK TO JENNINGS&apos; TIME.</p>
<p begin="00:06:09.903" end="00:06:14.274">FOR EXAMPLE, HE USED HIS LITERACY, IT&apos;S UNUSUAL FOR A SLAVE TO BE ABLE TO READ AND </p>
<p begin="00:06:14.274" end="00:06:19.246">WRITE, BUT JEBINGS COULD, AND HE USED IT TO FORGE PASSES AND FREE PAPERS FOR SLAVES.</p>
<p begin="00:06:19.246" end="00:06:22.249">&gt;&gt; IT REALLY IS ONE OF THOSE REMARKABLE STORIES THAT YOU </p>
<p begin="00:06:22.249" end="00:06:26.420">CAN&apos;T BELIEVE WE DON&apos;T KNOW MORE ABOUT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:26.420" end="00:06:29.389">IT&apos;S A WONDERFUL THING YOU&apos;VE DONE IN WRITING IT AND RESEARCHING IT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:29.389" end="00:06:30.390">IT&apos;S REALLY TERRIFIC.</p>
<p begin="00:06:30.390" end="00:06:32.326">A SLAVE IN THE WHITE HOUSE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:32.326" end="00:06:33.160">GET IT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:33.160" end="00:06:38.131">THE MOVIE ALL R OBVIOUSLY WITH PAUL GEE MOTI AS MADISON AND...</p>
<p begin="00:06:38.131" end="00:06:40.133">&gt;&gt; AND WHO HAS JENNINGS?</p>
<p begin="00:06:40.133" end="00:06:43.704">&gt;&gt; CUBA GOODING, JR., ODDLY ENOUGH, SURPRISINGLY ENOUGH.</p>
<p begin="00:06:43.704" end="00:06:45.205">IT&apos;S ON THE BOOKSHELVES NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:06:45.205" end="00:06:46.306">PLEASE GET IT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:46.306" end="00:06:48.075">ELIZABETH DOWLING TAYLOR, THANK YOU SO MUCH.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
