<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:05.772" end="00:00:08.942">&gt;&gt; Jon: MY GUEST TONIGHT IS A WRITER, HIS NEW BOOK IS CALLED </p>
<p begin="00:00:08.942" end="00:00:14.348">&quot;THE PIRATES OF SOMALIA: INSIDE THE HIDDEN WORLD.&quot; PLEASE WELCOME TO THE PROGRAM </p>
<p begin="00:00:14.348" end="00:00:16.016">JAY BAHADUR.</p>
<p begin="00:00:16.016" end="00:00:17.951">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) THANKS FOR JOINING US.</p>
<p begin="00:00:17.951" end="00:00:20.621">COME AND SIT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:20.621" end="00:00:26.627">THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE THE BOOK IS CALLED &quot;THE PIRATES OF SOMALIA.</p>
<p begin="00:00:26.627" end="00:00:30.130">THE HIDDEN WORLD.&quot; JAY, YOU ARE HOW OLD?</p>
<p begin="00:00:30.130" end="00:00:31.832">&gt;&gt; I&apos;M 27 NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:00:31.832" end="00:00:38.672">&gt;&gt; Jon: HOW OLD WERE YOU WHEN YOU WENT BY YOURSELF TO SOMALIA TO LIVE AMONGST THE PIRATES?</p>
<p begin="00:00:38.672" end="00:00:41.875">&gt;&gt; WELL, WHEN I STARTED SCHEMING ABOUT IT I WAS 24.</p>
<p begin="00:00:41.875" end="00:00:46.180">&gt;&gt; Jon: AS YOUR FATHER, I CANNOT ALLOW THIS!</p>
<p begin="00:00:46.180" end="00:00:46.580">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:00:46.580" end="00:00:50.083">&gt;&gt; YOU KNOW, SURPRISINGLY MY PARENTS SAID VERY LITTLE ABOUT IT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:50.083" end="00:00:53.754">WHICH IS... CAUSED ME TO BECOME CONCERNED ABOUT IT SINCE THEN BECAUSE...</p>
<p begin="00:00:53.754" end="00:00:54.154">(LAUGHTER).</p>
<p begin="00:00:54.154" end="00:00:57.457">EVERY MEDIA INTERVIEW I DO PEOPLE ASK &quot;WHAT DID YOUR PARENTS THINK?&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:00:57.457" end="00:01:00.894">AND I THINK &quot;NEVER SAID ANYTHING.&quot; THEN AGAIN I NEVER HAD A TALK </p>
<p begin="00:01:00.894" end="00:01:04.097">ABOUT DRUGS, SEX, ALCOHOL, SO...</p>
<p begin="00:01:04.097" end="00:01:09.536">NEITHER DID I HAVE ONE ABOUT GOING TO EMBED WITH VICIOUS MEN ON MY OWN.</p>
<p begin="00:01:09.536" end="00:01:13.207">&gt;&gt; Jon: SO YOUR PARENTS ARE SOMEWHAT LAISSEZ-FAIRE WHEN IT COMES TO PARENTING?</p>
<p begin="00:01:13.207" end="00:01:15.309">&gt;&gt; YEAH, I GUESS YOU COULD SAY THAT, YES.</p>
<p begin="00:01:15.309" end="00:01:16.109">&gt;&gt; Jon: FAIR ENOUGH.</p>
<p begin="00:01:16.109" end="00:01:18.412">IT IS A REMARKABLE STORY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:18.412" end="00:01:24.384">THERE&apos;S A GREAT SEQUENCE THAT DICTATES YOUR, I GUESS, 45-HOUR </p>
<p begin="00:01:24.384" end="00:01:30.591">TRIP, AS A 24-YEAR-OLD YOU DON&apos;T KNOW WHERE YOU&apos;RE GOING AND YOU </p>
<p begin="00:01:30.591" end="00:01:38.632">LAND, UKRAINIAN PILOT WITH COLD WAR TECHNOLOGY LANDS YOU SOMALIA AND YOU STEP OUT OF THE PLANE </p>
<p begin="00:01:38.632" end="00:01:40.601">AND THINK...</p>
<p begin="00:01:40.601" end="00:01:47.708">&gt;&gt; WELL, I SAID TO MYSELF &quot;I&apos;M IN (BLEEP) SOMALIA.&quot; (LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:01:47.708" end="00:01:50.210">THIS WAS SOMETHING... AND I TALK ABOUT IN THE THE BOOK HOW IT&apos;S A </p>
<p begin="00:01:50.210" end="00:01:55.115">STRANGE EXPERIENCE GOING FROM A PLACE WHERE I&apos;VE ALWAYS CONSUMED NEWS MY WHOLE LIFE TO A PLACE </p>
<p begin="00:01:55.115" end="00:01:57.117">THAT&apos;S REALLY ONLY BEEN DEFINED BY THE NEWS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:57.117" end="00:02:00.053">I NEVER KNEW ANYONE WHO&apos;D BEEN TO SOMALIA.</p>
<p begin="00:02:00.053" end="00:02:01.722">I WOULD GUESS THE SAME IS TRUE OF YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:02:01.722" end="00:02:03.524">&gt;&gt; Jon: NO, I&apos;VE GOT SOME...</p>
<p begin="00:02:03.524" end="00:02:03.924">(LAUGHTER).</p>
<p begin="00:02:03.924" end="00:02:07.895">SOME PEOPLE ON MY CHRISTMAS CARD LIST.</p>
<p begin="00:02:07.895" end="00:02:11.365">&gt;&gt; SO IT&apos;S A COUNTRY THAT&apos;S TOTALLY BEEN MANUFACTURED OUT OF </p>
<p begin="00:02:11.365" end="00:02:17.738">NEWS REPORTS AND COMING TO TERMS WITH THAT WAS SORT OF AN EXPERIENCE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:17.738" end="00:02:21.775">&gt;&gt; Jon: IS THE PORTRAYAL OF SOMALIA, THEN, MORE CHAOTIC,</p>
<p begin="00:02:21.775" end="00:02:25.145">LESS CHAOTIC, IS IT IN ANY WAY AN ACCURATE PORTRAYAL?</p>
<p begin="00:02:25.145" end="00:02:28.081">IS IT SUPERFICIAL AND EXAGGERATED?</p>
<p begin="00:02:28.081" end="00:02:28.448">WHAT&apos;S...</p>
<p begin="00:02:28.448" end="00:02:32.085">&gt;&gt; WELL, I THINK IT HAS TO BE SUPERFICIAL BECAUSE ONE THING THAT DOESN&apos;T COME ACROSS IN </p>
<p begin="00:02:32.085" end="00:02:37.558">MEDIA REPORTS IS THE FACT THAT SOMALIA IS INCREDIBLY SEGREGATE BID CLAN AND SO WHAT YOU HAVE ON </p>
<p begin="00:02:37.558" end="00:02:39.893">THE GROUND IS IN THE SOUTH IT&apos;S A MESS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:39.893" end="00:02:42.095">IT&apos;S SORT OF LIKE WHAT YOU SEE IN THE NEWS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:42.095" end="00:02:46.233">IN THE NORTH THERE&apos;S A LOT OF MINI STATES THAT HAVE CROPPED UP WHERE LOCAL PEOPLE HAVE COME </p>
<p begin="00:02:46.233" end="00:02:48.635">TOGETHER AND, YOU KNOW, FORMED GOVERNMENTS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:48.635" end="00:02:50.771">BECAUSE PEOPLE GENERALLY DON&apos;T LIKE TO LIVE IN ANARCHY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:50.771" end="00:02:57.811">AND SO YOU HAVE A NUMBER OF THESE STATELETS AND ONE OF THESE REGIONS I ENDED UP GOING TO WAS </p>
<p begin="00:02:57.811" end="00:03:06.920">THE CENTER OF THE WHOLE PIRACY EXPLOSION 2008 AND IT WAS CALLED PUNTLAND.</p>
<p begin="00:03:06.920" end="00:03:11.058">THE BOOK WAS ORIGINALLY CALLED &quot;THE PIRATES OF PUNTLAND&quot; BUT </p>
<p begin="00:03:11.058" end="00:03:15.395">NOBODY KNOWS WHAT PUNTLAND IS SO...</p>
<p begin="00:03:15.395" end="00:03:15.796">(LAUGHTER).</p>
<p begin="00:03:15.796" end="00:03:21.134">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU MENTION THE TERM IN THE BOOK THAT THEY PREFERRED TO BE REFERRED AS...</p>
<p begin="00:03:21.134" end="00:03:23.804">&gt;&gt; SAVIORS OF THE SEA.</p>
<p begin="00:03:23.804" end="00:03:30.944">WHICH IS A ROUGH TRANSLATION BUT, YEAH, IT&apos;S... IT ENCAPSULATES HOW THEY SEE THEMSELVES.</p>
<p begin="00:03:30.944" end="00:03:33.280">&gt;&gt; Jon: WHAT I DIDN&apos;T REALIZE IS IT&apos;S THE FIRST GENERATION OF </p>
<p begin="00:03:33.280" end="00:03:36.550">THE PIRATES COMES FROM DEFENDING THEIR LOBSTER FISHING TURF.</p>
<p begin="00:03:36.550" end="00:03:40.721">THAT SOME OF THESE PIRATES WERE ACTUALLY LOBSTER FISHERMEN.</p>
<p begin="00:03:40.721" end="00:03:41.288">&gt;&gt; RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:41.288" end="00:03:43.090">AND THAT&apos;S TRUE FOR A VERY,</p>
<p begin="00:03:43.090" end="00:03:44.191">VERY, VERY SMALL NUMBER.</p>
<p begin="00:03:44.191" end="00:03:49.162">WHAT MOST PEOPLE DON&apos;T KNOW IS THAT FISHING WAS NEVER A HUGE PART OF THE SOMALI ECONOMY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:49.162" end="00:03:51.765">IN FACT, THE FORMER DICTATOR,</p>
<p begin="00:03:51.765" end="00:03:57.538">THE ONLY REASON THERE WERE FISHING COMMUNITIES IS BECAUSE HE WAS A MARXIST AND WANTED TO </p>
<p begin="00:03:57.538" end="00:03:58.105">REENGINEER SOCIETY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:58.105" end="00:04:03.777">SO HE ESSENTIALLY STARTED FORCIBLY RELOCATING PEOPLE INTO THESE FISHING COMMUNITIES IN THE </p>
<p begin="00:04:03.777" end="00:04:06.847">&apos;70s AND &apos;80s WHICH WAS HOW SOME OF THE PIRATES STARTED.</p>
<p begin="00:04:06.847" end="00:04:08.582">BUT NOW IT&apos;S SORT OF GONE...</p>
<p begin="00:04:08.582" end="00:04:10.117">IT&apos;S FLOATED WAY BEYOND THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:10.117" end="00:04:13.754">IT&apos;S BECOME PART OF THE PIRATE P.R. MACHINE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:13.754" end="00:04:16.657">AND THERE VERY MUCH IS A PIRATE P.R. MACHINE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:16.657" end="00:04:17.291">I SWEAR.</p>
<p begin="00:04:17.291" end="00:04:21.061">WHEN YOU SPEAK TO THEM IT&apos;S LIKE THEY&apos;RE BEING ISSUED PRESS RELEASES.</p>
<p begin="00:04:21.061" end="00:04:25.899">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU SAID ONE OF THE BEST WAYS TO INTERVIEW THEM WAS TO GET THEM CHEW ON... HOW DO </p>
<p begin="00:04:25.899" end="00:04:29.536">YOU... KA&apos;AT, THE LEAF THAT MAKES THEM DROWSY...</p>
<p begin="00:04:29.536" end="00:04:31.071">&gt;&gt; Jon: QUITE THE OPPOSITE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:31.071" end="00:04:35.742">IT&apos;S LIKE A COCA LEAF, SOMETHING THAT REALLY JACKS YOU UP.</p>
<p begin="00:04:35.742" end="00:04:40.380">(LAUGHTER) AND THE... I THOUGHT IT WAS THE FUNNIEST THING IN THE WORLD BECAUSE YOU THINK, YOU KNOW,</p>
<p begin="00:04:40.380" end="00:04:45.752">PIRATES ARE... YOU READ IN THE MEDIA THAT THEY&apos;RE BUILDING HUGE </p>
<p begin="00:04:45.752" end="00:04:50.691">HOUSES AND LIVE THESE LUXURIOUS LIFE-STYLES BUT THEY SPEND IT ALL ON THIS DRUG.</p>
<p begin="00:04:50.691" end="00:04:51.792">IT&apos;S...</p>
<p begin="00:04:51.792" end="00:04:54.361">(LAUGHTER).</p>
<p begin="00:04:54.361" end="00:04:58.799">IT&apos;S A REALLY FOUL-TASTING LEAF IMPORTED FROM KENYA AND ETHIOPIA.</p>
<p begin="00:04:58.799" end="00:05:04.104">THEY CAN&apos;T GROW IT THERE SO THEY&apos;RE SENDING THE MONEY BACK INTO THE INTERNATIONAL MARKETSES.</p>
<p begin="00:05:04.104" end="00:05:07.541">AND I REALIZED VERY CONVICTLY THAT THIS WAS THE WAY TO A PIRATES&apos; HEART.</p>
<p begin="00:05:07.541" end="00:05:12.246">YOU BRING HIM BAGS OF KA&apos;AT, YOU NEED TO BRING BAGS OF THEM, CHEW </p>
<p begin="00:05:12.246" end="00:05:15.716">IT FOR HOURS IN A PICNIC-LIKE SETTING...</p>
<p begin="00:05:15.716" end="00:05:24.558">(LAUGHTER).</p>
<p begin="00:05:24.558" end="00:05:28.228">&gt;&gt; Jon: I JUST HATE IT WHEN ANTS (BLEEP) THE WHOLE THING UP.</p>
<p begin="00:05:28.228" end="00:05:29.162">GO AHEAD.</p>
<p begin="00:05:29.162" end="00:05:33.667">&gt;&gt; I WAS TOLD WHEN I WAS TRYING IT FOR THE FIRST TIME THAT IT WOULD EITHER MAKE ME SEX CRAZED </p>
<p begin="00:05:33.667" end="00:05:34.935">OR RELAXED AND TALKATIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:34.935" end="00:05:42.176">I DON&apos;T KNOW WHY THERE WAS SUCH A DICHOTOMY BETWEEN THE TWO EFFECTS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:42.176" end="00:05:48.382">(LAUGHTER) BUT IT MADE ME RELAXED AND TALKATIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:48.382" end="00:05:53.554">(LAUGHTER) A LOT OF THE PIRATES IT ACTUALLY REALLY MAKES THEM QUITE SEX CRAZED.</p>
<p begin="00:05:53.554" end="00:05:57.524">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU WOULD THINK THAT SOMALI PIRATES WOULD BE MORE RESPONSIBLE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:57.524" end="00:06:02.462">(LAUGHTER) AND YET IT&apos;S REALLY... IT&apos;S A GREAT READ AND THE FACT OF </p>
<p begin="00:06:02.462" end="00:06:07.367">MEETING YOU AND SEEING HOW YOUNG YOU ARE AND ALL THAT DEPRESSES THE HELL OUT OF ME.</p>
<p begin="00:06:07.367" end="00:06:11.071">(LAUGHTER) BUT IT&apos;S REALLY A GREAT PIECE OF WORK AND THANK YOU FOR BEING ON THE SHOW.</p>
<p begin="00:06:11.071" end="00:06:13.640">&quot;THE PIRATES OF SOMALIA&quot; IS ON  </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
