<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:04.371" end="00:00:06.740">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) </p>
<p begin="00:00:06.740" end="00:00:07.407">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELCOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:07.407" end="00:00:12.179">MY GUEST TONIGHT, SHE WAS A TWO TERM GOVERNOR OF THE GREAT STATE OF MICHIGAN.</p>
<p begin="00:00:12.179" end="00:00:16.250">HER NEW BOOK WHICH SHE COWROTE WITH HER HUSBAND IS CALLED A GOVERNOR&apos;S STORY,</p>
<p begin="00:00:16.250" end="00:00:20.454">THE FIGHT FOR JOBS IN AMERICA&apos;S ECONOMIC FUTURE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:20.454" end="00:00:24.024">PLEASE WELCOME TO THE PROGRAM JENNIFER GRANHOLM.</p>
<p begin="00:00:24.024" end="00:00:31.131">(APPLAUSE) HOW ARE YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:00:31.131" end="00:00:33.400">&gt;&gt; I&apos;M GREAT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:33.400" end="00:00:34.301">&gt;&gt; Jon: GOVERNOR&apos;S STORY,</p>
<p begin="00:00:34.301" end="00:00:36.503">FIGHT FOR JOBS AND AMERICA&apos;S ECONOMIC FUTURE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:36.503" end="00:00:42.042">YESTERDAY WE HAD ON ANOTHER MIDWESTERN GOVERNOR FACED WITH A LOT OF SIMILAR THINGS </p>
<p begin="00:00:42.042" end="00:00:47.414">THAT YOU FACED IN MICHIGAN ON THE REPUBLICAN SIDE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:47.414" end="00:00:51.351">HOW MUCH DO GOVERNORS COME TOGETHER ON POLICY?</p>
<p begin="00:00:51.351" end="00:00:56.456">HOW MUCH OF IT-- WHEN YOU ARE A GOVERNOR HOW MUCH IS IDEAOLOGICAL, HOW MUCH IS PRAGMATIC.</p>
<p begin="00:00:56.456" end="00:01:00.894">&gt;&gt; A TON OF IT IS PRAK MATIC BUT WE DO COMPETE AGAINST ONE ANOTHER, FOR JOBS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:00.894" end="00:01:03.964">WE&apos;RE ALWAYS BOASTING OH, I GOT THIS JOB FROM, YOU KNOW,</p>
<p begin="00:01:03.964" end="00:01:05.666">ILLINOIS OR INDIANA OR TEXAS,</p>
<p begin="00:01:05.666" end="00:01:08.068">EVERY GOVERNOR IS IN THE GAME OF COMPETING FOR JOBS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:08.068" end="00:01:11.171">AND THAT&apos;S NOT A VERY GOOD NATIONAL STRATEGY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:11.171" end="00:01:13.841">&gt;&gt; Jon: SO YOU ARE NOT JUST COMPETING GLOBALLY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:13.841" end="00:01:14.575">&gt;&gt; NO.</p>
<p begin="00:01:14.575" end="00:01:17.578">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU&apos;RE ACTUALLY COMPETING WITH RIGHT-TO-WORK STATES.</p>
<p begin="00:01:17.578" end="00:01:23.083">&gt;&gt; WELL, AND EVERY GOVERNOR HAS AN INTERVENTIONIST ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT </p>
<p begin="00:01:23.083" end="00:01:27.254">STRATEGY, YOU KNOW, RICK PERRY WHO SAYS, YOU KNOW, I WANT TO GET GOVERNMENT OUT </p>
<p begin="00:01:27.254" end="00:01:33.961">OF YOUR BUSINESS, BUT EVERY DAY HIS ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT TEAM HAS BIG ECONOMIC </p>
<p begin="00:01:33.961" end="00:01:37.431">DEVELOPMENT FUND AND THEY&apos;RE LURING BUSINESSES THAT ARE STRATEGIC TO TEXAS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:37.431" end="00:01:41.535">AN THEY&apos;RE CLOSING DEALS WITH SOME MONEY FROM THIS FUND THAT&apos;S PAID FOR BY OIL </p>
<p begin="00:01:41.535" end="00:01:43.170">&amp; GAS ROYALTIES.</p>
<p begin="00:01:43.170" end="00:01:45.405">EVERY STATE HAS GOT SOME VERSION OF THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:45.405" end="00:01:50.110">BUT THE BOTTOM LINE S THE REASON WHY WE WROTE THIS BOOK IS THAT IS A REALLY BAD NATIONAL STRATEGY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:50.110" end="00:01:56.149">BECAUSE YOU ARE JUST MOVING BUSINESSES FROM ONE STATE TO ANOTHER, ALL THROUGH TAX INCENTIVES.</p>
<p begin="00:01:56.149" end="00:02:02.055">YOU&apos;RE REALLY-- RATHER THAN COMPETING AND INVITING THE GLOBE TO INVEST.</p>
<p begin="00:02:02.055" end="00:02:07.794">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU&apos;RE SUGGESTING A DARWINNIAN STRATEGY EVERY MAN FOR THEMSELVES, MAY THE </p>
<p begin="00:02:07.794" end="00:02:09.830">BEST MAN WIN IS NOT A GOOD NATIONAL STRATEGY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:09.830" end="00:02:12.566">BECAUSE I DON&apos;T KNOW THAT I BUY THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:12.566" end="00:02:17.137">A, I LOVE THE ROUND-ROBIN ASPECT OF IT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:17.137" end="00:02:21.408">I THINK THE BCS COULD LEARN A THING OR TWO.</p>
<p begin="00:02:21.408" end="00:02:25.879">(LAUGHTER) HIS SUGGESTION, OBVIOUSLY,</p>
<p begin="00:02:25.879" end="00:02:31.585">YOU KNOW, THE BIG IDEA RIGHT NOW THAT&apos;S FLOATING IS WE MUST ONLY CUT-- WE MUST DO </p>
<p begin="00:02:31.585" end="00:02:37.457">WHATEVER WE CAN TO MAKE CORPORATIONS COMFORTABLE AND WANT TO BE WITH US, LOVE US.</p>
<p begin="00:02:37.457" end="00:02:42.896">WHAT CAN WE DO FOR YOU, THE BOOK IS JUST HEARTBREAKING,</p>
<p begin="00:02:42.896" end="00:02:44.965">STORY AFTER HEARTBREAKING STORY.</p>
<p begin="00:02:44.965" end="00:02:46.500">&gt;&gt; BUT IT HAS A HOPEFUL ENDING.</p>
<p begin="00:02:46.500" end="00:02:48.402">&gt;&gt; Jon: YES, DON&apos;T SPOIL IT FOR PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:48.402" end="00:02:49.102">&gt;&gt; OKAY, ALL RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:02:49.102" end="00:02:50.470">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:02:50.470" end="00:02:55.909">&gt;&gt; JUST SAYING.</p>
<p begin="00:02:55.909" end="00:02:57.945">&gt;&gt; Jon: BRUCE WILLIST IS DEAD THE WHOLE TIME.</p>
<p begin="00:02:57.945" end="00:03:02.716">BUT IT, IS, YOU ARE FIELDING CALLS FROM BUSINESSES CONSTANTLY SAYING TO YOUING </p>
<p begin="00:03:02.716" end="00:03:06.787">I&apos;M SORRY, WE&apos;RE MOVING TO TEXAS, IN THE CASE OF COMERICA MOVED THEIR </p>
<p begin="00:03:06.787" end="00:03:08.155">HEADQUARTERS TO TEXAS AND OTHERS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:08.155" end="00:03:12.092">AND IT&apos;S HEARTBREAKING TO HEAR YOU HAVE NO RECOURSE TO THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:12.092" end="00:03:17.664">&gt;&gt; WELL, THAT&apos;S-- EVERYTHING THAT IS HAPPENING TO THIS COUNTRY HAPPENS IN MICHIGAN FIRST.</p>
<p begin="00:03:17.664" end="00:03:21.835">BECAUSE WE NEVER CAME OUT OF THE 2 001, 2002 RECESSION.</p>
<p begin="00:03:21.835" end="00:03:24.905">AND YOU KNOW, EVERYBODY NOW IS SCRATCHING THEIR HEADS,</p>
<p begin="00:03:24.905" end="00:03:27.674">HOW DO YOU CREATE JOBS IN THIS GLOBAL ECONOMY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:27.674" end="00:03:32.513">IT&apos;S NOT BY THE SOLUTIONS THAT ARE BEING PROPOSED BY MANY WHO ARE SAYING THAT THE </p>
<p begin="00:03:32.513" end="00:03:36.617">THING WE OUGHT TO DO IS SIMPLY CUT TAXES AND CUT GOVERNMENT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:36.617" end="00:03:43.090">AND JUST AS AN EXAMPLE FROM THE LABORATORY OF DEMOCRACY THAT IS MICHIGAN, IN MY </p>
<p begin="00:03:43.090" end="00:03:48.862">TERMS AS GOVERNOR, IN MY FIRST TERM I CUT TAXES 99 TIMES.</p>
<p begin="00:03:48.862" end="00:03:52.666">I KNOW MY DETRACKERS ARE GOING TO SAY, OH, NO.</p>
<p begin="00:03:52.666" end="00:03:54.701">AND-- I&apos;M JUST SAYING, WAIT,</p>
<p begin="00:03:54.701" end="00:03:56.370">WAIT, WAIT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:56.370" end="00:04:03.043">&gt;&gt; Jon: CAN I HEAR THE ACCENT THAT YOUR DETRACTORS USE AGAIN, BECAUSE I THOUGHT THAT WAS -- </p>
<p begin="00:04:03.043" end="00:04:07.381">&gt;&gt; CUT A LOT OF TAXES, CUT GOVERNMENT MORE THAN ANY STATE IN NATION.</p>
<p begin="00:04:07.381" end="00:04:08.682">WE HAVE CUT MORE EMPLOYEES,</p>
<p begin="00:04:08.682" end="00:04:09.716">CUT MORE SPENDING.</p>
<p begin="00:04:09.716" end="00:04:13.854">WE WERE 48th IN THE COUNTRY BY THE TIME I LEFT OFFICE IN TERMS OF THE SIZE OF GOVERNMENT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:13.854" end="00:04:16.256">AND YOU WOULD THINK THAT WITH ALL THAT TAX CUTTING,</p>
<p begin="00:04:16.256" end="00:04:20.761">AND WITH ALL THAT SPENDING REDUCTION, REDUCING THE SIZE OF GOVERNMENT, THAT WE WOULD </p>
<p begin="00:04:20.761" end="00:04:22.062">BE NUMBER ONE IN EMPLOYMENT,</p>
<p begin="00:04:22.062" end="00:04:22.763">RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:22.763" end="00:04:23.931">IF THAT WERE THE SOLUTION.</p>
<p begin="00:04:23.931" end="00:04:28.836">BUT ALAS, WE WERE THE NUMBER ONE IN UNEMPLOYMENT FOR MANY YEARS IN THE PAST DECADE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:28.836" end="00:04:29.203">WHY?</p>
<p begin="00:04:29.203" end="00:04:30.537">SOMETHING ELSE WAS GOING ON.</p>
<p begin="00:04:30.537" end="00:04:35.709">AND IT WAS THAT THE STRUCTURE OF OUR ECONOMY WAS CHANGING BECAUSE OF GLOBAL EVASION.</p>
<p begin="00:04:35.709" end="00:04:41.148">AND THOSE OLD THEORIES WERE NOT APPLICABLE TO THIS NEW 21st CENTURY GLOBAL ECONOMY </p>
<p begin="00:04:41.148" end="00:04:44.218">WHERE WE ARE COMPETING AGAINST CHINA AND INDIA AND OTHER PLACES.</p>
<p begin="00:04:44.218" end="00:04:52.459">&gt;&gt; Jon: THIS IS WHAT I WAS TRYING TO SAY YESTERDAY TO THE GENTLEMAN, WAS-- YOU COULD OFFER -- </p>
<p begin="00:04:52.459" end="00:04:54.294">&gt;&gt; GOVERNOR DANIELS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:54.294" end="00:04:56.163">&gt;&gt; Jon: GOVERNOR DANIELS,</p>
<p begin="00:04:56.163" end="00:05:00.934">AND YOU CAN OFFER ZERO PERCENT TAX RATE TO CORPORATIONS AND THAT STILL </p>
<p begin="00:05:00.934" end="00:05:08.275">DOESN&apos;T MEAN THEY ARE GOING TO MAKE THEIR iPHONES, THE PARTS ANYPLACE BUT CHINA.</p>
<p begin="00:05:08.275" end="00:05:13.547">SO IN THAT ENVIRONMENT, WHAT DO WE DO AND HOW DO THESE-- DON&apos;T YOU THINK </p>
<p begin="00:05:13.547" end="00:05:18.652">THESE CORPORATIONS BEGIN TO LOOK AT US AS DESPERATE SUITORS IN THEY ARE NOW THE </p>
<p begin="00:05:18.652" end="00:05:21.755">ONLY GIRL AT AN ALL-MALE BOARDING SCHOOL.</p>
<p begin="00:05:21.755" end="00:05:26.560">AND IT&apos;S JUST LIKE WELL, HE GAVE ME A CORVETTE, I DON&apos;T KNOW.</p>
<p begin="00:05:26.560" end="00:05:27.494">WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO.</p>
<p begin="00:05:27.494" end="00:05:30.297">&gt;&gt; AND THAT&apos;S WHAT HAPPENS STATE TO STATE RIGHT NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:05:30.297" end="00:05:31.965">AND IT&apos;S TRUE COUNTRY TO COUNTRY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:31.965" end="00:05:35.369">BUT NO STATE HAS THE ABILITY TO COMPETE AGAINST CHINA.</p>
<p begin="00:05:35.369" end="00:05:36.837">THERE HAS GOT TO BE A PARTNERSHIP.</p>
<p begin="00:05:36.837" end="00:05:42.242">IN FACT, YOU KNOW, THE ONLY THING THAT WORKS IN MICHIGAN AND THE REASON WHY IN 2010 </p>
<p begin="00:05:42.242" end="00:05:45.646">THINGS STARTED TO TURN AROUND, WE&apos;RE CERTAINLY NOT THERE YET, BELIEVE ME.</p>
<p begin="00:05:45.646" end="00:05:47.347">BUT WE STOPPED THE DROP.</p>
<p begin="00:05:47.347" end="00:05:52.452">WE STARTED TO CLIMB OUT, OUR UNEMPLOYMENT RATE DROPPED SIX TIMES FASTER THAN THE </p>
<p begin="00:05:52.452" end="00:05:53.820">NATIONAL AVERAGE IN 2010,</p>
<p begin="00:05:53.820" end="00:05:54.221">WHY?</p>
<p begin="00:05:54.221" end="00:05:58.992">BECAUSE THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION GAVE US THE OPPORTUNITY TO PARTNER WITH THE PRIVATE SECTOR TO </p>
<p begin="00:05:58.992" end="00:06:06.133">COMPETE FOR FEDERAL GRANTS AND WE PUT STATE TAX INCENTIVES AND UNIVERSITIES FOR THE BATTERY FOR THE </p>
<p begin="00:06:06.133" end="00:06:07.201">ELECTRIC VEHICLE, FOR EXAMPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:07.201" end="00:06:12.206">WE WERE ABLE TO GET THE LITHIUM ION BATTERY WHICH PREVIOUSLY WAS ALL IN ASIA.</p>
<p begin="00:06:12.206" end="00:06:14.441">BUT WE WANTED TO BUILD THE ELECTRIC CAR.</p>
<p begin="00:06:14.441" end="00:06:16.310">YOU HAVE TO BUILD THE GUTS HERE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:16.310" end="00:06:22.816">AND SO WE GOT 18 COMPANIES TO COME TO MICHIGAN, IT WAS ONLY THROUGH THAT INVESTMENT </p>
<p begin="00:06:22.816" end="00:06:24.151">THAT WE WERE ABLE TO GO.</p>
<p begin="00:06:24.151" end="00:06:25.519">CAN I JUST-- .</p>
<p begin="00:06:25.519" end="00:06:27.554">&gt;&gt; Jon: IS IT OKAY IF YOU-- YOU CAN STICK AROUND.</p>
<p begin="00:06:27.554" end="00:06:30.357">WE&apos;LL GO TO COMMERCIAL AND COME BACK AND TALK FOR A LITTLE BIT AND YOU CAN </p>
<p begin="00:06:30.357" end="00:06:31.525">EXPLAIN THE PUBLIC PRIVATE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:31.525" end="00:06:38.632">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) I SAID THIS YESTERDAY, TO THE GUY, YOU KNOW, THEY MAY WANT TO INSIST THAT </p>
<p begin="00:06:38.632" end="00:06:40.934">CORPORATIONS ARE PEOPLE, BUT CORPORATIONS ARE CERTAINLY NOT AMERICANS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:40.934" end="00:06:43.070">AND THERE&apos;S GOT TO BE A WAY TO -- </p>
<p begin="00:06:43.070" end="00:06:46.807">&gt;&gt; SO GOVERNOR, ON THE BOOK SHELVES </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
