<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:06.139" end="00:00:06.673">FEBRUARY 24, 2011.</p>
<p begin="00:00:06.673" end="00:00:09.610">FROM COMEDY CENTRAL&apos;S WORLD NEWS HEADQUARTERS IN NEW YORK, THIS </p>
<p begin="00:00:09.610" end="00:00:11.445">IS &quot;THE DAILY SHOW&quot; WITH JON STEWART.</p>
<p begin="00:00:11.445" end="00:00:16.216">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE)  <span tts:color="#ffff00">Captioning sponsored by</span> </p>
<p begin="00:00:16.216" end="00:00:30.898"> <span tts:color="#ffff00">COMEDY CENTRAL</span> (CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) </p>
<p begin="00:00:30.898" end="00:00:34.501">&gt;&gt; Jon: VERY QUICKLY, BEFORE WE GET STARTED, JUST... WE ALSO </p>
<p begin="00:00:34.501" end="00:00:38.338">DIDN&apos;T TALK ABOUT TUNA SALADS AND EGG SALADS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:38.338" end="00:00:42.409">NOW THAT&apos;S SOMETHING SOMETHING THAT YOU TRADITIONLY ASSOCIATE WITH A NEW YORK DELI, BUT IS </p>
<p begin="00:00:42.409" end="00:00:43.844">YOUR FATHER A RUG LA MAN?</p>
<p begin="00:00:43.844" end="00:00:45.212">IS HE A RUG LA MAN?</p>
<p begin="00:00:45.212" end="00:00:49.016">DOES HE LIKE A NICE JEWISH PASTRY OR A BOBKA?</p>
<p begin="00:00:49.016" end="00:00:51.018">A CHOCOLATE BOBKA?</p>
<p begin="00:00:51.018" end="00:00:55.789">THIS IS A BOBKA THAT YOU WOULD NO SOONER EAT THAN (BEEP).</p>
<p begin="00:00:55.789" end="00:00:57.457">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) THIS IS THE BEST.</p>
<p begin="00:00:57.457" end="00:01:07.201">YOU WILL... FOR THOSE OF YOU DON&apos;T KNOW, HER FATHER WANTED A SANDWICH FROM THE DELI.</p>
<p begin="00:01:07.201" end="00:01:12.673">(LAUGHTER) I HAD MARRIED ONE OF THEIR CORN BEEF SANDWICHES BACK IN 1988 </p>
<p begin="00:01:12.673" end="00:01:14.808">BEFORE ANYBODY... ALL RIGHT, I&apos;M SORRY.</p>
<p begin="00:01:14.808" end="00:01:19.513">LITERALLY MY FAVORITE TOPIC TO TALK ABOUT WELCOME TO &quot;THE DAILY SHOW.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:01:19.513" end="00:01:25.552">MY GUEST TONIGHT, CHAIRMAN OF THE COUNCIL FOR ECONOMIC ADVISORS, US A STAN GOOLSBEE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:25.552" end="00:01:26.019">HE&apos;LL BE HERE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:26.019" end="00:01:32.726">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) BY THE WAY, I&apos;M BACK FROM THE BIRD FLU BONN.</p>
<p begin="00:01:32.726" end="00:01:36.029">I&apos;M TALKING DELI TALK.</p>
<p begin="00:01:36.029" end="00:01:40.868">THE TURMOIL IN NORTH AFTERNOON A OR WHAT WE PERSIST IN CALLING </p>
<p begin="00:01:40.868" end="00:01:42.769">MESS O&apos;THE WHOLE POTAMIA REGION.</p>
<p begin="00:01:42.769" end="00:01:48.275">THE REVOLUTION WAVE THAT BEGAN IN TUNISIA AND SPREAD TO EGYPT MAY WELL SURPRISE EVEN </p>
<p begin="00:01:48.275" end="00:01:50.277">EXPERIENCED OBSERVERS OF THIS REGION.</p>
<p begin="00:01:50.277" end="00:01:52.045">BUT A PEOPLE&apos;S REVOLT IN LIBYA,</p>
<p begin="00:01:52.045" end="00:01:56.717">A COUNTRY POSSESSING A RARE COMBINATION OF MASSIVE OIL RESERVES, WIDESPREAD POVERTY AND </p>
<p begin="00:01:56.717" end="00:02:02.055">A BAT (BEEP) LEADER WHO ON A GOOD DAY RESEMBLES A WAX FIGURE OF DAN ANY TREJO THAT&apos;S BEEN </p>
<p begin="00:02:02.055" end="00:02:04.191">LEFT OUT IN THE SUN...</p>
<p begin="00:02:04.191" end="00:02:15.068">(LAUGHTER) (APPLAUSE) THE UPRISING&apos;S TARGET, PRESIDENT FOR WHAT LITTLE REMAINS OF HIS </p>
<p begin="00:02:15.068" end="00:02:18.939">LIFE, MOAMMAR QADDAFI...</p>
<p begin="00:02:18.939" end="00:02:21.909">(LAUGHTER) ... HAS ALWAYS DEFIED DESCRIPTION.</p>
<p begin="00:02:21.909" end="00:02:26.680">ALTHOUGH I PERSONALLY FAVOR WHAT WOULD HAPPEN IF JIM HENSON HAD MADE A MUPPET VERSION OF PRINCE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:26.680" end="00:02:28.582">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:02:28.582" end="00:02:34.688">&gt;&gt; YOUNG REVOLUTIONARY, 1970s HIPSTER, PROUD BEDOUIN AND AS THE LONDON PRESS DESCRIBED HIM,</p>
<p begin="00:02:34.688" end="00:02:37.758">A CROSS BETWEEN MICHAEL JACKSON AND FILL SPECTER.</p>
<p begin="00:02:37.758" end="00:02:43.197">HATES ELEVATORS, LOVES FLAMENCO.</p>
<p begin="00:02:43.197" end="00:02:45.098">&gt;&gt; Jon: THAT&apos;S FROM HIS E-HARMONY PROFILE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:45.098" end="00:02:49.937">(LAUGHTER) BUT, BY THE WAY, LOVE FLAS MENTION CO-, HATESS ELEVATORS,</p>
<p begin="00:02:49.937" end="00:02:54.241">EXPLAINS WHY QADDAFI INVENTED THE FLA-MESCALATOR.</p>
<p begin="00:02:54.241" end="00:02:57.311">THAT INVENTION PLUS OIL RESERVES MADE HIM A WEALTHY MAN.</p>
<p begin="00:02:57.311" end="00:03:04.218">NOW, QADDAFI, WHO UNNAMED SOURCES HAVE SAID RESEMBLES A 1991 LIE FELL RICHIE AFTER HE&apos;D </p>
<p begin="00:03:04.218" end="00:03:08.655">TAKEN A QUICK PEEK INSIDE THE ARK OF THE COVENANT...</p>
<p begin="00:03:08.655" end="00:03:15.162">(LAUGHTER) WE HAVE LIKE A HUNDRED OF THESE AND I HAVE TO GET THEM OUT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:15.162" end="00:03:19.066">WE DON&apos;T KNOW HOW LONG THIS GUY IS GOING TO LAST AND THESE DESCRIPTIONS ARE...</p>
<p begin="00:03:19.066" end="00:03:24.371">(LAUGHTER) QADDAFI&apos;S ALREADY LOST CONTROL OF LIBYA&apos;S EASTERN HALF,</p>
<p begin="00:03:24.371" end="00:03:28.208">INCLUDING THE CITY OF BENGHAZI WHERE WEDNESDAY CROWDS TOOK TO THE STREETS TO CELEBRATE THEIR </p>
<p begin="00:03:28.208" end="00:03:33.480">FREEDOM AND VENT DECADES OF SUPPRESSED RAGE AT LARRY FROM THE THREE STOOGES.</p>
<p begin="00:03:33.480" end="00:03:36.517">(LAUGHTER) I DON&apos;T KNOW WHY THEY&apos;RE KICKING THAT GUY.</p>
<p begin="00:03:36.517" end="00:03:41.688">SINCE THE UNREST BEGAN, QADDAFI HAS TAKEN A VARIETY OF TACKS TO CONNECT WITH THOSE IN THE </p>
<p begin="00:03:41.688" end="00:03:43.156">COUNTRY STILL LOYAL TO HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:03:43.156" end="00:03:48.061">SUCH AS REMINDING THEM HOW IMPORTANT THEY ARE TO HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:03:48.061" end="00:03:52.132">&gt;&gt; ( translated ): WITH THE SWORD... OH, IT&apos;S RAINING, I WAS </p>
<p begin="00:03:52.132" end="00:03:56.803">GOING TO TALK TO THE YOUTH IN GREEN SQUARE AND SPEND THE NIGHT WITH THEM TONIGHT BUT IT IS RAINING.</p>
<p begin="00:03:56.803" end="00:03:57.871">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:03:57.871" end="00:04:03.010">&gt;&gt; Jon: YES, I TRULY DID WANT TO RAISE MY CITIZEN&apos;S SOLIDARITY </p>
<p begin="00:04:03.010" end="00:04:08.248">WITH THOSE WHO WILL SOON BE BATTLING THE DETERMINED OPPOSITION IN WHICH WHAT WILL BE </p>
<p begin="00:04:08.248" end="00:04:11.318">A FIGHT TO THE DEATH, BUT, YOU KNOW, THE HUMIDITY...</p>
<p begin="00:04:11.318" end="00:04:26.099">(LAUGHTER) MY THEIR THE RAIN, I GET LIKE A CRAZY JEW-FRO.</p>
<p begin="00:04:26.099" end="00:04:31.405">SOON THEREAFTER QADDAFI REALIZED HE WOULD HAVE TO LOSE THE UMBRELLA, TAKE THINGS UP A NOTCH </p>
<p begin="00:04:31.405" end="00:04:35.676">PERHAPS DITCHING THE CHRISTOPHER WALKEN TRANSLATOR WOULDN&apos;T HURT EITHER.</p>
<p begin="00:04:35.676" end="00:04:40.581">&gt;&gt; ( translated ): THOSE WHO CHALLENGE ANGER, I GREET YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:04:40.581" end="00:04:42.449">WE DEFIED AMERICA FROM HERE,</p>
<p begin="00:04:42.449" end="00:04:44.952">AMERICA WITH ITS POWER.</p>
<p begin="00:04:44.952" end="00:04:49.923">WE DEFIED THE ATOMIC... THE WORLD ATOMIC POWER.</p>
<p begin="00:04:49.923" end="00:04:59.900">A SMALL GROUP OF YOUTH WHO HAVE BEEN GIVEN HALLUCINATION PILLS ARE RAISING RAZING THE POLICE </p>
<p begin="00:04:59.900" end="00:05:03.303">STATIONS HERE AND THERE LIKE RATS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:03.303" end="00:05:04.338">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:05:04.338" end="00:05:08.575">&gt;&gt; Jon: A LITTLE CHRISTOPHER WALKEN WITH A LITTLE BORAT IN THERE AS WELL.</p>
<p begin="00:05:08.575" end="00:05:13.580">(LAUGHTER) SO YOU&apos;RE BLAMING AMERICA AND THE WORLD&apos;S ATOMIC POWERS AND </p>
<p begin="00:05:13.580" end="00:05:16.250">WHATEVER THE HELL HALLUCINATION PILLS ARE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:16.250" end="00:05:16.984">CLASSIC STUFF.</p>
<p begin="00:05:16.984" end="00:05:20.053">I&apos;M NOT SURE IT&apos;S GOING TO DO THE TRICK THIS TIME, QADDAFI.</p>
<p begin="00:05:20.053" end="00:05:24.558">WITH ALL THE CONSTANT CHANGES AND NUTTY TALK, IT MAKES YOU WONDER HOW A GUY LIKE THIS HELD </p>
<p begin="00:05:24.558" end="00:05:25.659">POWER FOR 42 YEARS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:25.659" end="00:05:29.429">HE HAS TO HAVE SOMETHING MORE CONVINCING UP HIS SLEEVE, A SLEEVE HE APPEARS TO HAVE </p>
<p begin="00:05:29.429" end="00:05:34.501">BORROWED FROM BROADWAY LEGEND TINE DALEY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:34.501" end="00:05:37.571">WE REALLY COULD DUES THIS ALL NIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:37.571" end="00:05:38.839">WHAT&apos;S HIS ACE IN THE HOLE?</p>
<p begin="00:05:38.839" end="00:05:43.243">&gt;&gt; THE LEADER CALLED ON HIS SUPPORTERS TO ATTACK AND KILL DEMONSTRATORS, HUNTING THEM DOWN </p>
<p begin="00:05:43.243" end="00:05:44.044">HOUSE TO HOUSE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:44.044" end="00:05:49.316">&gt;&gt; A CATASTROPHE FUELED NOT JUST BY THE LIBYAN MILITARY BUT REPORTEDLY BY PAID MERCENARIES </p>
<p begin="00:05:49.316" end="00:05:51.151">FROM NEIGHBORING COUNTRIES.</p>
<p begin="00:05:51.151" end="00:05:54.922">HIRED GUNS OF CHAD, NIGER AND ZIMBABWE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:54.922" end="00:05:58.392">&gt;&gt; OH, THAT&apos;S RIGHT HE&apos;S A (BEEP), I FORGOT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:58.392" end="00:06:01.862">HIRING OUTSOURCED AFRICAN MERCENARYS TO KILL HIS OWN PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:01.862" end="00:06:07.034">WHERE DO YOU EVEN FIND PEOPLE WHO WILL L DO THAT JOB?</p>
<p begin="00:06:07.034" end="00:06:10.370">Actualmonster.com?</p>
<p begin="00:06:10.370" end="00:06:14.541">(LAUGHTER) BUT WITH HIS GRIP ON POWER GROWING MORE TENUOUS BY THE HOUR </p>
<p begin="00:06:14.541" end="00:06:19.446">AND OLD STANDBYS LIKE AMERICA HATRED AND BLOODY REPRESSION NOT WORKING, IT WAS TIME FOR QADDAFI </p>
<p begin="00:06:19.446" end="00:06:24.818">TO THROW A HAIL MARY, OR WHATEVER ITS APPROPRIATE REGIONAL AND RELIGIOUS EQUIVALENT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:24.818" end="00:06:30.324">&gt;&gt; ( translated ): ONCE THEY DRINK THESE PILLS, THEY LET THEM GO OUT ON THE STREETS AND START </p>
<p begin="00:06:30.324" end="00:06:31.892">COMMITTING CRIMINAL ACTS.</p>
<p begin="00:06:31.892" end="00:06:37.531">THOSE ARE THE ONES WHO ARE UNDER BIN LADEN&apos;S INFLUENCE AND AUTHORITY.</p>
<p begin="00:06:37.531" end="00:06:38.265">&gt;&gt; Jon: WHOA!</p>
<p begin="00:06:38.265" end="00:06:40.434">(LAUGHTER) WAIT A SECOND.</p>
<p begin="00:06:40.434" end="00:06:48.308">FOR 42 YEARS YOU FED AMERICA A TON OF (BEEP), COMMITTED DROOISS AGAINST US, FINALLY AN UPRISEING </p>
<p begin="00:06:48.308" end="00:06:52.379">IS GOING TO KICK YOU DOWN AND WE HAVE TO SHARE CREDIT WITH THIS GUY?</p>
<p begin="00:06:52.379" end="00:06:58.051">(LAUGHTER) WAIT A SECOND, MAYBE IT&apos;S TRUE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:58.051" end="00:07:03.190">WHICH WOULD MEAN RIGHT NOW LIBYA IS A FIGHT BETWEEN AFRICAN MERCENARIES WHO ARE RUTHLESS AND </p>
<p begin="00:07:03.190" end="00:07:04.625">AL QAEDA.</p>
<p begin="00:07:04.625" end="00:07:08.595">THIS MIGHT BE A GOOD TIME FOR THE UNITED STATES TO SLOWLY BACK OUT OF THE ROOM.</p>
<p begin="00:07:08.595" end="00:07:15.636">(LAUGHTER) BECAUSE THAT IS SOME ALIEN VERSUS PREDATOR [NO AUDIO].</p>
<p begin="00:07:15.636" end="00:07:19.373">(LAUGHTER) AND WHILE PRESIDENT OBAMA HAD REFRAINED FROM PUBLIC STATEMENTS </p>
<p begin="00:07:19.373" end="00:07:24.344">ON THE LIBYAN CRISIS UNTIL YESTERDAY, CAREFULLY CAB BRETING HIS MESSAGE AS TO NOT FURTHER </p>
<p begin="00:07:24.344" end="00:07:31.785">UNTETHER A MAN WHO EASE CONFUSED WITH THE BALL FROM CASTWAYWAY,</p>
<p begin="00:07:31.785" end="00:07:38.192">WILSON, IF WILSON DRESSED LIKE A JEDI NIGHT... OKAY, WE&apos;RE RUNNING OUT OF STEAM WITH HIM,</p>
<p begin="00:07:38.192" end="00:07:39.960">I&apos;M NOT GOING TO LIE TO YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:07:39.960" end="00:07:42.196">OTHER WORLD LEADERS WERE LESS CIRCUMSTANCE SPECT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:42.196" end="00:07:46.600">&gt;&gt; ( translated ): IT IS UNIMAGINABLE THAT THERE IS SOMEONE WHO THE ABLE TO KILL AND </p>
<p begin="00:07:46.600" end="00:07:48.535">BOMBARD HIS OWN PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:48.535" end="00:07:55.075">HOW CAN A RULER BOMBARD HIS OWN PEOPLE AND THEN SAY &quot;I WILL KILL ANYONE WHO OPPOSES ME&quot;?</p>
<p begin="00:07:55.075" end="00:07:58.078">THIS IS ABSOLUTELY UNACCEPTABLE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:58.078" end="00:08:03.350">I THINK THE WHOLE WORLD WAS APPALLED AT WHAT HAPPENED IN LIBYA.</p>
<p begin="00:08:03.350" end="00:08:07.187">IT WAS VERY BAD BEHAVIOR AND I HOPE THEY WILL MAKE UP FOR THAT </p>
<p begin="00:08:07.187" end="00:08:10.324">AND MEET THEIR PEOPLE&apos;S DEMANDS.</p>
<p begin="00:08:10.324" end="00:08:12.459">&gt;&gt; Jon: WHAT THE WHAT?</p>
<p begin="00:08:12.459" end="00:08:17.531">(LAUGHTER) MAHMOUD AHMADINEJAD IS DISAPPOINTED THAT QADDAFI WOULD FIRE ON HIS OWN PROTESTING PEOPLE.</p>
<p begin="00:08:17.531" end="00:08:25.572">I&apos;LL TELL YOU WHAT MAY BE THE SCARIEST THING ABOUT THIS WHOLE SITUATION, I THINK IRAN HAS </p>
<p begin="00:08:25.572" end="00:08:28.842">FINALLY MASTERED THE TECHNOLOGY TO WEAPONIZE IRONY.</p>
<p begin="00:08:28.842" end="00:08:30.978">(LAUGHTER) WE&apos;LL BE RIGHT BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:08:30.978" end="00:08:31.044"> </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
