<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:06.740" end="00:00:07.841">&gt;&gt; WELCOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:07.841" end="00:00:10.777">MY GUESTS TONIGHT A FORMER MEMBER OF NAVY SEAL TEAM 6,</p>
<p begin="00:00:10.777" end="00:00:16.583">HIS NEW BOOK IS CALLED SEAL TEAM 6 MEMOIRS OF AN ELITE NAVY SEAL SNIPER.</p>
<p begin="00:00:16.583" end="00:00:25.359">WELCOME TO THE PROGRAM HOWARD WASDIN, SIR.</p>
<p begin="00:00:25.359" end="00:00:26.560">&gt;&gt; THANKS FOR BEING HERE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:26.560" end="00:00:28.128">&gt;&gt; A GREAT HONOR.</p>
<p begin="00:00:28.128" end="00:00:28.595">&gt;&gt; TREMENDOUS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:28.595" end="00:00:29.496">&gt;&gt; JUST LIKE TO SAY HELLO,</p>
<p begin="00:00:29.496" end="00:00:32.933">TAKE THAT APPLAUSE AND DIRECT IT TO THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO ARE SERVING NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:00:32.933" end="00:00:37.738">&gt;&gt; SERVING RIGHT NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:00:37.738" end="00:00:44.912">&gt;&gt; I THINK A LOT OF PEOPLE DON&apos;T REALIZE SEAL TEAM SIX IS AN ONGOING ELITE SUBSET </p>
<p begin="00:00:44.912" end="00:00:47.614">OF THE SEAL TEAMS; IS THAT CORRECT?</p>
<p begin="00:00:47.614" end="00:00:49.483">&gt;&gt; I DON&apos;T KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN BY SUBSET.</p>
<p begin="00:00:49.483" end="00:00:51.018">THEY HAVE A DIFFERENT MISSION, JOHN.</p>
<p begin="00:00:51.018" end="00:00:54.087">THEY ARE THE TIER 1 COUNTERTERRORIST UNITS.</p>
<p begin="00:00:54.087" end="00:00:57.157">WHICH MEANS THEY HAVE THE ASSETS, THE TRAINING,</p>
<p begin="00:00:57.157" end="00:00:59.927">CAPABILITIES TO DEPLOY ANYWHERE AT A MOMENT&apos;S NOTICE.</p>
<p begin="00:00:59.927" end="00:01:00.294">&gt;&gt; RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:00.294" end="00:01:02.663">&gt;&gt; AND DO THIS TYPE OF OP THAT YOU SAW ON ME FIRST.</p>
<p begin="00:01:02.663" end="00:01:09.303">&gt;&gt; I GUESS WHAT I AM SAYING IS THERE ARE OTHER NAVY SEAL TEAMS THAT ARE NOT PART OF SIX.</p>
<p begin="00:01:09.303" end="00:01:11.138">&gt;&gt; THERE ARE OTHER NUMBER TEAMS, THAT&apos;S RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:11.138" end="00:01:15.342">&gt;&gt; AND HOW, DOES THEIR TRAINING DIFFER FROM THE OTHER NAVY SEALS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:15.342" end="00:01:19.613">I KNOW IT DIFFERENTS FROM LET&apos;S SAY THE REGULAR NAVY BUT HOW WOULD IT DIFFERENT </p>
<p begin="00:01:19.613" end="00:01:21.348">FROM EVEN THE OTHER NAVY SEALS?</p>
<p begin="00:01:21.348" end="00:01:23.684">&gt;&gt; LET ME BE VERY CLEAR ON ONE POINT HERE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:23.684" end="00:01:29.122">JUST BECAUSE ARE YOU A MEMBER OF SEAL TEAM 6, OR A MORE ELITE SEAL, ALL SEALS ARE ELITE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:29.122" end="00:01:32.259">IT JUST MEANS YOU&apos;VE DECIDED TO HAVE A DIFFERENT LIFETILE.</p>
<p begin="00:01:32.259" end="00:01:37.097">AND WHAT I MEAN BY THAT IS YOU ARE EVEN MORE COMMITTED TO DOING THIS TYPE OF JOB IT </p>
<p begin="00:01:37.097" end="00:01:39.733">BECOMES A LIFESTYLE DAY IN AND DAY OUT OF PRACTICING,</p>
<p begin="00:01:39.733" end="00:01:40.767">TRAINING, NEVER ENDING.</p>
<p begin="00:01:40.767" end="00:01:46.940">AND THAT&apos;S WHY YOU HAVE ABOUT PROBABLY A SIX TO EIGHT YEAR TRAINING LIFE SPAN.</p>
<p begin="00:01:46.940" end="00:01:52.846">&gt;&gt; WHILE YOU&apos;RE ACTUALLY THERE, BECAUSE YOU PHYSICALLY JUST CAN&apos;T KEEP DOING THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:52.846" end="00:01:57.217">YOU MENTALLY CAN&apos;T KEEP DOING THAT AND YOUR FAMILY IS GOING TO SUFFER TOO </p>
<p begin="00:01:57.217" end="00:02:03.624">BECAUSE IF YOU HAVE GOT KIDS LIKE I HAVE, YOU COULDN&apos;T SERVE TWO MASTERS, IT COST </p>
<p begin="00:02:03.624" end="00:02:06.727">ME MY WIFE AND KIDS BECAUSE I WAS MORE MARRIED TO THE TEAM.</p>
<p begin="00:02:06.727" end="00:02:08.128">SO IF YOU GO TO THIS TEAM,</p>
<p begin="00:02:08.128" end="00:02:11.865">IT&apos;S ALL OR NOTHING, YOU HAVE TO BE COMPLETELY DEDICATED AND YOU KNOW, MOST </p>
<p begin="00:02:11.865" end="00:02:16.069">WIVES DON&apos;T LIKE IT WHEN A HUSBAND WAKES UP AND SAYS HEY, MY PAGER IS GOING OFF,</p>
<p begin="00:02:16.069" end="00:02:18.138">I WILL SEE YOU MAYBE IN A FEW MONTHS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:18.138" end="00:02:20.174">&gt;&gt; AND YOU REALLY DO LIVE LIKE A SHADOW.</p>
<p begin="00:02:20.174" end="00:02:23.577">YOU KIND OF MOVE AND DO THAT YOU WERE IN MOGADISHU.</p>
<p begin="00:02:23.577" end="00:02:25.913">&gt;&gt; THAT WAS MY CAREER ENDER,</p>
<p begin="00:02:25.913" end="00:02:30.417">THE WHOLE BLACKHAWK DOWN OP I GOT SHOT THREE TIMES IN THAT OP.</p>
<p begin="00:02:30.417" end="00:02:36.089">THERE ARE PARALLELS HERE WE DON&apos;T NEED TO MISS BETWEEN THE MOGADISHU BLACKHAWK DOWN </p>
<p begin="00:02:36.089" end="00:02:39.893">OP AND A BATA BAD OP.</p>
<p begin="00:02:39.893" end="00:02:43.630">LESSONS LEARN, 234 SOMALIA WE DIDN&apos;T HAVE OPERATIONAL SECURITY, WORKING WITH THE </p>
<p begin="00:02:43.630" end="00:02:47.100">UNITED NATIONS, WITH THESE OTHER COUNTRIES SO PEOPLE KNEW WHEN WE WERE COMING,</p>
<p begin="00:02:47.100" end="00:02:48.402">LEAVING, WHAT WE WERE DOING.</p>
<p begin="00:02:48.402" end="00:02:51.471">AND I&apos;M A REPUBLICAN BUT THE PRESIDENT GOT IT RIGHT HERE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:51.471" end="00:03:00.247">I&apos;M ACTUALLY THINKING MORE AND MORE ABOUT THIS GUY BEING A REALLY GOOD PRESIDENT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:00.247" end="00:03:01.515">&gt;&gt; WHAT DID HE GET RIGHT?</p>
<p begin="00:03:01.515" end="00:03:04.585">&gt;&gt; WHAT HE GOT RIGHT IS TWO THINGS ACTUALLY THREE THINGS IT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:04.585" end="00:03:09.556">ONE THING DEFINITELY WAS OPERATIONAL SECURITY, HE DID NOT TELL PAKISTAN WE WERE COMING.</p>
<p begin="00:03:09.556" end="00:03:12.960">I KNOW THAT MAKES US BAD PEOPLE BECAUSE WE DID SOMETHING ON THEIR FOREIGN SOIL.</p>
<p begin="00:03:12.960" end="00:03:15.429">WE DIDN&apos;T KILL 3,000 OF THEIR PEOPLE, BUT YOU KNOW,</p>
<p begin="00:03:15.429" end="00:03:19.199">SO WE WENT OVER THERE AND DID THAT AND DIDN&apos;T LET THEM KNOW WE WERE COMING SO THAT </p>
<p begin="00:03:19.199" end="00:03:20.667">KEPT OUR PEOPLE SAFE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:20.667" end="00:03:22.236">MADE THE MISSION.</p>
<p begin="00:03:22.236" end="00:03:26.940">&gt;&gt; DO YOU THINK THEY DID THAT BECAUSE THEY FELT THAT THAT WOULD COMPROMISE, THEY </p>
<p begin="00:03:26.940" end="00:03:29.643">FELT THEY COULD NOT TRUST THAT CHAIN OF COMMAND ON THE OTHER SIDE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:29.643" end="00:03:32.412">&gt;&gt; AND SINCE I&apos;M NOT RUNNING FOR OFFICE AND I DON&apos;T WANT </p>
<p begin="00:03:32.412" end="00:03:38.619">YOUR VOTE, ABSOLUTELY SECOND THING IS HE GOT IT RIGHT WITH THIS BURIAL AT SEA.</p>
<p begin="00:03:38.619" end="00:03:39.820">THAT WAS INGENUOUS.</p>
<p begin="00:03:39.820" end="00:03:42.890">&gt;&gt; THAT WAS MAYBE ONE OF THE MOST CONTROVERSIAL ASPECTS OF IT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:42.890" end="00:03:43.924">&gt;&gt; YEAH, BUT THINK ABOUT IT,</p>
<p begin="00:03:43.924" end="00:03:48.328">IF WE HAD GIVEN THEM SOMEWHERE TO GO AND PAY HOMAGE TO THIS, YOU KNOW,</p>
<p begin="00:03:48.328" end="00:03:50.464">EVIL PERSON OR WHATEVER THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN TERRIBLE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:50.464" end="00:03:53.600">THE OTHER THING HE GOT RIGHT WAS NOT RELEASING THE PICTURES.</p>
<p begin="00:03:53.600" end="00:03:57.371">I THINK HE GOT IT RIGHT ON ALL THREE THINGS AND I&apos;M SITTING HERE GOING YOU KNOW </p>
<p begin="00:03:57.371" end="00:04:01.408">WHAT I DIDN&apos;T VOTE FOR THE GUY BUT HEY, AS AMERICA WE GOT TO ADMIT WHEN A </p>
<p begin="00:04:01.408" end="00:04:03.443">PRESIDENT GETS IT RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:03.443" end="00:04:07.514">&gt;&gt; I ALWAYS THOUGHT, I ALWAYS FEEL LIKE WE DON&apos;T KNOW ENOUGH ABOUT WAR BUT I </p>
<p begin="00:04:07.514" end="00:04:12.653">THINK MAYBE IN THIS PARTICULAR SITUATION IN TERMS OF SECURITY, I HAD NOT </p>
<p begin="00:04:12.653" end="00:04:17.391">REALIZED JUST HOW SECRETIVE THE SEAL TEAMS HAVE TO BE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:17.391" end="00:04:20.694">I MEAN EVEN IN YOUR BOOK THERE ARE FACES BLACKED OUT STILL.</p>
<p begin="00:04:20.694" end="00:04:23.463">THERE IS AN ANONYMITY THAT NEEDS TO OCCUR.</p>
<p begin="00:04:23.463" end="00:04:24.064">&gt;&gt; SURE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:24.064" end="00:04:25.832">&gt;&gt; AND MOGADISHU WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:04:25.832" end="00:04:26.867">WHEN YOU WERE INJURED.</p>
<p begin="00:04:26.867" end="00:04:31.338">&gt;&gt; I WAS PART OF THE FAILED OP TO TAKE DOWN THE, YOU KNOW, THE HOTEL THAT DAY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:31.338" end="00:04:34.908">I WAS SHOT THE FIRST TIME AT THE TARGET HOTEL.</p>
<p begin="00:04:34.908" end="00:04:36.109">SHOT THE SECOND TIME,</p>
<p begin="00:04:36.109" end="00:04:40.881">PICKING UP RANGERS OFF THE STREET AND SHOT THE THIRD TIME TRYING TO GET THE HELL OUT OF THERE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:40.881" end="00:04:41.882">IN A HUMVEE.</p>
<p begin="00:04:41.882" end="00:04:49.656">&gt;&gt; HOW LONG DID THE PROCESS LAST WHERE YOU CONTINUED TO OPERATE WHILE HAVING BEEN SHOT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:49.656" end="00:04:50.657">&gt;&gt; ABOUT FOUR AND A HALF HOURS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:50.657" end="00:04:52.659">BUT WHILE WE ARE TALKING ABOUT THAT -- </p>
<p begin="00:04:52.659" end="00:04:54.795">&gt;&gt; NO, LET&apos;S NOT GLORIFY THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:54.795" end="00:04:56.129">LET&apos;S JUST STOP FOR A SECOND.</p>
<p begin="00:04:56.129" end="00:04:59.166">BECAUSE YOU AND I IT VERY SIMILAR, AND I DON&apos;T,</p>
<p begin="00:04:59.166" end="00:05:02.636">OBVIOUSLY WANT TO BRAG, BUT I&apos;M GOING TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:05:02.636" end="00:05:06.773">YOU-- YOU HAVEN&apos;T NECESSARILY BEEN AROUND IN A WHILE BUT I KNOW YOU WANT TO </p>
<p begin="00:05:06.773" end="00:05:08.475">SEE THAT, RIGHT THERE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:08.475" end="00:05:11.478">LET ME TELL YOU MY WAR STORY.</p>
<p begin="00:05:11.478" end="00:05:14.047">&gt;&gt; IS THAT ON THE PENIS WHEEL?</p>
<p begin="00:05:14.047" end="00:05:19.052">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) </p>
<p begin="00:05:19.052" end="00:05:23.857">&gt;&gt; THAT THING IS MUCH SHARPER THAN IT LOOKS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:23.857" end="00:05:29.329">&gt;&gt; IT BRINGS UP A POINT, YOU KNOW, YOU&apos;RE LIVING A LIFE THAT IS SO BEYOND IN </p>
<p begin="00:05:29.329" end="00:05:33.767">COMPARISON TO WHAT WE CAN IMAGINE AND THEN THIS STORY COMES UP IN ABBOTTABAD.</p>
<p begin="00:05:33.767" end="00:05:35.969">HOW DO YOU READJUST TO CIVILIAN LIFE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:35.969" end="00:05:38.272">ARE YOU A CHIROPRACTOR NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:05:38.272" end="00:05:40.307">YOU PICKED YOUR LIFE UP AND HAVE DONE THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:40.307" end="00:05:45.746">BUT HOW HAVE YOU BEEN ABLE TO READJUST TO SORT OF THIS IDEA THAT YOU ARE LIVING </p>
<p begin="00:05:45.746" end="00:05:46.914">LIKE A NORMAL CITIZEN?</p>
<p begin="00:05:46.914" end="00:05:50.851">&gt;&gt; YOU KNOW WHAT, AND THAT&apos;S A GREAT QUESTION AND A LOT OF WHAT THE BOOK IS ABOUT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:50.851" end="00:05:52.252">ANYBODY WHO BUYS THIS BOOK,</p>
<p begin="00:05:52.252" end="00:05:53.620">IT&apos;S NOT A WAR STORY BOOK,</p>
<p begin="00:05:53.620" end="00:05:55.355">NOT A WARMONGERING BOOK.</p>
<p begin="00:05:55.355" end="00:05:59.426">IT&apos;S ABOUT OVERCOMING ADVERSITY, OVERCOMING ADVERSITY IN MY EARLY LIFE </p>
<p begin="00:05:59.426" end="00:06:01.028">AND THEN THE QUESTION YOU JUST WENT INTO.</p>
<p begin="00:06:01.028" end="00:06:02.563">THE LOWEST POINT OF MY LIFE,</p>
<p begin="00:06:02.563" end="00:06:07.334">JOHN, WAS AFTER GETTING SHOT THREE TIMES, GOING THROUGH A DIVORCE, THINKING I WAS WEAK </p>
<p begin="00:06:07.334" end="00:06:13.540">BECAUSE LOOKING BACK WITH MY DOCTOR HAD ON NOW, NOT REALIZING I HAD POST TRAUMATIC STRESS AND THIS </p>
<p begin="00:06:13.540" end="00:06:17.110">OTHER THING CALLED SURVIVOR&apos;S GUILT THAT I DIDN&apos;T FIND OUT ABOUT UNTIL YEARS LATER.</p>
<p begin="00:06:17.110" end="00:06:21.215">WHY I WAS ALLOWED TO LIVE AND SO MANY GOOD PEOPLE WERE ALLOWED TO DIE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:21.215" end="00:06:26.119">SO TRANSITIONING FROM ROCK STAR TO ROCK BOTTOM, AND TRYING TO ASSIMILATE BACK </p>
<p begin="00:06:26.119" end="00:06:28.222">INTO SOCIETY WAS ALMOST THE END OF ME.</p>
<p begin="00:06:28.222" end="00:06:31.291">AND LUCKILY, GOD PUT THE RIGHT WOMAN IN MY PATH.</p>
<p begin="00:06:31.291" end="00:06:36.496">SHE PICKED ME UP, DUSTED ME OFF, TAUGHT ME INTO GOING BACK INTO SCHOOL TO BE A </p>
<p begin="00:06:36.496" end="00:06:40.534">CHIROPRACTOR, TALKED ME INTO FINISHING MY BOOK AND I OWE EVERYTHING TO HER.</p>
<p begin="00:06:40.534" end="00:06:42.169">&gt;&gt; IT&apos;S AN AMAZING STORY.</p>
<p begin="00:06:42.169" end="00:06:44.271">WE THANK YOU FOR YOUR SERVICE AND YOUR STORY.</p>
<p begin="00:06:44.271" end="00:06:46.273">YOU CAN STATE RYE THERE.</p>
<p begin="00:06:46.273" end="00:06:48.642">SALE TEAM SIX, ON THE BOOK SHELVES NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:06:48.642" end="00:06:50.077">IT&apos;S A WONDERFUL BOOK.</p>
<p begin="00:06:50.077" end="00:06:50.878">HOWARD WASDIN, SIR </p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
