<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<tt xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#styling" xmlns:ttm="http://www.w3.org/2006/10/ttaf1#metadata" >
<body tts:textAlign="center">
<div ttm:role="captions">
<p begin="00:00:02.536" end="00:00:06.406">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) </p>
<p begin="00:00:06.406" end="00:00:07.608">&gt;&gt; Jon: WELCOME BACK.</p>
<p begin="00:00:07.608" end="00:00:10.377">MY GUEST TONIGHT, HE SERVED IN THE BUSH ADMINISTRATION&apos;S OFFICE </p>
<p begin="00:00:10.377" end="00:00:13.614">OF LEGAL COUNSEL, HE&apos;S CURRENTLY A PROFESSOR AT HARVARD LAW SCHOOL.</p>
<p begin="00:00:13.614" end="00:00:18.886">HIS NEW BOOK IS CALLED &quot;POWER AND CONSTRAINT: THE ACCOUNTABLE PRESIDENCY AFTER 9/11.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:00:18.886" end="00:00:21.722">PLEASE WELCOME BACK TO THE PROGRAM JACK GOLDSMITH!</p>
<p begin="00:00:21.722" end="00:00:28.061">(CHEERS AND APPLAUSE) HOW ARE YOU?</p>
<p begin="00:00:28.061" end="00:00:36.170">JACK, IT&apos;S NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN WE HEARD YOU&apos;D WRITTEN A BOOK </p>
<p begin="00:00:36.170" end="00:00:40.807">ABOUT POST-9/11, EXECUTIVE POWER I THOUGHT FOR SURE &quot;POWER AND </p>
<p begin="00:00:40.807" end="00:00:46.446">CONSTRAINT&quot; WOULD BE ABOUT THE UNRESTRAINED EXECUTIVE, THE IMPERIAL PRESIDENCY.</p>
<p begin="00:00:46.446" end="00:00:56.523">YOUR PREMISE SEEMS TO BE THAT OUR ACTUAL CHECKS AND BALANCES HAVE DONE A PRETTY DECENT JOB OF </p>
<p begin="00:00:56.523" end="00:00:58.959">CONSTRAINING EXECUTIVE POWER.</p>
<p begin="00:00:58.959" end="00:00:59.626">&gt;&gt; THAT IS CORRECT.</p>
<p begin="00:00:59.626" end="00:01:03.063">EVERYBODY FOCUSES ON HOW POWERFUL THE POST-9/11 PRESIDENCY IS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:03.063" end="00:01:05.132">AND IT IS POWERFUL.</p>
<p begin="00:01:05.132" end="00:01:08.368">WE&apos;VE FORGOTTEN OR HAVEN&apos;T SEEN ALL THE DIFFERENT WAYS IN WHICH </p>
<p begin="00:01:08.368" end="00:01:14.675">COURTS, THE PRESS, HUMAN RIGHTS ORGANIZATIONS, PEOPLE INSIDE THE EXECUTIVE HAVE PUSHED BACK </p>
<p begin="00:01:14.675" end="00:01:18.111">AGAINST THE PRESIDENCY AND CHANGED WHAT HE&apos;S DOING, BOTH IN THE BUSH ADMINISTRATION AND THE </p>
<p begin="00:01:18.111" end="00:01:18.712">OBAMA ADMINISTRATION.</p>
<p begin="00:01:18.712" end="00:01:21.882">&gt;&gt; Jon: YOU MAKE A POINT ABOUT THERE&apos;S A VERY SMALL GROUP OF </p>
<p begin="00:01:21.882" end="00:01:27.487">CIVIL RIGHTS ATTORNEYS WHO GOT THE BUSH ADMINISTRATION TO ADDRESS INDEFINITE DETENTION AND </p>
<p begin="00:01:27.487" end="00:01:28.255">HABEAS CORPUS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:28.255" end="00:01:32.092">&gt;&gt; THEY WERE VERY SUCCESSFUL IN BRINGING LANDMARK SUPREME COURT CASES.</p>
<p begin="00:01:32.092" end="00:01:33.827">THEY WON SOME VERY IMPORTANT DECISIONS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:33.827" end="00:01:38.398">THEY GOT WHAT THEY WANTED WHICH WAS HABEAS CORPUS JUDICIAL REVIEW OF THE GUANTANAMO DETAINEES.</p>
<p begin="00:01:38.398" end="00:01:40.767">THEY WERE ABLE TO GET 600 OR 700 PEOPLE OUT.</p>
<p begin="00:01:40.767" end="00:01:45.339">BUT WHEN THE COURTS LOOKED AT IT AND CONGRESS GOT INVOLVED AS WELL THEY DECIDED HEY, IT TURNS </p>
<p begin="00:01:45.339" end="00:01:52.145">OUT IT IS LAWFUL TO DETAIN THESE PEOPLE AND GITMO INDEFINITELY AND NOW IT HAS THE IMPRIMATUR OF </p>
<p begin="00:01:52.145" end="00:01:52.913">THE FEDERAL COURTS.</p>
<p begin="00:01:52.913" end="00:01:58.018">&gt;&gt; Jon: IS THAT CONSTRAINING THE PRESIDENCY OR JUST CODIFYING THINGS WE DID NOT THINK WERE </p>
<p begin="00:01:58.018" end="00:02:04.558">POSSIBLE AND HAVE NOW ACCEPTED AND MAYBE SHOULDN&apos;T BECAUSE THIS IS A WAR OF NO END.</p>
<p begin="00:02:04.558" end="00:02:10.430">&gt;&gt; WELL, THAT&apos;S AN IMPORTANT QUESTION, IT&apos;S A BIG QUESTION.</p>
<p begin="00:02:10.430" end="00:02:14.501">WHO IS &quot;WE&quot; THAT THINKS WE SHOULDN&apos;T DO THAT?</p>
<p begin="00:02:14.501" end="00:02:15.536">&gt;&gt; Jon: I MEAN ME AND YOU.</p>
<p begin="00:02:15.536" end="00:02:16.103">(LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:02:16.103" end="00:02:19.873">&gt;&gt; THE COURTS HAVE PUSHED BACK QUITE A LOT AGAINST THE EXECUTIVE AND THEY STILL ALLOW </p>
<p begin="00:02:19.873" end="00:02:23.677">THEM TO DETAIN BUT THE STANDARD IS MUCH NARROWER THAN IT USED TO BE.</p>
<p begin="00:02:23.677" end="00:02:26.413">HIS POWERS ARE NARROWLY CONFINED.</p>
<p begin="00:02:26.413" end="00:02:28.348">HE HAS EXTRAORDINARY POWERS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:28.348" end="00:02:31.652">HE USED MILITARY COMMISSIONS TO ENGAGE IN TARGETED KILLINGS.</p>
<p begin="00:02:31.652" end="00:02:38.792">&gt;&gt; Jon: DOES IT FEEL WORSE BECAUSE OBAMA CAMPAIGNED TO REPEAL THAT STATE OF AFFAIRS?</p>
<p begin="00:02:38.792" end="00:02:43.664">SO MUCH OF HIS RHETORIC WAS &quot;WE DO NOT HAVE TO SACRIFICE OUR </p>
<p begin="00:02:43.664" end="00:02:48.335">VALUES FOR OUR SAFETY&quot; AND THEN HE GOT IN THE OFFICE AND WENT &quot;WELL, ACTUALLY, THAT VALUE </p>
<p begin="00:02:48.335" end="00:02:49.203">COULD GO.&quot; </p>
<p begin="00:02:49.203" end="00:02:54.975">&gt;&gt; RIGHT, AND THIS IS A LARGE PART OF WHAT THE BOOK IS ABOUT BECAUSE OBAMA IN JANUARY OF 2009 </p>
<p begin="00:02:54.975" end="00:03:01.415">EVERYONE THOUGHT THAT EVERYTHING WAS GOING TO CHANGE AND WHAT HAPPENED WAS THAT HE DIDN&apos;T...</p>
<p begin="00:03:01.415" end="00:03:05.652">OBAMA DIDN&apos;T LACK THE COURAGE OF HIS CONVICTIONS ON CIVIL LIBERTIES.</p>
<p begin="00:03:05.652" end="00:03:09.489">HE GOT INTO POWER, HE HAD THE RESPONSIBILITY FOR NATIONAL SECURITY AND IT TURNS OUT THAT A </p>
<p begin="00:03:09.489" end="00:03:15.629">LOT OF THE PRACTICES THAT THE BUSH ADMINISTRATION HAD BEEN ENGAGED IN HAD BEEN CHANGED AND </p>
<p begin="00:03:15.629" end="00:03:17.764">ALTERED SOME QUITE A LOT, SOME QUITE A LITTLE.</p>
<p begin="00:03:17.764" end="00:03:22.069">MUCH HAD BEEN APPROVED BY COURTS AND THE SYSTEM HAD BASICALLY BECOME LEGITIMATED AND WHEN HE </p>
<p begin="00:03:22.069" end="00:03:26.940">HAD THE RESPONSIBILITY FOR KEEPING THE COUNTRY SAFE HE WASN&apos;T GOING TO WALK AWAY FROM </p>
<p begin="00:03:26.940" end="00:03:29.476">THAT LEGITIMATED SYSTEM.</p>
<p begin="00:03:29.476" end="00:03:35.182">AND IN SOME INSTANCES HE TRIED TO WALK AWAY, TRYING TO CLOSE GITMO, TRYING TO HAVE CIVILIAN </p>
<p begin="00:03:35.182" end="00:03:38.919">TRIALS AND HE WASN&apos;T ABLE TO BECAUSE THE SAME FORCES THAT PUSHED BUSH TOWARDS THE CENTER </p>
<p begin="00:03:38.919" end="00:03:41.889">PUSHED OBAMA TOWARDS THE CENTER AS WELL.</p>
<p begin="00:03:41.889" end="00:03:46.226">&gt;&gt; Jon: WE ALSO KNOW THAT CERTAIN OF THOSE CONSTRAINTS WERE INHERENT IN THE WAY THAT </p>
<p begin="00:03:46.226" end="00:03:47.928">THE ORIGINAL REGIME HAD BEEN SET UP.</p>
<p begin="00:03:47.928" end="00:03:51.999">IN OTHER WORDS, YOU COULDN&apos;T TAKE THESE TRIALS TO CIVILIAN COURTS BECAUSE SO MUCH OF THE </p>
<p begin="00:03:51.999" end="00:03:57.604">INFORMATION WE HAD GOTTEN FROM TERRORISTS WAS COERCE SOD IF YOU DID THAT YOU COULDN&apos;T UNRAVEL THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:03:57.604" end="00:04:03.744">&gt;&gt; SOME HE COULDN&apos;T UNRAVEL AND PEOPLE IN GITMO WERE THE HARDEST THING.</p>
<p begin="00:04:03.744" end="00:04:05.512">THAT WAS THE HARDEST SITUATION TO UNRAVEL.</p>
<p begin="00:04:05.512" end="00:04:08.315">&gt;&gt; SO ARE WE JUST TO ACCEPT BECAUSE IT&apos;S BEEN LEGITIMATED </p>
<p begin="00:04:08.315" end="00:04:13.754">THAT THERE ARE INDIVIDUALS RIGHT NOW THAT WE WILL HOLD FOREVER WHO WILL NEVER HAVE AN </p>
<p begin="00:04:13.754" end="00:04:17.858">OPPORTUNITY FOR WHAT WE WOULD CONSIDER A DUE PROCESS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:17.858" end="00:04:21.495">&gt;&gt; WELL, THEY&apos;VE HAD VERY SIGNIFICANT DUE PROCESS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:21.495" end="00:04:24.798">I BET IF YOU GO BACK AND LOOK AT YOUR SHOWS FROM A DECADE AGO....</p>
<p begin="00:04:24.798" end="00:04:26.567">&gt;&gt; Jon: OH, WE WERE SO YOUNG THEN.</p>
<p begin="00:04:26.567" end="00:04:31.371">&gt;&gt; IF YOU LOOK AT THE KIND OF THINGS YOU WERE INSISTING ON BACK THEN I BET ONE WAS JUDICIAL REVIEW.</p>
<p begin="00:04:31.371" end="00:04:35.242">YOU WERE PROBABLY INSISTING ON HABEAS CORPUS.</p>
<p begin="00:04:35.242" end="00:04:40.981">&gt;&gt; Jon: OUR HABEAS CORPUS WEEK WAS VERY POPULAR WITH THE COLLEGE KIDS THAT YEAR, I REMEMBER.</p>
<p begin="00:04:40.981" end="00:04:46.753">&gt;&gt; THE TRUTH IS THAT THE DETAINEES IN WARTIME ARE GETTING MORE PROCEDURAL PROTECTIONS THAN </p>
<p begin="00:04:46.753" end="00:04:51.258">THEY&apos;VE EVER HAD BEFORE AND MANY HAVE BEEN RELEASED EVEN THOUGH THEY WERE FIGHTING FOR THE ENEMY.</p>
<p begin="00:04:51.258" end="00:04:52.092">BUT YOU&apos;RE RIGHT.</p>
<p begin="00:04:52.092" end="00:04:55.329">WE HAVE GOTTEN DOWN NOW TO A NUMBER OF THE ISSUES.</p>
<p begin="00:04:55.329" end="00:04:56.997">THERE ARE PEOPLE THAT ARE...</p>
<p begin="00:04:56.997" end="00:05:01.201">THERE ARE A MILITARY COMMISSION SOME OF THEM, THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO TRY SOME OF THEM IN </p>
<p begin="00:05:01.201" end="00:05:03.036">CIVILIAN COURT BUT CONGRESS WON&apos;T LET HIM.</p>
<p begin="00:05:03.036" end="00:05:07.040">THERE ARE A GROUP OF PEOPLE WHO WILL BE DETAINED INDEFINITELY AND THERE&apos;S NO ALTERNATIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:07.040" end="00:05:11.912">SO WHAT THE GOVERNMENT HAS DONE IS RAMPED UP THE PROTECTIONS TO MAKE SURE THE FACTS ARE RIGHT </p>
<p begin="00:05:11.912" end="00:05:13.914">AND THEY&apos;VE HAD FULL JUDICIAL REVIEW.</p>
<p begin="00:05:13.914" end="00:05:17.584">THAT THE CIRCUMSTANCES OF THEIR... THEIR LIVING CIRCUMSTANCES ARE AS GOOD AS THEY CAN BE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:17.584" end="00:05:20.654">&gt;&gt; Jon: BUT ULTIMATELY WE HAVE TO TRUST THE EXECUTIVE IN THAT.</p>
<p begin="00:05:20.654" end="00:05:22.789">&gt;&gt; I DON&apos;T THINK YOU HAVE TO TRUST THE EXECUTIVE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:22.789" end="00:05:25.092">THE EXECUTIVE HAS TO GO BEFORE THE COURT AND MAKE HIS CASE.</p>
<p begin="00:05:25.092" end="00:05:26.260">&gt;&gt; Jon: MILITARY COURT?</p>
<p begin="00:05:26.260" end="00:05:27.528">&gt;&gt; NO, FEDERAL COURTS.</p>
<p begin="00:05:27.528" end="00:05:31.665">ALL THE PEOPLE IN GOT GO TO...</p>
<p begin="00:05:31.665" end="00:05:35.936">GUANTANAMO BAY GO TO THE SUPREME COURT POTENTIALLY AND THIS IS ONE OF THE GREAT ADVANCES.</p>
<p begin="00:05:35.936" end="00:05:39.106">ONE OF BUSH&apos;S PROBLEMS WAS THAT HE RESISTED JUDICIAL REVIEW AND </p>
<p begin="00:05:39.106" end="00:05:42.576">THAT WAS ONE OF THE MANY REASONS WHY PEOPLE DIDN&apos;T TRUST WHAT HE WAS DOING.</p>
<p begin="00:05:42.576" end="00:05:48.982">&gt;&gt; Jon: ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT GENERAL CIVIL LIBERTIES AND THE SORT OF WINDOW THAT HAS BEEN </p>
<p begin="00:05:48.982" end="00:05:54.588">PUSHED ABOUT DATA MINING, THE GOVERNMENT&apos;S ABILITY TO JUST COLLECT DATA FROM ITS CITIZENS,</p>
<p begin="00:05:54.588" end="00:06:00.093">THIS SUPREME COURT CASE ABOUT STRIP CERTAINS FOR EVEN MINOR INFRACTIONS, THINGS THAT WE ARE </p>
<p begin="00:06:00.093" end="00:06:05.532">JUST TENDING TO ACCEPT AND THE SLIPPERY SLOPE WE GO DOWN WHEN WE DO THAT?</p>
<p begin="00:06:05.532" end="00:06:06.900">&gt;&gt; OF COURSE I WORRY ABOUT IT.</p>
<p begin="00:06:06.900" end="00:06:10.904">I WORRY ABOUT THE SIZE OF THE GOVERNMENT, THE SIZE OF THE NATIONAL SECURITY BUREAUCRACY,</p>
<p begin="00:06:10.904" end="00:06:15.475">THE SIZE OF THE EXECUTIVE BRANCH AND THE AMAZING SCARY POWERS IT HAS AND NOTHING IN MY BOOK </p>
<p begin="00:06:15.475" end="00:06:20.414">SUGGESTS WE SHOULDN&apos;T BE VIGILANT IN QUESTIONING AND CRITICIZING BUT I THINK THERE </p>
<p begin="00:06:20.414" end="00:06:24.518">ARE ALL SORTS OF CONSTRAINTS AND CHECK HERBS AND WATCHERS LOOKING AT THE PRESIDENT TO MAKE SURE </p>
<p begin="00:06:24.518" end="00:06:28.055">WHAT HE&apos;S DOING IS LAWFUL AND USEFUL.</p>
<p begin="00:06:28.055" end="00:06:32.159">&gt;&gt; Jon: BELIEVE ME, I WAS READY TO OPEN THIS UP AND BE RIGHT </p>
<p begin="00:06:32.159" end="00:06:35.229">&quot;WE&apos;RE ALL MONTHS AWAY FROM LIVING IN A GULAG.&quot; (LAUGHTER) </p>
<p begin="00:06:35.229" end="00:06:39.800">BUT YOU MAKE A GOOD CASE THAT THERE IS A VERY HEALTHY SYSTEM IN PLACE THAT ATTACKED THESE </p>
<p begin="00:06:39.800" end="00:06:41.935">EXCESSES AND DOES FIND A WAY,</p>
<p begin="00:06:41.935" end="00:06:48.408">MAYBE NOT IMMEDIATELY TO CONSTRAIN THEM MAYBE NOT BACK TO ITS ORIGINAL FORM.</p>
<p begin="00:06:48.408" end="00:06:52.312">&gt;&gt; THAT&apos;S RIGHT, BACK TO THE ORIGINAL FORM BUT WE&apos;RE NOT IN A PRE-9/11 WORLD.</p>
<p begin="00:06:52.312" end="00:06:58.986">WE HAVEN&apos;T BEEN ATTACKED IN A LONG TIME IN THIS COUNTRY BUT INSIDE THE EXECUTIVE BRANCH </p>
<p begin="00:06:58.986" end="00:07:02.322">THEY&apos;RE WORRIED ABOUT THE NEXT ATTACK AND IT&apos;S NOT A PRE-9/11 </p>
<p begin="00:07:02.322" end="00:07:08.462">WORLD SO WE HAD THIS POWERFUL PRESIDENCY AND AN INDEFINITE WAR AND MY BOOK IS ABOUT THE VARIOUS </p>
<p begin="00:07:08.462" end="00:07:14.234">CONSTRAINTS THAT HAVE GROWN UP TO CHECK AND LEGITIMATE AS IT GOES FORWARD.</p>
<p begin="00:07:14.234" end="00:07:15.569">IT&apos;S NOT JUST THE OVAL OFFICE.</p>
<p begin="00:07:15.569" end="00:07:17.604">I SIT UP IN MY OFFICE AND DO THIS ALL NIGHT SO...</p>
<p begin="00:07:17.604" end="00:07:26.547">(LAUGHTER) IT&apos;S REALLY JUST AN INTERESTING ARGUMENT, SO WELL LAID OUT.</p>
<p begin="00:07:26.547" end="00:07:29.116">&quot;POWER AND CONSTRAINT.&quot; ON THE BOOKSHELVES NOW.</p>
<p begin="00:07:29.116" end="00:07:30.317">OUR FRIEND JACK GOLDSMITH.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
